Hello guys
How's everyone this night, I hope you're having a nice day. What is it Wednesday night?
Welcome in welcome in
I don't know.
I'm wrong.
These headphones aren't charging.
Hey, sit down.
I hear I got the wrong one.
Close my link.
I do need to, like, do some stuff.
I can hold off on it now.
Timeline to my my table screen was cleaned off. I mean, it's one of the last things I had to do in this room
Unfortunately, my I don't think my back is very good anymore. I need to get it back
Always something right guys
Also hold off a little bit on it maybe you can get like a dust blister or something on team horses. They got a lot
That's how I'm being as you know this guy name. Oh, do you guys do you guys do you guys guys know uh, oh 21
You guys know Danny danger or you're a danger ranger
Looks like this guys. He's this guy
Can you please
Get him on my show
We'll get him on this show. That's very cool. Thank you guys
Anybody knows them
I have a little crush on him, but
There he's controversial
Yeah
Yes, hit the like everybody. Thank you. Yeah, but that'd be fun of you. Yeah, I want to show he's pretty funny. I like it
they go
He'll hillbilly
sense sense
Hmm. Yeah guys, we'll see what's gonna happen tonight. It's gonna be interesting. I have a beer in the fridge. Yeah
You don't know if he'll be very nice to me. Hmm. I know, you know, I'm friends with saints too
And so that's gonna be a negative probably in my column, but
I don't have anything I mean, I'm not I'm not
Yeah, he I didn't hear him going off about people on like
People are just want to be IPG stars. I'm maybe I don't know. I don't think he was talking about me, but you know, I don't know
I just kind of threw it out there one time people kind of overreacted about it
Oh well
The show is doing great. Hey
Dixon James Cowboys here the flow key
I have to look I might have looked with his brother. Okay, his brother. What's his brother's brother's not brother's name
Yeah
Well, that's like but that's like what scribbles and scribbles accept me over his brother instead of like my deal with me
He's like, oh go talk to the fourth time. He's like I curious. So I don't know
Like
Directing me away from him
Yeah, oh, yeah, one time I called scribbles on the phone like I called him on the phone on the stream and I was like
Hey, I met you in the venue in the jail like eight years ago
Yeah, we dated he's like what? I was I was jail and I was like, yeah
We uh, well you can read on though and hold hands and appear and stuff
He's like what then the next day he said oh, he heard that he got clips and it said hey
Hey, what's up? Okay, if you got clips and he said oh, he said oh now I got clips and people are saying that
They think I'm by curious or I'm gay for K or gay for pay
And that uh, you know, it's really like so you should date my brother torture
He's they come out of the closet, but I didn't turn that brother didn't come out of the closet
He's not even gay, but you know who did Chris came pretty much. I mean Chris came was like, yeah, he's like
I don't know he's
I don't know if he wasn't kidding he would uh
He would be in a basically a game game bang with you know with me and some women that
Find no, I don't know if I just magical woman, but not there's always a dollar store wig and
Some my wet and wild lipstick and nipolish I'm just kidding. I wouldn't I wouldn't do that
How are we doing tonight guys? Yeah? I mean, let's say it was interesting. I don't want to bring up this person. Everyone knows there's a person. I always
Friends and then they're mad at me the next day. They were friends again
Well, this person to be something's a very routine message. Okay, and they weren't very nice text messages were rude
They were they were complete and they were say, oh
They're like ha ha you
Well words
use the words you
Clueless fool or something like that. You clueless fool. She's like, don't you know that?
You know once I left the chat half your chat left
No
She's like, don't say my name or or else and just all these threats. I remember this
Downs happening. I was like, what's that? I didn't do anything else. I was like, I'm gonna say that and I'm saying the name
It rhymes with
Beheda the rhymes with the either so someone didn't someone did rhyme with the heater in a in a limerick once
I thought was a cute limerick, but
I was cute oh
I didn't say I know I said I didn't say I didn't say I didn't say I didn't say I didn't say I was seen
The I was saying that the heat is okay. I got it was the accident
I didn't say the name. Okay. I didn't say the name. I said fajita. I'm so confused guys.
I wasn't supposed to say it. I kind of said it. Well, they're saying it rhymes with fajita.
Sabrina Carpenter. It sounds like a lot of things. Is he not allowed to say the name if it rhymes?
The name rhymes with Fida. I know, I don't know. I'm not allowed to say it, Kate. I'm not allowed to say it.
I'm banned from even the thought of...
I'm sorry. Okay, maybe.
Hello. Person's name is right. Name's from Spikyta. Can I please say your name? It just makes the show more interesting.
Or, you know, I won't say anything bad. I'll just say, you know, so I don't have to like...
Walk on it. Walk on eggshells. Well, my hair is all
I'm not either to really do to the truth. Okay. Good. Well good. Okay. Well, I wonder to be a truce
The need to your truth would be okay. Let's all have a truth. I'll have it. Why is why isn't you ever choose to beat out?
What why can't I get one of those? I
Know I didn't do any. I don't know
I can't even I don't even I can't even get like a polite text message
She's over fruit making fruits is it with Kate
Geez guys, I am just I'm just I guess
I'm just like I'm not good at like that. You know the show survivor and then like everybody's okay
It's okay. Yeah, let's just revive her and then like everyone he had like
Like getting a little group of them like can I have to like, you know, we get like see where in the future and they probably didn't
It was probably mostly chance that you know
They look like a genius. Oh, I was strategizing the whole time
Probably just like, you know, but it's either pants. Like we all do right, but
I'm not that good at that. I'm not that good at like
I'm gonna like get you off before I'm as I say I don't like those little games
I think if there's like a you know, I'm always the last to be picked for a team anyway
So it's like what maybe the first to be kicked off of a team
But they're fucking have to make it like I
Kind of like where did
Yesterday go I don't know or yeah, I saw yesterday yesterday
Yesterday? Okay. Not sure. Are y'all talking? No, we're not talking. No, we're not talking
about it. I'm rather to say the name, that name here right now because she will be very
upset. So just say the person that name rhymes with fajita. That's the name. Okay, so, yeah.
Thank you guys. Oh, it's like it's much easier when people go along rather than like the math
Like I say who's and I'm gonna say you said it but someone said
They didn't like my show
I don't read the message if they didn't like my show
I'm just I'm just some joke some locale
And everyone everyone's fighting over me everyone's to ranch this little pal. You know what? I
Am
becoming vegetarian I
am
Going on strike from providing meat or milk for my body and
I am
Gonna move to Epstein Island and retire
Let's see
Yeah, well, I don't know what the last part, but I don't know. I'm the first two I have kind of felt through so no more fish tacos
Oh, why no, why I'm not I'm not going. I'm just kidding. But
What about a strike
Yeah, just in terror. Yeah, you're serving just in tears. Yeah, what's up girl? Yeah
Grass-fed lol, yeah, I want to be one of those they you know
I want to be one of those like why goo I want to be like the Japanese why goo lol
Okay, we're actually like you know, they'll come in the massage me
Periodically before they slaughter me better. Maybe I'll escape. Maybe I'll be maybe I'll have a via milk why you cow?
You know, I want to be the most expensive me. Yeah, but I
Don't want to be like McDonald's the
The cow world does that's like a hundred cows mixed into one patty. I want to be like a beautiful mixtape
The whole cow is used
Boo, okay
There's worse things to call you. What if they have like names like like an LOL
porcupine? I mean that'd be even worse. Okay cows are kind of like you know
they're kind of dumb but they're lovable. They're like you know they're kind of
pretty. What if they got skunk or you know those are like more offensive
animals. Well the first thing they got lazy was to sing an LOL cow. I mean yeah
Floor to diamond. Okay. God. I'm sorry. I can so does, you know, you know, I think birds give milk to you. Okay, so
Thank you, you know, it's a buyer. So you could
You should you stick to qualify for charity qualify them. Hi. I've heard you don't really I'm sorry. It was a joke. It was a joke
I love you for them
That's funny
Yes, I people are watching. Hey, I see what's up. How are you? I hope you laugh. We're done. I hope you go
I hope you I hope you left everyone left it was in a good way
Okay, hey my traveling gypsy. Hey, okay good. I think we're all having fun today
So let's do like a little collective for the chat little do villains
Just do like, you know, we'll do three and the advice card for the chat
So this is like three for the chat and advice card. So this might apply to you. It might not just there's a little special message in here
You just pass the five signs where you're at
Yeah, okay
Five signs watch for signs is two boxes, right?
Watch for sign. Okay, so let's make it these cars a little bit
Little shuffled a little bit a little bit skew. Okay. Oh
Thank you traveling just deep. Thank you so much. You're so sweet. I
Will get you a I'll get you a reading. Yeah, pull you please and pursue after
It's collective
Thank you, Teresa. That's awesome. Thank you so much very much. Appreciate you. Thank you. Okay
so guys
If we have if we have today
There we have
Okay
Okay, we have the seven of pentacles
Seven of pentacles. It's like wow. So you guys have been
Planting some seeds and things are growing and you have this he's gonna give this harvest to look for you, right?
You know you've been
Washing things carefully
You know you've guarded them. It's everything's going according to the time so far. So it looks like
Whatever plan you made I think it's uh, it's looking well boating. Well, and what we have the hermit, okay?
But maybe I don't know if this is something because let's take I don't know. There's there I
Think this might be actually on with the hunting dogs or something, but yeah, there's this hermit card
I'm not sure what we discussed from either, but you know we get to meeting this hermit. It's how it's really time to
You know, I think this this especially means they can be careful of outside influences on your mind
And it's like, you know and withdraw in a certain way from
the mundane world or just like like the
Some of the silliness though, and I know yeah, I know a lot of I know a lot of people have a have done that
Yeah, it could be true stuff. Let me know if the resonates with you. Yeah
But yeah, so we have the hermit. We okay, but we have another thing
So someone's gonna be bringing you something to like you when you're in this hermit state
So this is I think it's the one we bring something this is the night of night of pinnacles night of pinnacles is a guy that
He's uh, he's pretty successful and you know and some again some good taste and also, you know
He comes and he comes at all the nights. He comes to stay a little longer than the other nights, you know
tonight's always kind of
Spend the weekend, but you know the yeah night of pinnacles might might think next just three day
No, it's an extra holiday, right? Yeah
You got busy for a moment. Yeah
It's always good to pull back. Oh, and you're okay, and if you got another night
So yeah, so you think you got
So king of coin and now we have the or the night of coin now. We have the night of cups
Warning you about this guy because they know two nights and that's there's you know, you know
There could be like very but very well two different people that I'm interested in you, but it could be
It looks from this car like a song shows up and like the first of the chariot like not kind of running away
I don't know. It's like you kind of
It's I don't know if you know what I mean by that. It just seems like
That's the advice I give you the advice. Oh, yeah, the advice is the nine of wands advice is
Mm-hmm
Advices keep powering up to keep it power into this. It's that it's working. It's all paying off the nine
Also a hermit card, right? I'm not hermit. It's a major Akana
Yeah, it's just like you know, it's a lot. It is a lot. It can be a
Lot to carry but I think you know, you're at that nine
You're almost at the finish line your passion is being realized your passion is being realized
Sassy you don't go of slapping you at the wrench. Oh my gosh. Yeah, I still have a scar when Tiger Butterfly
threw her wrench at my head and
You know it almost knocked me out
I mean she was like take my wrench. I was like no no I like don't like to take wrenches like people tell me to
I'd only do when I I feel
Feel a need to and then it's like you know, she's she threw it at me virtually
I hurt look yeah, not me today. Yeah, so
I'm gonna be more my I'm gonna be more careful with the branches and stuff like I think I think everybody that I
Wretched I rent so far. I know like for like a long time. They're here all the time in the chat
It's just with the porters and the really great people. I think everyone
Like live my month. I don't think I have a
Bad mod in the bunch. I think everybody I've gone over I just prove themselves be great month
Have I been with a Vivian Von B. Good to see you. Hey, Nicole
I'm pretty good. It's just like you know people
People you know people are weird people always are
Able to sometimes they're able to get on our nerves, right? And it's like when they
It's just like
Yeah, we probably get on people's nerves and people get on our nerves and it's like he's got on my nerves
Um, you know, some of the people that are coming on my panel, you know, Alex
You know JT's who less who less they're kind of extend or in Zegan and lesser extent guys
I mean these there was kind of like monopolizing the panel last night
I'm slain and you're not gotting there, right? He's he's not he's fine. He's fine. He's a module, but
VG and DT or just they wind so much and it's like
It's just like really is the draining kind of it's like kind of whining it is like
Okay, get over it. You know, I don't know. It's like, you know, you know, I know how it is
It's like when someone just won't go over something that's not even serious. It's like
That's my in the end of the day how serious is my show my little YouTube tiny little YouTube show that you know how big
What does it matter if you're not in the chat? I mean, it's like you know, I like I
Bring people back in the chat
And you know, I hardly ever believe people that uses have said the n-word and porn about me
I mean, it's like I'm insane. Thank you for giving me everybody trying to be like
Jesus like I've done something for me Jesus, but she's in flight where he was able to forgive everybody
because then I think so I don't know so I'm able to
Try to forgive everybody, but it's not easy
Planning to save Thanksgiving dinner. Are ya?
Who page hunting turkey again, but everyone equally well like yeah, but it was like no it's like we really
Just say you just say everyone needs this day in their own life. What happened? I mean, it's like, oh
There's just been like these people coming they're from this
discord
if some people call it a cabal some people call it a
Brigade it's a brigade right and it's and then it's like people have said oh now
There's all these conspiracy theories about it like Alex has just like made it so rigid now Alex
First I mean first of the science. It's like the you know, it's like the
The Amish the Mormon Scientologists are involved the Satanists are involved
Sury diamond is actually this other person named
Pretty diamond who's that burdo? Yeah, this question. I said you were burdo last night and and then and then he's they
you know Vicky is
God and I mean, they're all I mean, it's just like it's so so ridiculous. I mean, he's making mockery out of conspiracy theories
but
Yeah, I mean, yeah, I don't know but
Then analysis screaming these theories and then that's like if I'm five and say, oh, well, what about no?
It's like, no, no, no you idiot. Oh, you fuck you. He calls me the
effing
Reach hot. I mean, he's like, you know, they're the worst names. I
Just sit there and like, you know
Let's don't take it
Doing guys, I don't know he just yells at me. He's so nice. He's so charming
Does that mean dinner now? He just sends me, you know, blue text
Didn't take that
I'll take that from Alex. Yeah. Oh, come on Alex. Alex is very into people's podcast panels
I don't know. He's on some other panel. He's hardly ever here anymore. He's
Gone he's gotten bored of me
What you're laughing flat you're laughing flat for but what Alex was like, you know, he's saying crazy things
I think he's calling on me mean names
He was more mean to me sometimes and sort of big pipes
The city first video when it kissed me I said I really didn't want to do but then he then he was like
Oh, but take a shower first. He's been like this
He pees and then jog in his room and he's
Talking about you know making a fish taco joke about me. How dare him
How dare him only you guys are allowed to make this fish taco? I know I'm just so I'm sure you know guys
Maybe this is for a place
Comedic comic read a little comic. I'm trying to be trying to be a little bit a little bit light-hearted, okay?
I'm not really that upset about it. Yeah, I know I'm a good actor and I do seem like
Wow, he's taken star. I really don't I really
Try to make you laugh. So mermaid
You'll go a little throw up if you are nobody, huh? Is that you know, I know a lot of people are a little shocked
I don't know. It's a try harder. You can't get his
Oh
You can't get heart. Oh can't get heart. Okay. Yeah. Well, I don't I don't know about that
Maybe you can you know, I mean if you can't just strap something on I mean do something
I don't just leave me alone. Just do it do something else. Alex and Gaudi and JT
You know go
No, I
Don't want to play with the sex toy with you
If something I don't know I just I'm just writing ideas up. Actually I did I did put like you know, I didn't put a
Yeah
A flashlight on my Amazon wishlist, but I did put some kind of weird
It's like it looks like a flashlight with like a mouth on it like a cartoon mouth. It looks really weird
I don't know. It's kind of expensive. I just want you to want to see it
Take my Amazon wishlist. It's an unusual
Thanks, so I don't I don't it might make me laugh if I use that. I don't know if that was how pleasurable it would be
Yeah, there's my Amazon. There we go. Thank you. Thank you sassy
Yeah, I mean I added a few things. I thought that's been too much sex. There's a lot of sex stuff on that. I'm surprised like there's
You know
Still a triple-headed dildo and fiber in a huge machine. I mean it's like so crazy. No one sell it
They won't sell a single bong. No pocket. Pussy's loud. Yeah
Well, so someone called who called it like someone said oh be to put something in her
See, oh, I don't know never mind there. I go get one. No, no, no, these hits already diamond-puzzling in her
Not my pizza pocket or it's some kind of secret pocket. I don't know
There's just a weird comment. I'm sorry
Hell is
Accurative hell is active. Yeah
Then is a place I know
How many pockets are there? Oh, there's hot Hawkeyes, which is technically not a pocket
That's a Hawkeyes, but you know and then there's like you know the few brands of hot pockets
You know
When a hungry bun shows up for lunch, what are you gonna pick?
And it's like you know, there's a pizza. There's a guy once I got the sausage one is pretty terrible
But there's like I like the cheese one and then uh, what else it's like some Italian seasoning one
When a hungry bunch shows up all night. Yeah, I got I know all the commercials and I know a lot of the
TV
Told I had no life and I watched a lot TV, but
Yes, did I
Where's that symbol? Did I
Got a fish
Yeah, can you tell me what that I can't really see that will on the streamer. Okay, have I
It looks like a
Is that a just
Nobody I'm flaky you're here. How how sweet you are speaking to say. Yeah, okay
Thank you that did I make it they smoke. Oh, it's more green. Yeah, I'm a little oh
You're being oh come on
I know I've been smoking these vapes are great. They're fabulous vapes
I'm funny today. Well, thank you. I try to be funny every day. I just know I woke up on the right side of the bed
Oh pin the link, okay?
Pin the link under
You have been peeking on you I'm sweetie who me I have not
In good guys, there's a really pretty like you know, I'm not like she was pulling up
But look at this lady. This lady is really cute to see her. She's her name is wicked wands
And she has a tarot channel so you can look at wicked one. She's very sweet
But she's like a nice version of that other Emily. Okay, so
Can you please get a car oh absolutely. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Yeah, I thought you
We're reasoning with that with that last reading, but I think that yes, we should be getting some fresh cards. Okay. I'm sorry
I'll leave the cards home. Let's see
She'll see what we got. Okay. We got this view of points. Okay, so but this was in reverse case
So maybe some kind of collaboration did not work as expected, right?
A lot of times it's like this third-party situation anyway
Where somebody coming to complicate things that wouldn't have worked out, but it also could have been
Think I think you're more experienced in that alright. I think I don't know if these other two people
There's two people maybe there
That we're wanting to come in on you. We got the
Okay, not so that's a page of pinnacle. Okay page of pinnacle in reverse. And so he's telling us something didn't
Take off. There's all there's always a reason for that, right? So it's like and I think it was not the right
collaboration but
Don't see it as being that that's serious that it was the okay, you know, it's the end of the in the world card
And this is the world's okay, so so that is over looks like that looks like that cycle
Whatever whatever whatever it was. It's like, you know take the lessons and learn from those if it didn't you know
It's like as you can see
And then you can you can prevent
You get through the next cycle perfectly, okay, and
Finally we have the justice card
He is the advice is the advice is to be just but and be fair right be fair and just and
You will receive justice for yourself, right? I was I would really do believe that
No, we are just in our life and justice will happen for us
Justice in the upright. We all hope for justice in the upright and it can be a legal case. It can be
just things very in general, but
Operate from that fair balance fair and balance, you know
Not like boxing news, but no fair and balanced, you know, actually like, you know, like fair and balanced
Like just that kind of temperance card a little bit just a gust
Just a gust I guess, huh? Yes. Okay. Hope you like that
Thank you so much for the day if you want more cars like I got you of course I've run a different deck the best thing I learned about today is
Don't hold your pee and then sneeze. Mmm. Yeah, because now you can't you know
You can't even you can't open your eyes when you sneeze you close your eyes
And so if you're peeing then you can you take your eye off the stream
That's never a good idea on YouTube or in real life. Take care of the stream
All with no pee on the floor
So
Yeah, that's it. Yeah
We're always learning lessons guys always learning lessons
Have you had
Sweety a kid or cats, you know
They tend to sometimes pee outside the box. They think I was at the box with the you know
My cat's pee outside the box
Mid-flow if you sneeze or hurt. Yeah, yeah, I might seem to start like violent. I think they're just like
My dad used to have these things that he would like scream and I like literally I scream out
And it's like people like oh my god, everyone's like people look turn their head to like
From everywhere like who the hell seems like that. This is so loud. Have you guys heard it before I go?
That usually happens three times in a row
Say them allergic to cats too
I'm thinking that's better than a story.
I think my mom has a snore.
My dad's, my dad was a snorer.
My dad snored, my mom had the snore.
She had like a little snore that was left.
I mean, it was not, it was cute, it's not like,
instead of me, she has it anymore,
but she did, because it was kind of like,
I guess, you know, she probably laughed it that way.
My jokes are a little bit sarcastic with snore.
So, I don't know.
But I never hear do it much anymore
I haven't spunky you this heavy gas. Yeah, and I think I think I
Love to like, you know, and look this is like going on vacation. I'd like to like visit
The other people like they're you know, the real people and then you know, then it's over at that. I don't want to
It's like it'd be immersed in like in like
literally all these lives
Like you know full-time it's like I like I like vacation. I like so that's why you know, I like I like
little breaks from my piano like occasionally or
Then I come back with fresh and better ready to go. I do have like the are you do you want kids one day now?
because I have cats and
It would probably be very, very, very, very, very, very expensive because it would involve
being a vitro or adoption fees, and it would probably involve me having some of the partners
that really should fail and everything, I mean, there's just, I'm, like, happy with
my cat.
I'm kind of, I don't want to kind of be in that marriage either.
Ah, uh, sweepy, are you talking to me?
I don't know, you have to catch my sweet
screams from something and find out.
I'm talking, oh yeah.
Well, I don't know, I don't know,
hopefully the sound of this sneeze
would cover any other noise.
Apparently I do, you sleep, oh my gosh.
Well, someone else was saying that I mean some people do have that problem, you know, I think that
Page was saying that she wouldn't want to do sleep from she repeats your phrase
She'd be doing that on this on this is a dream
And they know and then she probably would and then it's like and then she be clipped and then people would say oh look
There's a page did on her sleep string and it would be
It's okay. I wouldn't judge her it's like, you know
We're human, we're all human beings.
Okay, so yeah, my dad was snore so loud
I could hear it from the upstairs.
I think my mom had either earplugged
or some kind of just able to zone that sound out, you know?
Pretty cool.
Just unless you make it back to you guys.
I don't know.
Just someone telling some disgusting story.
I mean, I mean, it's like, I think that.
Those would be the only stories that I've had a man that was hearing because he was like a Harvard Stern kind of, I don't know.
It probably has sleep apnea.
Or that's like the 3 a 3 you know, there's 3 a.m. Like demons will sometimes wake people up at like 3 a.m.
Wake up really what I'm like at 3 a.m. Hey, Nike, huh? Nike, huh?
Is there a Nike in the chat? Oh, Mikey. Oh my god guys my eyes
Seeing other words and stuff
So I was reading about Nike today. He is the name of the goddess of victory in Greece
So probably a clever branding name that seems to love these
It is the great gods
But they did pick, you know, like he's not a perfect perfect goddess. She's not even a
Quite quite. I don't think she's a little Olympic goddess. She's one of the
Tertiary goddess, you know, she's got us on one of the things, you know
She got the god and goddess frankly everything, but this reason for the good thing we got of them
It's like goddesses of the doubly, right?
So, what's so special about that, then hey James and Nicole, hello James and Nicole,
do you know these people, um Spunky, Nicole's relatively new, James, well James is using
that big, I think his name was something like, I thought it was Joker, are you Joker, James?
He's a Joker. Yeah, you look like him having the fake you look like you're crossing him and it's your big pipes in your picture right there
Then you glad I just kind of Lurie. It's because you see the light
slowing through right now
Yeah, I kind of do any classes. I need some reading classes
Look at some events. I had late six like 25 years ago. I was finally starting to wear off like the rest of my body
Or you don't know them
Okay, I'm sorry to me to put you on the spot. Hey, you know, yeah, yeah, I think uh
See
I don't know. I don't know what the name was. Okay, maybe I'm listening guys. I'm seeing people in the chat that aren't in here
So we pee person
a wizard turquoise. I like that. OG chatters, guys. Yeah, we have a great chat here. There's
people in the chat that were my first chat. How many people? Oh, 27 people in chat. Awesome.
There's people that were my first chat. And my chats have gone a little bigger, but like,
there's so many people that have stayed with me. A lot of people have left. So I really
appreciate people have stayed with me. So how many couples on here? I think awesome. How many
You know Michael and and Merneth
We have well, so we have guys we have a hot Hockets and Q right all right home and
We have I think beta and blogger or something I'm not sure the one that left it ain't meant to be right
Yeah
Guys anybody knows know some happy couples. I know you know we have made some married people here. I don't know
Summer has like 10 kids and married for like a hundred years, not a hundred, maybe thirty before, she's I mean she's very impressed with me.
It's blogger and page now. Oh.
Page, is that true?
Blogger, really blogger.
Well, go over to bloggerawakenstero and see how he treats you, okay? He's not very nice.
Blogger I'm paid. Yeah. Oh my gosh. It's a perfect couple of power couple
It's called it's gonna be called pager or
Bage like what blade what blogger page or
blogger
page blogger
Me and Joker. I don't know me and Joker me and
Yeah, I want to I want those guys to fight for me. I want them to like, you know, kind of like
Pick up the super villain persona and actually like, you know go crazy and you know do some cool shit
Oh, we'll do that. Okay
Some of my tail. Yeah guys page. Hold on. Where's siren? Oh, I need a siren sound you see
No, I don't I just have this
What's that's a warning to pay does it's a warning from the universe?
Dig it. Hold on. Hold on. It's your big pipes and
Another guy trying to hit on you and on the page. Okay for yep. No, oh nobody good question. He likes him. It's not
It's funky. Okay, it's funky
He was cool he man, yeah
Well
Sometimes you got to stay goodbye
Sometimes you got to stay so long. I don't know that's how the words go, but if everybody had a new
Anybody had shoes now. I've got the golden girls in my head
Okay
Never miss him
My god, my eyes look like it's so be I look like I look like I'm Estelle Getty
Like like Sophia from the Golden Girls without the glasses. I'm like, hey, I'm you know, hey
Consistently I have no eyes
Open them a little bit
So I
Guess we'll go for a walk outside. Yeah, some of the nose be my name
I hear you now. I just can't stay inside all day. I gotta get out. Give me some of those
That's one a pretty bunch. I'm planning on going out though. I need to get a cigar so I thought it would be fitting
Yeah, I was I was so yeah, I was I was I was the granny. I wasn't I wasn't even
Be Arthur. I was I was already the grandmother
you know or
No doors his mom, but
Hi, who's in here? Who's your GMO's here? Mikey? Nobody?
Funky, Sweet Pea, He-Man?
Yeah, it's going wild.
Lowkey a member
Funky's a member. Thank you guys for being members. Awesome. I think I might have about 80 memberships
No, some people are renewed and a lot of a lot of gifted memberships from very blessed. Thank you so much guys
Yeah, I'm happy
No, this time I just have like kind of like
Decided not to worry too much about
Things are dull. I think that what things have even control over things that
You know the serenity prayer. I'm just saying the serenity prayer kind of works
Give me the wisdom to tell the difference. You know what I
Like what I can't change or what I can
Nobody Emma banned me so hell with her. She bans you. Why was she?
Recently or just on that first night because she might not have banned you if it was that night because
It was just like people were not able to type my name in that her chat. She banned my name in her chat
Oh, that's like it 2025. You know, I start you know, I started that Emma
2025 stuff that was like the first time on our show
I was I was typing these banners of the hashtag Emma for Queen of Hell and all this kind of stuff
I never get credit for anything. It's just fine though. Hi. I know I know how we you know
The guy who admitted to do the violent deals one day. No time
Eyes and they'll be
And it was wild. I think psyche to and page has
Three yeah, you know for the over but the the mod family is growing
But it's just for that. I'm people I can trust
Don't fucking do it. Okay. Now you have it
Is any of us, you know what?
The I have people I don't really hear people really bragging about mods, but this your big pipes dip it in his on his banner
he said he was
Vegan Patriots managing mods, I mean
That's a guy's it's pretty it's pretty big deal guys. It's a pretty big deal
And then yeah
He's trying to ban on the show and it's I told Saints you black. Oh, I'm gonna do Doug. I can't say that
I can't do this. Don't don't make them don't say that comment is that I'm at read the comment or bring it up
I don't want to say that
I hope everyone gets along in this chat.
You guys are like, oh, a bell.
So when it gets too loud, I'll ring the bell for no one.
And it's kind of like a cowbell
because it has the moon horns, it has the snake, you know?
So.
And guys because I ring a cowbell don't start to say. Oh, he's a little cow. Okay. Now. This is unreliate. It's not a
weekend thing they kind of kind of like some of the ranching stuff, too
Have you open mind?
Okay, I
Definitely I'm not gonna go I'm not gonna give milk. It's not not willingly
My key you don't have it anymore
Kickoff booted you oh my gosh, well they booted Emma to they kicked her off because she did a few things like she
Smoked me on the camera. She said fuck buddy, and she danced to sexy once
And she didn't win as though the tiktok store was it's the final straw thing
Tick tock gave her four chances. He only gave me one chance
One chance. It's true. But maybe she gave me a couple chances, but
All right, she's let's forget me the tick tock. So, you know, she won't see why she has kicked off a tick off
Not for forgiving karma
Hi
Hey, little I be you can't join in your quadra. Polizik you had hope you're using in narrow link
You can't join your own who was wearing your who's wearing it. Don't worry a narrow link in chat. Not me
Who is?
My god guys, what if you can see my what my eyes see that'd be horrifying
Okay, Mickey
Hey, Mickey you're so fine as Mickey. Sorry. What's the best?
Mickey don't believe on the paint here. You could ever make an account. Okay. Is that me? Is that Mickey get around?
Doug is cybernetic is a Dougie Doug or is that that other Doug?
What do you think
Wow, so I got these tools from Timo I should do I should everyone's I got this like you know
It's like six bucks. It's a huge tool case. I'm beautiful red and black. It was like, you know
Count Dracula's, you know manicure set, but you know, it's Timo and so it comes in little things little things
Oh, I mean it's like it's okay. It's metal. It's like but it's like
Bend it bend it too hard. They'll even will break. It should be like a
Bendule metal not something will
Break under my skin. Okay, but did it there's some cool stuff though. Let me see was there's a little nail flippers
What I mean being two pairs of the same pink nail clip, but I've seen one
What's what you do? They gave me like 30 of these little things and then shoot like two pairs of scissors like that
I will see yeah, let me maybe any two scissors at the same time and then then a big
Super there's only six bucks
So my in a carrying case
Mikey I
Know you but you're forcing me to see my when she puts the PM hub
Over my head over my head over my head over my head I do not know what's going on, but
Carry on guys carry on carry on
How's the song go?
carry on
My soldier
Sorry
Here we go guys
You probably more retarded than
being quadriplegic is my super, you know, I don't think, I think it would be a third of a difficult life, you know, I feel, and I know people that remember Christopher Reeve how it has a difficult little life.
Disaster when the human body stops working in certain ways. This is a disaster because it's like what did they actually have to like
Go in and they pull that stuff out of your intestine or but your organs aren't processing right? I mean, it's just really a
lot of uh
There was here. I think that's the bull was in the
Heriocardial caretaker drive. Did you get your eye to park closer to stone life is hard enough, right?
Yeah, but yeah, we take for granted how like, you know, how good we have it when we think about I think there's
people with like, you know, you're basically just right there ahead on it on a
horse though, they basically there's people like that. I mean there's people that
every variety of
people in a sense that's everybody every kind of person every every everything is like, you know, and
It's amazing, right?
There's no offense anybody. It's not offense anybody. But yeah, I guess I'm really I think though
It just comes down to the good people that evil people, right? Did I ever pin the link? I don't think
Yeah, but that's sort of saying like it's like a little like meme and wicca. It's like, do you know harm but take no
I really do like that one. Let me see if I
Yep, oh, okay
Now watch later
Watch later. Okay. There you go.
Uh, look at the precious fur back there. Yes. Isn't this your fur baby?
Thanks for your little fur baby. There he is right there.
Okay, I got my back into my leg. Up, up. I don't have this.
Kind of like, you know
You know, just get one more beer I'll get like a few cigars
Can you guys like this is ringing we have 40 people in chat we have nine likes tough. That's pretty good nine likes
Okay
Now put the link up finally. Sorry for the delay
There we go
You know I come and join I might be kicking a walk to the liquor store
Or I don't know maybe I'll try to take the bike again, but I just don't want to get the bike rims out of
Electricity like it's something like a little less late. I'm afraid it'll like stop
I don't know if I'll go just right at home like a bike or I feel like to walk at home or something
But here's the link why I couldn't hold
How's our day guys, let's be a comment
Don't tell Lenore all Lenore Lenore here. Oh
Hey, me Allen
He's me Allen. I think Rudy's running around here, too
Hi everybody. Hi everyone
Yeah, so these babes are you this one is already almost done. I think it's like
Probably getting it. I'm trying to get you a hit out of it
There's a little bit with this one is full and the other one's pretty much full
So those have been a good investment
Already had him play five days
What happens to the bike? Oh the bike is just you know the bike is fine. So I mean, it's like so so working. It's uh,
It's just not not charging. I need to take it to be service. They could probably just
Replace a fuse or something like that. I guess and
Here's not a difficult fix might be a little pricey
so I need to
Look into it, but I'm kind of unfortunate, but hopefully it's not a not too expensive of a mistake
Shrimp tacos with fresh salsa
Ooh and cool, so that sounds delicious
You're trying to make tacos tonight, too. Well, maybe I should get taco bellies
Yeah
Okay, yeah because I was smoking cigarettes this week
I was buying packs of cigarettes and the soil is they got
They're very expensive and it's like it just made me realize that they're going to smoke very I don't want to add
You know all ten dollars to my budget a day, right?
ridiculous
Just to smoke cigarettes as opposed to swishers. I'd rather just quit
how many weeks of mouth so you
Okay, okay, so you thought you okay taco. I'm trying to quit
I mean I think I bought one cigar
I mean they don't sell the switchers here anymore, and I don't want to buy that the cigarette and so I'm just buying like one or two
Their back roads beck was which are really nasty cigars, but
You thought cotton candy melatonin vape. It's wonderful. You can't express
That you need to do everyone should have that helps you drop it helps y'all so things I sleep how do you sleep?
I'm sorry my vision is not very good
Yeah, melatonin here is very good the natural natural chemical is great for sleeping. It's you know
Great great natural remedy for insomnia as I've heard
Probably smoked the whole thing
Well, speaking of smoke the whole thing as we have some we have some sage today
You always do some sage, you know, we can like it in case there were like any like
Weird negative energies in the last time as well. Oh
We can send all the negative energy back the smoke will collect at all
The smoke will dissipate. It was just doesn't basically disappear. You know, so diluted
The negative energy that they sent will just dilute into like the you know, that limit this universe
But you can picture it. Oh, I'm sure other ways like no
It's burning away like smoke
Okay
All the native is just not going away
You'll have a good time. Yeah, but you do have fun. Yeah
kind of far
Nears I get one cigar after really six blocks
What kind of BS is that?
Yes, this stage is a little bit I would say I
Don't like it that much because it is burning me it burns me sometimes
It's kind of like they spark off of the stage and it's like they
One time it landed my fingernail and they burn
CP
Hey, Lenore you coming in. Hi babe. Hi Lenore
It's fun. I'm so fussy today.
Okay. Yeah. So, I did burn my palm.
Hey, Lenore. And, uh,
What are we doing? Chat.
Sweet pea. Are they? Oh, hey, Christie.
So, yeah. Well, sweet pea said, I think,
Egg in the orange Julius is you have I get I get a raw egg
I'm never even heard of that. Oh, you see Peter said that sounds interesting. Oh
That's I'm good egg and orange juice. I
Trying to figure out because they make an omelet out of that or they will just drink that raw
Yes, I like that was good. We have a good memory. I would have a good memory. We love sweet P and chat. Nobody. Hey guys
great
loyal
supporters
the show
Nobody I know from Elisa. Oh shit. One of the last of people from the least of the
Talk to me, you know, I think Doug went in there and no Doug D went in there and you know, ruined things. He said, oh
Yeah, he's huge. I think that I went I sent people in there to troll her so and you know, she knows I did that though
Yeah, I can't really trust Doug the chat that much
Dougie Diaz, but not not the Dougie with the situations photo
You're not surprised. Yeah
Yeah
Little too. It's like that and there's people that don't that don't ever talk in my chat
There is is lurk in my chat and wait for me to say something like hey go to my friend's chat and subscribe
And they'll go and go say whole things
so
So is she mad at me?
The woman whose name rhymes with the years. Yeah, um, I
Don't know. Okay, so we're fine again. You know things come down. We you know, we didn't really talk it out too much
But we were being we're being civil and we were you know, she's coming this show. I was going her show and then
Last night she was on it was fine. And then all of a sudden all of a sudden she was like
Hey, will you suck it terror? I mean
She's you know, sir. It's going after the Terry is the same thing from a few weeks ago
And I don't know I was like please and I just and then she wants to do a fortune for me
I just was gonna be insulting and he's like telling everyone. Oh, yeah, I'll tell me true colors. I'll see the real psyche
I mean, it's like
Guys, I can't do more real than I am. I'm like basically I'm my most embarrassing in front of a
Hell of his audience. I mean, it's like what more can I do? I mean, it's like
jeez. So
anyway, I
Doesn't talk about the Truman show, right?
Hello. Hello. I
Wish I wish I said I'm really some carry, but you go how loud
Yeah
Feels like I'm I feels like I'm in a cross between the Truman show and
Peewee's big adventure
Except if I'm bite to get stolen the battery just
as it's glitching at the moment and
You know, I don't wear a suit and a red bow tie and he's the other character. Oh, yeah, I'm not
Keep carry
Basically the story is the same
Just put the two movies together. I'm sure you'll find me there somewhere except the day
I didn't know you were happening in and then you put yourself up there on purpose
You know, he didn't even heat that he didn't you know is happening to see
You put yourself up there on purpose. Yeah
Yeah
And so yeah, I really
I gave like a little bit information about myself like I gave my first and my last name all different times on my during my show
And I really didn't care at the time and then people when they people say oh, I know their real name
They'll just go crazy like those like oh, they don't think they
Yeah, you know just trapper opal silt skin or something like that. Oh my god. I know you know, it's like no
Somebody's more mortals don't you know our true names, right?
Those trauma too many didn't even know didn't know I meant I thought you would understand
Never mind. Yeah
It's really no that was being yourself. Yeah, I think I don't even think I've watched the whole movie all the way through
I think I love a moment boring for me the Truman show, but I like the
Premise in the beginning. I just kind of kind of figure out what's in that
Kind of know the ending already and so it's like uh, but
Good good try good try guys
Human show, you know Harry Truman was the 33rd president of the United States
It's true. Have I hooked on phonics. It's on fun. It's worked for me ABCD FC. Oh
Okay
You know there's actually a program called hooked on fun. It's not just a myth it was actually ever it would sell it
it's called hooked on phonics and
No, it's he's vocabulary and it's a it's not fun. It's work for me ABCD
It's mostly made like, you know, it's posed you're supposed to give it to your like, you know
Here like ADHD tile and then become a brilliant brilliant author or something. I mean if they were the marking on for it was great
But I don't know how
Let me see follow that bird. Yeah, I love all of them for let me see
So she made it
No, I mean I thought you wouldn't understand never mind. Yeah
I don't I don't we don't know what you don't know what you know, you know
And what you don't know you mean we we know we don't know something. We don't know what it is. That's the problem, right?
But so the arrows we would know it that's the whole conundrum of fucking language, right?
so
Yeah, how's chat doing?
and I went to my number wish list with my Amazon wish list at a
Let's see, tweet p says, I'm fine.
I'm not adding hooks on phonics to my wish.
I don't, I really did, I don't need hooks on phonics.
I liked words enough to, yeah, I learned how to pronounce.
I mean, I think hooks on phonics is like,
I guess some people like, you know,
their pronunciation was way, way off, you know?
Okay, maybe some some of these to some of them if they're from, you know, New Jersey or you know Boston or
Smothers some other places. I think they can have a different difference. I get the California is the worst
I mean, yeah, it's something that's just back pot. I'm just a big pot in California now
No, it's the California is the worst. I make families up to work, but
You know, it's one of those that people like are pronouncing the like cow or something co or something like that
It's like, oh, no, no, no, you have to say cow and it was easy to say. Ah, the out sound
Emphasize the oh, I don't know how it works. It totally taught people English. So
Yeah, did you see yeah, it's everybody. Hey, sleepy. Nobody
Yeah, I'm being a little silly today
It's time to like, you know, I like get under a lot of stress sometimes it's nice to like not be under stress
It's like laugh and have fun
kind of like
Doesn't happen at all, but I
Like I love having to show I'm being able to chat. I feel like you guys
So anyway
So what was I talking about?
Yeah, what should I eat today?
It's Wednesday, so let's see.
We need a Christine and DJ Electra
to perform other people that know all the show to be here.
I know, I know, but let's take it.
There should be a disk, a message that goes to Discord.
You get it.
Here's some Roseanne Triva, should be it.
Okay, I just I mean it's like
Really getting very specialized. I know I mean I could play Roseanne trivia maybe and I don't they do great at it
I don't move their names that well. I know some of the
show
But I could also do a
Golden girls trivia, and I've watched it enough. I did watch a lot of TV guys a lot of TV
It was my third, it was my babysitter actually. I was too old for babysitter, so it was just always a TV.
Elektra and Christina are cool.
Uh, did you look at the stream later? Yeah, everyone check out did you get Elektra's stream later?
If a mod can post Elektra's channel, people can make sure to go support her streams.
I don't know if it's her, um, she's, you know, she's just the, uh, uncovering Eric.
We talked about Eric's image and Howard's, and she has another show.
She does too
It's very specific questions you would have to know that show what doesn't she like you that's crazy. I
Think I'll like him does like you. She likes you. Oh
Christina, I think she likes you
Don't know what happens. Maybe you got me down or even one night. I know yeah
I didn't think you know, I just I don't I shouldn't I don't want to bring up
You know what she said it's like, you know sometimes
Sometimes there's misunderstandings with women, you know, or in men too, you know,
but sometimes there's a bad first impression, and it's just like, you know,
and then they never get to know the real person. I think if you have to know
you, if you have to know each other, you know, they'll love each other, say no, she
doesn't trust you. Well, I don't know how much she trusts me either, you know, she,
She's uh, she's you know, she's helps you know, it's unlocked. She's unlocked for me
Women exactly. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah women and men
Humans, you know women and men
Who has the panel gets last night, okay, so guys how remind me it was
Guys who is the guest list even remember the show
Drink too much. I forgot who's on the show
Guys, well, who's who did I live on the panel? I don't I can't go back and shit. I was just on one time, Mr.
I think
Sam and was on I think salmon came on I
Didn't be they came on me. I mean beautiful spy beat us coming on last night. He was five dollars seven and she shows
Yelling at me. I don't get it. Okay
Everyone's on I don't have them be it beat is that me guys every other day
Yeah
No, I think it's like I say a private I made it in the last stream
They can go and just see what she calls it what she calls it and see I was like I was trying to be nice
And I say hi. Hi. How are you?
I mean you oh
It's a little better home
If you go to bed early home
Testing oh, okay
Guys you hear me. I switched up my my head bones
What's that say Christine says hydroxene again, oh
That is that like oxy oxycodone or is that like they bike it sounds good. Hold on
Okay, yeah, we're all friends here. Got it. We're all friends
So...
I do enjoy having a house. I think they hurt Alex accused me of being blade. Oh my god
It gets and it gets like, you know, it gets so oh, yeah, oh the burdo. Yeah, burdo flirty. Yeah
Yeah, he was like birdies flurto and it's like keep birdie and then he's like
The flirty sounds like the name burdo. He's like flirty burdo. It's like the same thing. Oh, yeah, okay
I was flirty burdo. Yeah, there is like the I R D or I
I yeah, I R T and yeah
Right
I don't know it was yeah, it was bad. I mean Alice. I hope Alice is joking. I don't think anybody could be that like
Insane, I mean, it's like you bring he really believes he's
He'll fight about it too for later for hours if I love it's like, you know, it's I don't really care who's who but it's like
You know, he just thinks everyone's a everywhere
Alice's final conspiracy theory will be that that I'm all the voices on the show including him
I've just been like, you know, just talking to, like, locked in an attic talking to myself
and that's, that's, I've been dreaming that I had a show, that's, that's logical explanation
after Alex's.
Did you hear how the space made floor, uh, floor, it actually made a glass, I just watched
the destination and Google it, fuck that.
That Space Needle floor is made of glass. Yeah, the floor of the Space Needle out there is blocked from almost everyone
Yeah, that's all I feel bad. So I don't I want to be at the last place
They even like the devil can like, you know kind of have a drink here or something
But I want everyone to
Where everybody knows your name and they always dox your fame
You want to be where you should be and troubles are all the same
You don't want to be where everybody knows your name. It's like the it's like the anti-cheers. I think the psyche cheers
It's not about alcohol. It's cake. It's coke. Oh, yeah, sorry coke
Yeah
well, you know and
You know Alex I
Mean well
What's worse, I mean, I don't know it maybe think it coax better me alcohol is better
I can't decide just don't do both at the same time. I guess but
Alex openly admitted he's on coat. Yeah, you know, he said he was buying key. Those of me as leader or stuff
But I don't know what it's true. Nobody, you know that the path. Oh my gosh. Speak of the devil the devil peers
And the are blue is here
If there's a god, there's a devil, right?
Ying and yang son and mom
They can be like it can be like God's reflection is kind of like
Yeah, the mirror is not ours. It's not us, but it I mean if it is
It's gonna be light without darkness, right?
We'll be no darkness you need darkness for light to exist or else it would just be light like it would do you got it
It's you need it. It's a duality
That's the best the balance is the balance we're talking about like the
Can have one without the other right if we go out back something to play because he can
that's right
It's not physical body, go into spiritual energies to all of us.
I'm saying, I'm saying, I'm saying where we are like we're manifested in the meat suits or in some kind of physical thing, but we're like, you know, but God is, you know, I think God is spiritual.
He's like, you know, whatever physical being you have, you have faith that there is something else.
Like right. Do you know you die happy like I'm coming home Papa, or are you gonna be like?
I don't know or I'm better like that's what faith comes in. Well, yeah
Well, a lot of people even if they do do do very strongly believe in stuff
Religion says believe in me and you will come home
Yeah in the Bible says just believe it believe in like faith as big as a mustard seed, which is like a little
Mountains
Just so you can have a
That's how small it is
But it knows it's a mustard seed and it has the faith of God in it so it can move mountains
A human doesn't have no faith so he can't even move a fucking piece of dirt
Yeah, well, it's a good, you know, I think
We need to have more faith there. We're naturally, I think as human beings, we're naturally like
kind of doubters, but we're also, you know, we're a lot of things that's hardly, hardly like
dumb, but it's like we're skeptics at the same time. We're a believer. I mean, it's like, and so
right. So the government's focused, even the Romans, whoever wrote the Bible, right? Because they
they were humans that wrote that it wasn't like aliens. And the winners, right?
the Bible, right? The losers don't like to win those awards, right? All these rules.
So they figure out, yo, we need to control the masses. We have to feed them some story
about believing this or you're going to hell. So they're obedient as much as we need them to,
or is it real? Because it's either one or the other.
Yeah, I mean, no, it's like, of course, like, you know, the Bible is like the most published book in, like, the history of the world.
Yeah, who wrote that shit?
Like, who wrote it? You know, who wrote it? Well, you know, the heat, like, some Hebrew...
Hebrew rabbis wrote the old guy that had to go to the bathroom and shit and had hemorrhoids men right regular men wrote
Maybe women there's some there's some there's some scriptures by females too, you know
Both females whatever all I'm saying is humans humans roti and half of it is on the
What they saw from Jesus like it was a testimony like we saw this guy do this do this do this
Yeah
They're like magic tricks. They're like magic tricks today
Is it a book to control the masses or is it really that shunned for it?
It's a bunch of laws. It's actually like, you know, if you go to the Dematria stuff
You can get like, you know, you rabbit holes in the Bible
But the Bible is a lot of old stories that were like, you know
collected around and like a lot of and then they kind of like were adapted into the
Old right
Yeah
Came with a piece of wood and started to see and like people walked through it
You believe that you know what they do every time they have a new invention that this is great for media like a book or
You know a TV TV channel is that they you know they will start
Put out something like the Bible or you know some kind of huge mind control project like music like the Beatles
The biggest my control project
So, you're saying God doesn't exist and Jesus and all that bullshit?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
Government government means my control the work the word government my control book and then say no, I didn't say that
In Buddhism there's like a I have one of these these are the important Tibetan Buddhism the novels that support the school and it's called
mind
Mine training and it's the my you know, and it's it's all about it's basically my kids
The whole thing is that learning to control your mind not letting your mind be control. That's the whole point
It's like, you know, you my control is like
The ancient Egyptians and all these people 10,000 years ago figured this out, right?
Well, yeah, there's my theory as civilization progressed and kept growing and growing and growing the masses that the powers
That be we're like we have to control these masses
this is crazy what are we gonna do we can't control these people
we have to build like we gotta write some shit like if you don't believe in god
you're going to fucking the lake of fire and people will leave that shit
it's either that or it's true so it's crazy to me psych this is such a
i wish more people up here throwing their fucking you know two cents in
right
You believe it to my control book. I believe it's either
That's why I don't care I know there is like a
like, that's not even worthy who's saying there is some there's some there's some kind of force or some kind of indescribable
Unimable power
The system within you the heart the veins the bones the joints the every it's a system
It's like a what they used to say that in on those books those physics books a watchmaker
Like when a watchmaker makes a watch every piece is intricate and it coincides with every other little ticking thing
How can you look at yourself and just say I just came out of nothing?
Yeah
Energy or spirit or call it whatever you want, man. Yeah, well, you know
The mystery of the sperm egg. Well, you're on the right track. So this is the sperm in the egg. You're on the right track. Okay
That's that's where the
Mystery it's too much and then you look at nature
All the birds all the animals. They're just coincidence to because the gas is in
Like coincidences that would be just like, you know, like a bunch of random particles would come together
They want to come into this
No, there's something there's an intelligent intelligence, whatever you call it.
And that's what hurts me
Like your god my friend
You know, I told people and like I can see like they don't even realize like
This and that's the problem with the world that half of the planet doesn't even realize they are God and connected to him
They think like they're separate entity and like I like evil and all that bullshit
And you know, some people see it but not everybody and that's the one we live in is this permanent egg like a chicken and eggs
this permanent egg is like the
chicken semen and the
all right, so let me ask you
if I eat chicken and the egg
what came first
You can't ever
The rooster came first and then he got the chicken pregnant. No
Exactly. There is a God, bro. You could never answer that but science will tell us
Micro-microbiology like there was
You're saying God is a giant chicken. Oh the big bang theory
Yeah, it's chicken, exactly. A black chicken named Alexander.
Bro, the big bank theory says that two gases in space collided, and here we are.
That!
But a big bank...
An evolution says that a monkey, and here we are.
But the big bank theory, that's a sexual innuendo.
It's just in the milky way, the sexual innuendo.
It also has a window.
They're like
Right the Hindus believe in some lady with ten arms and an elephant
Buddhism Jewish people believe the Christians believe in the cross and it's but at the end of the day all the religions lead back to the same fucking thing
The source one thing whether it's Mohammed peace and Buddha whoever it's the same shit
So that's what's inviting the whole planet. Everyone's stuck in this stupid religious circle. They can't figure out. It's all the same
And they're fighting each other over the same shit like I believe in the same God you do like let's kill each other
That's what I'm crazy, and I'll tell you nothing's like
Why humanity can't figure it out because it's not just in religion the secret to life
It's in religion
science
physics metaphysics spiritual like right
The meaning the meaning to life is actually it's actually
It's us it's us and we're the sea we're the meaning of life because we're the one with they even cared enough to measure
Yeah
and this goes to everybody listening.
And I know everybody knows what I'm talking about.
Go to water at a period night
and you'll see the moon reflection
comes straight to you on the water.
All right?
All right, and you can move, you can go a mile down
and that's it, and there's still
the moon reflection off the water.
There's a white line just
you. So now that's
to you and the person next
to it sees the same thing to them.
and the and the hundred people down, see the same thing
you understand what perception comes in
yeah and you know Alex
but people they can't understand this like this
Alex
Alex and when the moon hits your eye like a big pizza pie that's a moray
that's a when your eye hits the sky like a big pizza pie that's a moray
Yeah, we're having an Italian Italian. Yeah, I see. Yeah. Yeah, it's it is deep. Yeah. Yeah, but the yeah, Mori means love
And it's like, yeah, so what you see?
Were you if we're on a date?
You're on a date or hanging out with friends and you go to appear
That's five of you. Yeah. Yeah, and you look at the moon
You're so no clouds in the sky is a full moon the reflection of the moon
Will go straight to you. You won't see it aligned to your friends or anybody. Yeah, you go straight to you
So who's right why does that happen ask yourself that?
To life my friend, okay
Yeah, it gets deep bro. You want to go with Alice in Wonderland on the rabbit hole?
Well
He's accused of treason his bull fella. That's the funniest thing on earth. That's a skit right there
That's a skit. You can make a skit of a comedy skit and make millions. That's the type of shit Nick Johnson's on
Well, I don't know it sounds like a Saturday at lab skit. Sometimes I'm not too funny
Yeah, exactly a mad TV skit. I think my TV everything to me is a Saturday night skit. I've been saying this forever
everyone takes it personal like serious. It's just a skit
The van down by the river
Got my white tight pants look at Christine
They all told Amanda isn't that funny? It's like they all suck my dick and then when I like bug out like this
They'll say Alex ruins everything. Oh
and they call me Bobola. You just suck my dick, or you know.
There's a nice there's a nice ladies walking their dogs walking by and you're in here instead of the you know act like you
Delays initially you do that ladies in your town. You say hi. Hello, ma'am. Hi
Good morning. You know you hear you're here. You're calling everyone bitch and
It's not ladies. It's my family for two years
It's I'm dead summer. You know my like sisters
Depends on your movie usually everyone the first night I'll start treating them like that
You've known her for 30 years, but they don't know that they think that you're
It's like me
Remember you're supposed to like you to make a good first impression not they see you getting arrested outside
The studio when the show's starting. I wouldn't know what happened
Yes, I'm ready. What do you think about that one?
No, I thought we didn't three guilty on to the judge denied bail is a good one
He's living on FC. I'm a two don't worry about it. Okay, so awesome. I'll bless him
God God bless America. Okay
God bless the Queen God everyone bro. What America like everyone says God's America. Yes, of course, but when I got blessy theopia
Well
is that he'd be
and I never hear that
God, God, you got to hunt
you got to hunt
God bless the most richest country on the planet
even more
God bless Ethiopia
The Ethiopia is fine. Ethiopia is very blessed. It does have a nice Jewish blessing on it because the Queen of Sheba lives there
So, you know, you know, it's fine. We have a little Bible
See how's the chat doing? I have psyche. Yeah, we're having a crazy run the whimsical Wednesday
I said whimsical what I said. Yeah, I said whimsical. I don't know why I said whimsical
You said that because of beta whimsical
She says whisper Wednesdays. It's with where is she by the way?
beta came here and then
yelled at me again and then
Started saying something bad. It's like
Yeah, and then she said you're banned because you docked summer you've been you've got summer
I mean, don't don't say her name. You said it earlier. Don't you not gonna say anything
I'm gonna say
Don't say it please not acting of it's been out there for years already, right?
Just I prefer not to have an actual names, but let's just use
Thank you, but it's just set you free. She feels bad. Okay. It's okay. It's okay. I know my guy guys
I think summer summer was actually born. Her name was winter and she was born and
I call her dimples, bro. She has changed to it. She changed to a war. She changed to a warmer month and you know
Anyone can change their season. Um, there's no judgment. Sometimes leaves will fall. Oh, it's already diamond
All the leaves are blue brown. The sky will be gray. It's just california dreamers where you're right
I'm sorry, those are really cheap, okay?
Oh, let me see, yeah, so I'm just,
I have like thousands and thousands of these books
on Amazon, you know, in the Kindle store.
There are thousands of them.
Most of them are free, so I think they're kind of iffy
on the content, but I bought some of them on sale.
A little bit of sale.
How's everyone doing?
It's a doctor and a, okay, let's not call people names.
Okay.
So, I'm seeing if there's any interesting book that catches my eye that I could read a little bit to you.
Let me see.
It says, good luck, bad luck, who knows?
Okay, so is there good luck, bad luck?
I don't know, what's the premise of this book?
It's like being a casino, red or black, at the roulette table.
Who knows?
As is our lives are full of choices, focused intently on our experiences, we create a view
of the world, ourselves, our relationships, and determine future actions.
Each event analyzed, categorized, and conclusions formulated, attempting to comment fleeting
moments we struggle from one experience to another to provide meaning and purpose.
When all those fails, we abandon remnants of common sense, get it wrong most of the time,
our minds to the possibilities of understanding different perspectives and defend our position
to the bitter end. Near the end of our days, faced with terror of an uncertain future,
we discard long-held stubbornness, suddenly focus on the something else that has been
We thought there would be more time to figure out this mystery of life.
Believe these clues to why we are here and what we should accomplish would have been
easy to find and clearly labeled.
We may have relied on others to light our path or stumbled upon beliefs, which provide
a support, encouragement, and possible answers to difficult questions.
Whenever we discovered, we encountered a pivotal time when doubts creep in.
The questions we happily answered to our liking years before are no longer satisfied.
Subconsciously, we constantly measure our progress in life and apply a definition of success
tainted by a world which judges where we are and who we are against an unpublished checklist of
dubious origins, and sinister motives. It's no coincidence that right at this moment conflicts
rise to the surface, and all our previous certainties turn into only possibilities.
Though a known past and unknown future collide in the present moment, with so much force,
the glass ceiling of all the thoughts we would have created shatters. Shocking and comfortable,
Moment in our whole lives. Good luck. Bad luck. Who knows in it's about this that moment the invitation
It's proposes and how to move into that time
We have left remaining with renewed hope and certainty
Knowing how much we are loved to get to that moment or more usually moments
I invite you to join me in taking a fresh look at your journey.
We will revisit your past, reflecting rather than judging.
We will consider the questions we ask, the answers we get,
the different voices we have listened to, and the luck factor
we would like to believe that makes a difference.
We will look at the allure of the outward journey,
why we may struggle to find real meaning until later in our quest.
How distraction keeps us off the path of discovery and how love keeps us living in the moment
Ultimately discovering the wisdom we need to find the gateway to the most important journey we could ever take if we only
Realize the courage we need to choose. It was with us when we arrived. There's a wizard of us
Okay, we have a completed dreams and finished business
If you haven't closed this book yet start reading okay, so then you wait that it sounds like a good book, huh?
It's got us some really interesting introductions. So maybe I'll be through some of that later
Oh, oh, oh my gosh. Oh, it's only been you on the panel. Okay, that's one left
Someone leave Alex. Are you here? I
Think Alex left
I'm thinking hear me Alex Alex
you know I was in the bad time my man relax he's
We started cocaine in your bathroom
No, I was taking a leak, but I'm gonna smoke cocaine in my living room now
Okay
I
Want to hear the snort on here
Now here's a whoo
He named himself after a shoe designer or why did he do that? I
Think he's just he he he relates to the Queen. I think Alice is a closet drag queen actually
He's a transvestite if you date you woman with datum. She knows her clothes start to missing
And her like her favorite bag her her hat her pair of shoes
then she would like you know wait outside the building in the morning and
I also walk out wearing all those I'm back baby yeah I mean and then I mean then
usually the pattern after that is like she'll check into like some kind of
shelter while she well she waits for the restraining order I'm just kidding I'll
Am I keeping the guest away bro?
Guys, I'm gonna laugh right psyche he has only left the futon
For fish tacos the past three weeks. I what you don't know that
This is a full-size couch Le Roy Le Roy or whatever your name is this is a full-size couch
Sikey 2020 mentioned there were banned in chat. We checked well because 2020 as I remember
Was very rude to me. They're my mod and they're like, oh fuck you
Sikey, you're a bad person
To be smacked a little bit in the backside
I mean, I mean, I try to like give people other chances at 2020
Or you see it's Christine. Can you ask if they're gonna be nice to me or they just want to come like troll me?
I mean, I think because even as a mod he was a troll, but it's like
After I unmodded him. He got really bad and he's a terror reader too. I used to understand. It's like, you know
I'll check on my back
Oh, I'm so here. Hey, yeah, I think my thing is coming up
Okay, so I'll have to find it later. I I did
Ria
You know, I unbanned the blood blood bloods impulse
Zimples but simple. Yeah, I'll have to look into
Who you said Ziggy or something Ziggy. I'll look at that later
Too dizzy right now dizzy
This is a 719 the only as it's truth. We're spinning truth and a
total harsh, but
Still lies the GT discord
Okay, I'll be right guys. I'm getting a prep for message
Uno dos tres cuatro cinco seis
Saiki ya viene para atrás otras veces
si no sabes español no venga a hablar conmigo
especialmente si no lo consigo
Oh shit
Do we really get that can do the mod and mod is take it off take off that you're the dog
Yeah, I don't think there's a dog see my chat. Don't talk so much money. Yes, you did
So I know your name is is saying in my chat, you know summer's address and something so don't
Look at look at look up a little yes, yeah, I see a message from a
where so somebody in the chat
An anonymous tipster just to send me a screenshot
What it says it says
Alex Queen says summer's address is blank blank blank and he's like not an over after I don't know her address, bro
I just know her real name
I don't know what I'm talking about.
Don't share a real name.
That's what I know.
That's what I'm saying.
Her name is Winter Sanderson.
Yeah, Winter Sanderson.
There you go.
She's the fourth Sanderson sister.
You guys don't read too much into it.
And not say your address is this.
Uh, okay, Alex you better chill out. Yeah, look he's right and look he look he does have
Already the second look he is a long-time member
You know everything and approve it everything, huh? Yep. I have
To see I see everything I see every little everything that goes on my channel, but like the all-seeing eye of my channel
Hey black or G. Oh
No one blocked or G. Okay
Guys, no, I'm a man. I'm a man. Are you blocking your duty? I mean come on Amanda. Yeah, I told you
of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of
it's okay yeah everyone's wrenches and only have one I'm not gonna I don't know no no no
it hurts my show because then people are like oh my gosh oh it doesn't hurt your show
yeah it does it because then people think especially you think people only use to have a wrench
They're not
It's a bummer because you think oh I've modded her for some reason like some
I care because I care about my audience
They should not care about my nobody should honestly except you
JT and JT and the Ziggy are ready for a wrench. I'm like, no, no, no, no, no.
Well, just give a wrench to a legit little few that you trust, man, but you have over five years.
all of those of us see the scarlet,
james, was the key in the
Oh, I know I can't but I just need I just need some more
Channels um, yeah, so I don't build it. They are they'll know what to do. They're all good. They're all good
They don't want to get months, you know, pick up three and five is
I've already kicked off a bunch of months and so I don't people that have no feet like, um
Everyone's feeling everybody's
Even uh
Even that that last person I was much I don't know
And I see a stripping coming again, he's gonna wake up tomorrow with no renters or nobody
And then he started delivering it back here in the little by little and half of them do to serve it
Jamie's cowboys a hundred percent
Um, even he meant as much as I don't like uh, you know, like there's people that you know, nick johnson like hello
You know, of course like there's people so you feel bad not giving them the wrench. I see that too
I know
I'm pathetic in that way. I'm like yo, I hear that I want to take everyone's wrench and half of these people
I know deserve it, but there's so many assholes in there make stand
And and then you give it little by little by little by little and then everyone starts sneaking in like give me one
Where's mine? I can help you too. Like but next thing, you know, you're back to 30 ranches
Yeah
Once I gave out I really did no one asked for
I just, I was just, I was just giving them to people.
Like, you know, just because they were good mods
and so then I just wanted to let them know.
I appreciate that man.
It wasn't like, I wasn't trying to like,
oh, I can't, you know, I don't like having mods.
I like having mods, but as in,
I think I got the perfect blend now.
Just don't always do the alchemy.
So I got, everyone's off balance, let's see.
So it's a, now it's 725.
Sir, if he has fire, if Sir, if he has skill control
His business exactly. I was there business for diamond says David 25 Alice is trying to gas life. Oh
That was taking a little too. She's been here with the beginning
Flirty has been here with you from the beginning
Flirty help to the channel too. She brought a lot of attention to the shit, right? How many nights for diamond a lot of people attack are up here
You know, she's been loyal whatever. See, you know, there's some people like your family, bro
Gymnac of a beater like all the people, you know
But then when these like outsiders and then I think you know have 40 wrenches of half family have to do jacks
And then it turns into well, they're in their dog thing
Everyone's away, right? Yeah
You said is that fucking lurking a little bit a little bit little and if no one should care about that honestly if your name is
fucking white or blue
That's a stupid thing
No, we really care better
You can only give it to the people that are here to help your channel like grow and protect it
That have no feelings associated or with the child or whatever. They just hear like yo, you know, just to protect you like secret service
But I think from from this point on I think I've remodeled most people at this point on I would like really prefer my mods to actually
be members of the show at least or
Support the show
Your channel you give them a key basically like a spare key to your house and they're not even like a member
They don't even drop $5 a month, but yeah, they have a kid
You can have people like that bro, you have to have strict family vetted
Identified motherfuckers that got your back no matter what
And then maybe I'll do something like the first time like the first your first appearance maybe is on the show is you know I
Don't I will not you know ask it for anything
But it's like if you're on the show like you know on a basis, you know, I think you should be a member
I think you know that should be like because
Really, I think I put myself at risk having people on the panel that don't care about the show and I want to break the rules and stuff
So if I if I think of these people that were when it comes to righteous
You gotta forget about friends and think about your channel like a business like who's gonna protect my shit
Not like oh, this is my best friend Jamie Cowboys. He's a ranch even though God bless her and she doesn't you know
She should you know, I'm trying to say but you should in that sense of the right
Like not friends more like who's gonna protect my shit like
Everybody is they say that's why that's why you're not a mod because
You started hacking everybody including other mods and people this chat and people on the poor a good good
It's good. So exactly. So I can't show anything that approaches even if it's me, bro
So so so page
Paisen page to be the mod or my
Yeah, I'll see the mod and then you can be the bad cop. You can be the bad cop
You're like a scary cop. That's like wants to steal the drugs they have and then
No, anybody ever blocked when I had a wrench or time down was your enemy
So that's what I went crazy like bye bye bye bye bye and then once I had fun with hillbilly
Just because I was I was young and let me tell me I'll put 10 seconds
You've said a bit but time is fun is not hiding him from my chatter
you got to go to that list and forget about friends think I have I have I
I went through the whole list and I
I'm not everybody now. I'm slowly remodeling as people come that uh, you know prove themselves to me. I put them
I'm I'm I'm gonna probably give up
I'm trying to make uh, you know trying
He's lying straight. You can't have only women mods. So you got to throw one dick in there. That's like, uh,
you know
of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of
No, no
as Alice black cock and
Justine that was just a satire
No friends as better than fake as people nobody on your percent
And you want a mind nobody because you've been here too forever and he's a good dude never betrayed you
It's hard because you have to follow rule or not like no mods for nobody only for people
But I love all these people. I want all them to be mods
I get it
but when you have too many and then you know minds and alcohol comes in the picture you're gonna have nights like
People blocking and then you get the shit for it. Yeah, so you have to choose a heart
and go through that bullshit or foul shit rules like I only have four months and the story.
I mean, I do kick him out when he like, you know, and he yells at me and stuff, but
heals me so often. If I was to kick him out every time, it was just
there would never be a guest on the show. It just gets you quite.
So anyway, I'm just kidding. Alice, Alice is a, Alice is a good guy. Guys, this guy's not a bad guy.
You know what's funny? Time, that dog thing, time.
Blocked me on beaters the other night. I went up there and I said some dumb shit about her nose
Because they were beat it was like what's my know?
What do I look like or to can or a suit can and I was like yo to can Sam bitch
Father knows like and then time. Yeah the bird from the Froo loops. I was like your two can beta and then time
Time me out
And then last night time was up here in the child like hey Alex, how are you?
You called it you can't you called her to can't be there
That's cool can't be there that can't Sam is usually it's actually like a he's a bird with an enormous
What is it?
Norma's nose and it's a multi-colored
But who can be there?
Guys, these are two cans alone. Okay, don't call it don't call it to camp either
Okay, I don't know it's permanent and not since I can't after I'm not sure I think yeah
guys
Everyone well, I know your son said it with the nose because you also have a nose going you your toucan side
To can't say but see me. He has more of a hook
Who's your fake balls?
space was the most and they were gonna fucking give her back the fucking old nose
Unless they give up the cold for the air
Yeah, oh one
I really I really
Kind of coordinate he has on his luggage
guys guys
Guys, so so he man says psyche he talked shit
I want the coat of your back her old nose. That's beat him
They'll be she has a beak, bro
She can dive into water and pick up fucking bass no problem. Oh, she cannot she cannot
Okay, she can't she can't see the superpower, but you know what? It's a I uh, I
As you know, we all have our superpowers, especially people born in the 80s. We're like, you know, you know, you're
karate kung fu or
You know that weird
That's from the cocoon. Okay. I'm grounded how a grandma says like he was reading Bible verses pissed him off
Well, it's okay. I mean, it's like, you know what? My people will like the Bible and yeah, I can't
Reality Nancy has a trans child. Okay
People's kids
Like
My mind my nose is like it was a guy was a guy
It looks like mr. Potato it's nose
like I can just take it off my fingers over the fingers over
the stage you know I'd say that bro because I had a friend that is that a cancer of the nose
and then he literally had no nose it was the weirdest thing they literally
and then but he would take it off at night
the poor
And then I hit my toe on a fucking, you know going to pee in the bathroom
I hit my little toe and I'm like, ah, hey everybody died. No, bro. There's people out there with no nose
Okay, huh?
Gotta suck it in you gotta suck the tear back in not today tears get back in that eyeball
I'm gonna I'm gonna suck up your here Alex suck it up. No, I'm gonna live another hundred years probably
Because I'm wondering, you know, I mean, it's like I'm
going to need new window currents and open the purple.
You got to switch it up.
No, you're a different color because it's too much.
My mind's going crazy with the purple.
I'm telling you, it will help your channel or put a yellow, a
different color.
People need to see fresh shit.
I'm not.
You know, the purple sometimes I'll come up and I'm like, I
can't see the purple again.
The mind works weird.
Well
Think about I think about how
Delighted the the buzzer grapes from the fruit of the loom commercial made me until I like purple
But what's that? No, I know man, but you know what life is about evolving and changing
Constantly just changing and changing. That's why when you say I don't want to have kids. It hurt me
Because that's the point of life is to multiply
Every organism on earth just needs to multiply.
They will do anything on the planet to multiply.
Whether it's an earthworm, a monkey, a dog, a fucking shark, whale, or whatever you name it,
especially humans, is to multiply.
It even says it in the Bible if you read it, right?
Multiply, spread your seed, multiply, multiply, multiply.
So, when you say, I don't want kids, your soul's dead.
You're basically the devil, you're reverting back into the devilhood.
Like, don't multiply, just die now. End your bloodline.
You know, every family has a fucking bloodline.
You need to keep living.
And everybody here, go check your fucking family tree, and I guarantee it's dwindling.
Like three generations ago. There was 30 people on the tree now. That's like eight
Like me my mom made and there and every fucking decade by until you crammy tree gets erased
So everybody out there needs to fucking start fucking and multiplying
Mother fuckers, what do you think the fucking point of life is?
To just erase your family tree out of existence. It's to multiply
You could throw a fucking worm in a box and all it's gonna do is just try to fuck the box and multiply
Organisms, which is basically what we are living organisms
whether you believe in religion, that says multiply, or science, that says multiply,
the point of being alive is to fucking multiply.
And change the stupid current, psych, I'm sick of the purple.
Gotta keep that family bloodline going
Why do you think the Jewish people have fucking 30 kids?
Right? You see just walking around with fucking nine kids strapped to the rest because they believe in the multiplying theory
But I can't multiply you as a gay man because the assholes don't make kids
So I think him yeah, exactly you can't fuck a guy in coming his ass and a kid comes out
So I think you say I don't want kids. It's just the defense mechanism
Because you can't have them
But everybody deep down in size has to want an old spring whether gay or not, right? I believe that
Nobody's just like no, I don't want to move like a kid. No. No, even if you're gay
You will want a little gage done or whatever like you multiply like another one of you, right? I
Mean correct me from wrong here guys
I'm no one telling me otherwise. What the fuck I'm just saying what I think what the fuck
to multiply i gave bestest can multiply so now like i don't want kids shout out yeah you do
you just can't have them because you're whatever and actually you could have them but then you'll
break them you're gonna see a father walking around in a skirt what the hell's that i don't
so i have two moms one has a dick come on why is everyone crazy bro and if you believe in the
Hey, you have a family and you multiply I make that I multiply shit
Can multiply sucking dick and coming in assholes
That's why he did he's still in jail because I know God shout out to that judge
Ha ha ha you know what he did he turned around it was like I'm coming home. I'm coming home
The justice was like no you're not you ain't going nowhere, baby except back to that stupid cell
Pete did he thought he was going home
Because he got a quarter of three out of five. What a dick
You know what fucked them up, by the way, was his arrogance and his lawyers arrogance
The lawyers demanded bail. That's what they fucked up
You know, they got him a quarter three year. You're awesome top of the line lawyers sharks
Ten thousand thousand hour type lawyer, but you got to arrogant my friend
Demand he got slept released today on bail because of this and that the judge was like what you demand
You were kept his mouth shut
Maybe and then he did he started shouting out. I'm coming home. I'll see you know now. I'm out. Ha ha I
Think that arrogance fucked him up
The judge was like really but he's a straight shooter
He did he's gonna be in jail for at least two years. I mean, you know, he should be for the 20
They should throw the book at the motherfucker in my in my eyes
But you know if they gotta go the minimum
No bail for you
no sentencing happy 4th of July and
He's not getting Oscar free
Man act charges
That old ten years tops
If the judge wanted he could put him in jail for 20 fucking years. There is a guideline of sentencing
But it's still up to the judge I like my ass
So minimum he's doing two years minimum worst case scenario two years
He's not going home for bail and he'll be there for you know, 2027 whatever
worst case scenario
best case scenario the judge trips out and says yo ten years later
Don't play with the feds the judge can overcompensate that just does not like him and that's a fact
He denied the bail five times
That's the same judge that denied him five fucking times including today
Nope, I don't go fuck me through so hundred million ten airplane season are going nowhere back to your little cell
And MDC motherfucker Brooklyn federal detention Center
You're gonna keep eating shit
And guess what the next time you leave that cell is to get sentenced
And we'll see what my man judge does
He denied bail so obviously he's not gonna let him go at satisiting day I
Didn't wait to see this shit. He can say any number he wants three years four years five 20
maximum 10 10
19 815
His life is in that guy's hands
amazing
there are some people saying that the federal guidelines
that he can only do this amount
or some bullshade by the federal sentencing guidelines
at the end of the day the judge has discretion
he can do whatever he wants
he does have to fire
you know
go by the sentencing fucking guidelines
I thought Trump was gonna be in jail. So I dropped that after that one you can grab him by the pussy
Everyone forgot about that one really quick
Diddy walking no, he's not he would walk today Jacob Randon did he's not going nowhere. He's gonna suck dick
For at least best-case scenario two years
100%
He was denied bail imagine that
After beating three out of five the judge was like nope
I see you're sentencing asshole
What do you think that means?
Balloons and flowers like all right by sentencing. You're gonna be like yo, you're going to jail for 10 years later
You got convicted of the man act which carries
10 year sentence each
So what you're gonna shit on the law now and go back to free course
He can fucking throw him in jail for 20 years, and he's what 55?
He'll come out at 75
We saw three cops. I
Want to be surprised it doesn't happen
Was in a store today, and I found a phone wallet. I'm so what the fuck is this? It's just sitting there
And I opened it up, and it was a phone wallet. They had all these credit cards, and they had a PBA card in it
I was like at the fuck out here with a shield number
So I take the PBA card out and flip it over and it says I
Am officer
blank blank junior this is my whatever the guy's name and then he goes this is
my dad with a phone number and it said 67th precinct so I found a fellow
brother's cops cops dad's wallet today was great
So I called the number I pulled psyche. I found a wild play and it was my boys dad's while it
Yeah, I called them up. I was like you I find your dad's wallet. He's like, oh my god. He's going crazy
And then set a cop car over and retrieved it
Pretty ways
Got the gold treatment. So yeah, I did go like I think the bike
Wait didn't charge the new charger didn't work. It's not charging, but it did go the last
Way back to the to the liquor store and died. I think it died right away at home
I'll try to get it fixed
Put it tomorrow the next day. Hey, babe. Hey, what are you doing?
Yeah, I got I got and guys
Mike my keys are medium
Through my pocket once again. They also space they say yeah swishers and stock today
Yeah, I hope you got a couple boxes
No switches today
Yeah, I think he's better than the backwoods because there's like back was actually like case if they're like
Like a fucking good times rolling off himself in the backwoods. I mean, it's just like they're terrible
So I like these nice little a little bit
The neater
Um, yeah, we're married. Yeah, just you are you who you marry you and who? Oh
What's wrong?
18 years next month. Oh wow
Yes, Mary and chatting on her or tea on her husband's already
Legitimate court. Okay. Well
guys
It's all legit. It's all allegedly until you don't have a prison sentence. Even then there's appeals, you know
Who knows who knows what the truth is going?
always be skeptical
Yeah, I did ten years, bro. It's not fun. You tell me you did ten years. You did ten years. Alex and then you're gonna cop
You know, you know, I don't know big head. I didn't become a cop after that. I was a cop one
Oh, you're still but you're still coffee. You didn't get fired
Yeah, I was like you see a very long vacancy very long. I remember you talking about I know the night
I said that but that night I was trying to throw people off because I don't want them to like find out so I was like
Yeah, so I was trying to like you know makes the little story up, but
Right, you know
You can't become a cop after a shit like that, but the flesh can do anything. So they are the law
They probably make you like a
Undercover like you know probably like a seeker have a thing around your active work. You just be like a name
Don't leave you on industry investigating crimes
But they use you where you can
Okay. Hey everybody in the chat. Yeah. Well, you know Alex
You Alex did you want to come you know when cute when Chris K and I meet up do you want to be the number three?
I'm not gay dick. No, no, but you know, we have a number four
We are have a whole or it's an orgy. There's this it's probably means to be like mostly
I have one woman come just so that all the guys will do it until
I'll play along and then I'll break your dicks off
I'll put it along again, and then if you really take it there, I'll break that cock right off of it.
You're off the show.
No, Alex, no.
I don't want to hear it.
Alex, do you know that, you know, that can be, it's a traumatic thought for somebody, okay?
Imagine you have a prize, your prize black rooster.
From your you're perceived and you know you have you this you this the rooster's a piece
I guess he's a city rooster, but he's beautiful and his name is Alex, but she named it me out and then Alex
You know what happens to Alex?
She sells him he okay Alex lays the best eggs and in pregnancy that she but she's like a
you know, I'm gonna sell Alex for
Sometimes some cock me some cock me
And so then, you're gone, the cockmeat is gone within a day.
And then thinking of all the eggs you could have laid for her
But she just wanted that cock meat so bad guys. That's why you have to like we just wait for the eggs
And then make a deal with the chicken the guy. What you guys are so mean. Yeah, yeah, they're trying to you know
Pulse poultry fowl out of there out of their hooves because they're sick. They're sick
Yeah, I'm just gonna go out where's Alice why isn't he alone? Oh my god
Oh, I was gonna I need Alex here so I can blame him for putting those thoughts on my mind. He's not here
guilty I know this because this is all my comments
Well, okay when you're when I'm the only person in the chat
Probably I'm probably this year comment will be sure you know, I'll see even easier if you guys in membership and you
Your name in green right? That'd be cool. Hopefully I'll turn green tonight for another reason
Turn it from a frog or people are annoying
Okay, we're a lie. Okay
Charlie we are we not at
He honest how we need duck picks to be said, uh, I hear oh
Ziggy said he said a dick picked to uh
Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rusty, Rust
Part of the lore probably worse something up. Hey, Charlie. Good to see you. Oh, okay. Thank for gosh fucking sake. Okay
No, that one is your profile. Yeah, that one. That's a Alexander's official
No
Queens Queens fashion mall ID
Guys who's talking about people
We can guys you just coming so strong to the get them people will do to coming on the show. You're like, oh, no
they have out like
Maybe they'll really come on if people are nice and then
Then you can jump on them when they're on the panel and then you're in the audience, but otherwise
It's not funny. Thank you fucking okay wait
was may have not me
And say wait what no one has sent me anything. I know I mean you're a summer
Every other you know freakin 40 diamond has the whole you know get this book of world records collection of dick pics
all types shades
all shapes tight
Shapes sizes flavors colors and
I'm over here. I can barely tell the difference between
The word and and the ampersand
Hey dinner, you don't want any come on summer get some smoke come on summer come on get some smoke on my pal come on
Come on girl. Let's see. Oh, you don't want. Oh, you don't want any, but you what?
My use my use clothing
Don't you don't want my speedos? I was gonna get my speedos away and I was gonna
You know raffle and you're gonna be the first man. I've been
Thanks, okay. Yeah, I'm not no my my my
My spears actually be going to museum someday. I'm gonna have a
Madam to so's wax figure he made of me. That'll be the outfit
My original speedo. No, how perfect is that?
I'm just I'm good. I have a lot of good ideas
have a lot of good ideas yeah what it was basket to and her poppy I don't know
yeah hey loser what did you just say you just says
I'll take 365 free pass I'll pay off promise
Okay, so my last one was Rusty's ex staying at your hand. Okay, so
So Rusty, can you confirm? Did you ever did you ever date Tiffany? Where's t-shirt?
And she's not she's not a female to male transition. It's just I don't anyone you confuse rusty. What happened there?
Okay guys, it can't get confused. It can't get confusing. Yeah
Especially when guys start getting long hair of the older generation cannot tell the difference between the sexes anymore
Vicky did you the most whole time you slept or sleep with your cousin? Well, maybe just in a tent in the back
Yeah, I don't think she's she's saying oh, she was you know
Having intimate relations with her cousins weekly. I think she said oh, you know, maybe they made out when they were
Teenagers or something, but that's not too weird
Tiffany
Let's see, I tell Tiffy before, tell Tiffy, oh, I'm not going to, why do I tell her that?
I always create a reminder about Hannah talking, oh, oh, oh, I can't read the comments guys,
stop it.
You're so negative, now everyone's left the panel, guys, use this guy, I was talking
to a nice panel, and I'm talking to you guys in the chat.
Seiki and a ton of ex-boyfriend books. Oh
Yeah, I mean I have to admit I have a bunch of books about narcissism I was thinking about certain people when I bought these books, but
Yeah, I was going through the narcissists narcissism
All right, I don't know what you call it. Okay, so how are we doing chat?
So, I don't know does everyone's sleep is 48 people in chat pretty people
Okay, I think my friend Walder should be here. I don't know if he wants to be on camera
So I refuse to even come tonight. I
I'm sure he probably doesn't want to
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I'm just
Okay, whoo whoo ah
So
We're doing good guys
That's not move in but my mouth is
You had to pay a dude
$0.00 all in zero right or $50.00 to show his cock
Why would you do that better face? Oh?
Cuz you have a better face. I understand but you know, that's a little too much for a picture of this
How was though was it black?
Uh, no, no, I'm not doxing it. I mean it's reading her research. Oh, what did I say I?
Was just her name is butterface sniddle bat. I don't think that's a real name
It's funny now my name is
You're not doxing never have no yeah, I haven't been guys I
Was doxed months ago
Where that happens is someone said an unpaid, well, we're still several unpaid pieces of my house
Otherwise, it's a good way for people to find, you know, my address
Don't go looking for it, you're not gonna find it.
I told the peer people not to take your calls.
Well, I, you know, some of you, okay.
Bikki, Scott, Canning, I like you.
You're being, oh, loser, hold on.
Guys, if loser's being doxxed, why are you,
how are you being doxxed?
Is that your name, loser?
If loser's being doxxed, guys, I don't know.
Just kick those people for 24 hours
if someone's doxxing her in the chat, okay?
All right, this is a scam to get the to get a mod
Loser because I'm not some mod you just you can fix it because I don't know what's going on
I can't I can't even look at my phone Hannah and Tiffany attacked
immediately their manipulate
But they're hand victim card
enjoyable people
I'm not sure. Yeah. Well, I got he's kind of enjoyable
No, I mean mind like chatting with him 45 minutes over like a like a dinner and dessert
I don't know about going to the strip club with him afterward
But yeah, I'm sure we have a guess one. Oh
I see what is it? What is that? What are we looking at? Oh my god, it's form bombing
Ah, oh, I said dynamite guys dynamite look
You heard happy force you you're lying motherfucker
Guys is that a lag I don't know guys
See that's like a night like dynamite on my show. I don't know
I don't know is that loud can someone look at this to us for
Looks like he had
Mine dynamite or something. I don't know. What was that about guys? Why is my life so random?
So there's already a rabbit hole there. You don't need to like throw dynamite down and make it even bigger
I mean Alex is already there
Save the dynamite to for the cast of cards at the end. You don't use it in the rabbit hole. Please. Yeah, I'm sure
It's fire to find okay good
Stop the fighting. I know I'm sorry Alex
Yeah, I was gonna just gonna be like a
It's gonna be like I can see in a turner. I'm just gonna always have black eyes
He's gonna he's gonna like you know be a good talker. So he loves me. I'm gonna say why'd you do it?
I thought you do it
And I'll channel my pain into
Great songs
proud Mary
Well, what's love got to do?
Do what's wrong?
Lady lady chick on married and paying dues for zero dollars
little cows
Mo
No, I mean, I don't know why Tiffany you're wearing t-shirts. Oh, no
Someone taught Jeff about nightbot Jeff leaves at me night about alone person alone a lot of let's let's uh
Operate night ball without a murder mission. Oh
It's nice to meet you program the last answer to be perfect for him. Okay. Well in that case
I'll just keep it doing it. I'll make it
We'll make it the the accuracy higher in my book just don't roll with it
Just I'm sorry. I'm kind of I'm so out of it Norman Norman Bates Norman Bates. Oh, that's my name chef
Guys my all my all my University are crashing together right now some very strange feeling
Oh, no, I need it mod
You don't need a mod because you're a member. I see you just as easily. Hey, look at there's flow key. That's the member of the chat
Hey, but if you do want to take a drink home or something like, you know, you're like
So did to get warm
I'll try to pay it before you
It's a little bit tight this week. I did buy those extra $25 cigarettes. I'm budgeting. Oh
I'm sorry. That's sad. I'm sorry
That's about when when Wednesday, you know, I was born on Wednesday. So that's kind of sad
but also at Wednesday is ruled by you know, Mercury or Odin Odin say and
It kind of celebrated the you know, the the negative aspects of the say
It's not a party anyway, and it's Saturnalia. They had other
festivities where the gods, we get drunk, people get drunk, everyone just had a great time, but a lot of boobs would be shown.
This day, New Orleans is still cursed by the amount of boobs that they saw in 1992.
It was on the Girl's Gone Wild, first.
Yeah, so 30. Are you cool with women with summer and Christine after they lied on you? Oh, okay
So are you starting shit? Hold on Charlie?
I saw sort of diamond did she see this kind of AI with
Christine and summer in a loving embrace and kiss and I don't think they've ever been in that position before
Maybe maybe kiss unless she but not like that. I mean, there's tongue
Sorry, how'd you make that?
I know I think she left.
Oh, oh, shit, I was trying to get the good stuff.
We can just imagine guys.
So, you know, you just take the computer,
you put the computer around the breast area,
because that's the biggest part,
cover it with like a little latex, latex portions.
We'll all in there. It'll be fine. I'll come out a few years
And then I will probably you know, I'll be better. Otherwise
Always always get a second opinion before research
Please my friends
Don't want to lose any more of region demon
Than the couple of ear lobes that are already operating tables
Guys, I'm not funny guys. I'm not funny. I'm not I'm being dumb. Tell me I'm being dumb
Your batch implants are disgusting.
My implants are not botched for the diamond.
They're not, okay, one nipple's bigger than the other.
And I do have three nipples on one of them.
Oh, hold on, hold on.
Oh, okay, you're talking to me, okay.
The skirt community has become a old lady fella.
Well, I mean, I think the lead-ups of this show is a bingo night on a Friday night at the local church
Okay, so you're not wrong, but you're not right because nobody's here for bingo
Except for you guys except for now once the church has already started then the bingo people start coming in
You can't come in because you're mis-churched. Oh
Maybe guess one. Oh, who's this?
It needs it with a poem a ninja with a pencil is this you oh shit. I'll pick the one
Hello
Hey, how's it going?
Okay. Okay. Thank God even nice. It's a nice calming voice. Hi. Have you been on the show before?
Yeah, I've seen you in the chat on the show
Yeah, definitely check out the chat
Okay, nice. It's nice to see you. We'll bring you here tonight on this lovely Wednesday night
Oh, no much just having a night camp ready to fucking pass out or party. I don't know
What are you drinking?
Little whiskey
Whiskey, okay
Anybody in shadow whiskey person right now?
If you haven't met authority or you want to come up have a whiskey shot with our guests
I'm looking at 40 diamond of a ninja with a pencil. I think
You guys will get along great. So look he please say sorry. Okay. I'm sorry of all the support is very I'm sorry
Apologize the world for anything
Well, you said my apology he man and everybody everyone to say yes and
No harm no foul, right?
Chicken is a foul. Yes
Christina's my diversity three diamond laughing face flirty. You're not kidding
Look, he said Vicky by forty Vader once you he's implying. He still does his parents. Okay?
of 40s for the 40 left. Okay. Well, anyway, anyway, I don't know. I don't know about this. I don't know about this
It appeared to be a
You know a farmhouse. I mean in LA. I'm not sure. I'm not sure where it is. I'm not sure where it is
But I think I saw a raging humans car there last time I left. He was sitting out waiting for at least a few hours
So that might be true love
What do you think guys true love
You never know never know I grew up on Disney movies
No
You know, I can believe that you know
Cinderella's curse we lifted
chickens no white will
Well, so marry the prince probably get restraining order against the seven dwarfs. They look like a little bit touchy-feely
Then we have who else you know
Frickin and frozen or not frozen
Pangle got rid of her stepmother played by Lisa Lampinelli or you had that or Carol Burnett. I'm not sure
Oh, and what else guys? What am I missing guys? You know if I lose a bulk from the craft
That's like this Dorothy from Return to Oz
Isn't that crazy? You know that sir
Learned something every day. I'm pulling some some of the the craft and the trivia out of my butt right now
Do you play one the black drag queen in the?
Two long food things for everything Julie Neumar. Who is the black drag queen? Anybody know?
Anybody here still
If you're diamond not an older scene or you're she's older. I've been replaced. I already can't yeah
We can't convert flurry all we can do is
You know time them out for a few second. I mean it's like really it's like I think
Relatively, they're harmless the people I've seen in the chat on the streets lately. I think people are just nuts and lucky him
I'm still standing
Miley yeah, yeah, and that was the but they attack you and ban
They thought we have your boyfriend on the panel defending. I mean he left, but you know, you have your boyfriend defending
well
Very happy for you guys. Huh getting a 40 diamond rate. I know
Do you give your cats cat once in a while catnip yeah, I have right here. Oh, I think I'm right here. Where is it over here?
This was like my feet cat cat. Oh, you what's kind of catnip here?
You ever make a pile they love when you make tea with it. I like the tea watch this look I pour it on their back like that
Oh, oh, you look oh my gosh. Oh, and here comes Lola Lola come here. You're getting on the get on this
Come right back. We're having a cat in a party. Here she comes. Hey Lola. Here she goes. You're right here. Oh
Okay, now they're covered in cat. Are you happy guys? They're covered in cat. Oh, you're there
Okay
Well, those those are the moments that make life worth living right take more pills and regulate your emotions. Oh
What?
What are you talking? I'm I don't take pills on Miley. There's a Miley. Oh Mikey Mikey. She told me
Online stuff about you be best to ignore the hote
Hote
Okay
Let's do ignore the okay
Do not contribute oh the kids okay, and then get see but do this laugh
Reality answers cat nip time doing run by run my chat guys is exciting. I can only imagine your
My motion yeah, it's kind of like a kind of like a gray alien, you know
Major depression. You turn you'll say I will die from a line of work. I gave you there's the same meaning
So I hope I didn't say I did not make that kind of joke. Who's joking about?
Matt in the chat stop it
Not funny guys
That is actually a hell of a drug. It's a hell of a
Three bad guys. Next thing you want to complete my math. Just try a bunch of fentanyl
You'll forget all about it. Okay. I'm just kidding. I don't think so. So it says some day stop hitting the pipe
Maybe
You'll find out it's not psychosis. Well
Who's on a pipe? I just want to smoke a a
night with
Willa Ford's pipe
Play hockey with them. That's interesting to ask
Not your not your I your wiener like you know, like I'm like a pipe like a little one of those pipe bars. I
Don't know nevermind. Okay. How's the chat doing? Yeah, why are you so quiet? You so awkward?
Awkward with me alone. I don't have to say
Can't even handle with hot guys. I'll wake up
Next day my underwear off
I had a lipstick smear all over my face and I was like, what happened last night?
Oh, the chat was telling me to get in the skirt and hit on the guys again.
Chat, I blame you.
Is this Christine?
Hello.
Oh, oh, hey Christine.
Sure I am, because, you know, I'm going to tell you.
Bloody diamond. Don't worry about what fucking hospital yet is a nice looking hospital
If you think you're trying to intimidate me you are dead
wrong
For your diamond, it's called the Mayo Clinic. It's including me to unlock on alive myself
Glory don't know you're not supposed to say that you're not saying on my chest. That's what she said
Larry you're not saying that stuff. Don't say that to Christine. Just don't say no. He can go fuck himself
That's okay to say that I mean it's like it's fun to say that to Allison, you know
You know, he thinks he thinks he's going to find the hospital I work at
He thinks he's going to make me lose my job. He thinks he's going to
Docs me, but he hasn't realized my real name's not even Christine you tarred
And dying to know your real name now, but I'll never guess because Christine doesn't really rhyme with anything
So it's really a maybe she's a big fan of the opera person. I don't know. Maybe her name is
What was it? What was the um, what was Christine's understudy and in uh, the fan of the opera? Anybody know?
He did
sassy
She did say to unalive myself
I timed it out and witched for 10 seconds and it removed her shit or his shit
He did say it
I know anybody any music. Oh my god. I'm gonna get me a block in your chapter. Well, I'll take a screen shot
I'm practically I'm practically one step for me blog for my own shot. I mean, I thought I can't like, you know, I can't magically
Fix it fix everything. I'm trying. I'm trying my best. Hey, babe. Thank you. Yeah, you really fix it here on tricks
And taking pills. Hell. I don't smoke pot. I don't drink. Fuck you
Well
You take placebo
No, it's kind of pill. It's kind of pill. I mean, it's just sugar. Well, what would I take a placebo for?
For anything, they're actually that's gonna be as almost as half of effective as like the actual medicine to see those are quite effective
Yeah, just based on the thing. I'm not sure I'm not sure I haven't taken myself. There's a band that I call placebo. There's a
The pills probably when the taster pills I prefer to hear the he Charlie. He's got a dick. He walks the street every night
sells his body
Well, I think as a morally rents rents out his body here's rents out whatever it gets. No, my implants are not botched
See, that's what you're not that's what you're not
He's saying that my you and you've never seen my breasts. I'm not like you and try to show them
I'm not like you that I need the
Pro cleavage to try to get attention
Lordy did ask to see your boobs and
What do you know, you know, I've never shown my breasts
So that's definitely you know, because you don't have to do it from behind her curtains at home with the curtain open a little bit and the lights up
It's every be shown on YouTube or TV
And I don't think she wants it about anyway
I don't wear bras if I don't have to and I don't wear panties either. I like that one
Wow, I know I know I know what I'm counting the fall asleep tonight
Christine just you know your video was completely a I
It's all it was AI
Yeah, but she actually a lecture did put some
input for the lyrics into it and so it actually meant that that does make it copyrightable for
Talking about I'm talking about the video. She did of me. Oh for you. Oh, that's a different diamond
I thought you have a lecture here for me. Yeah, flirty diamond. Yeah, but you're kissing. I saw you could you were kissing Christine summer
What was that about? Why are you Chris? Why are you kissing Christine? I was shocked. I didn't know I didn't know you
Come on psych. Stop it. It was AI. She
Oh my gosh. Oh my gosh. Pretty diamond. Get out of here. Get off me. You can do that.
Pretty diamond. How do you do that? I can't even figure out AI. Somebody did it. It's
AI though. Do you have a secret AI hack? He's the disgusting person. How about a picture
She'd kiss any man that that would allow it
Tell it you kiss JT. Oh JT's backstage. You know something flirty. I love summer with all my heart
You know, it wouldn't bother me if I kiss summer anyway
It's the fact that you as a disgusting human
Tried to think you were gonna anger and get back at me and or summer and it didn't work
You know, someone was laughing when I showed her, she was laughing, and then she made this, she made the little lunchable thing that came out of them, and I was like, thank you, they're good, I don't know, people bring me food sometimes, they think it's like, oh, it's gonna give me anxiety or trauma, I'm like, oh, that's my favorite sandwich or fruit or whatever, I don't know, I like fruits and sandwiches.
Good thing. Okay, JT. You're not your camera's not on backstage my dude. So I have no problem people smoking pot
I don't I would much rather somebody smoke pot
That have an alcoholic beverage because it changes people who they are
And speaking of your swishers can't can't somebody hook up?
Hook you up with swishers that live in another state. Well, they had they said they
They had a couple boxes left apparently because they haven't had them for like a week
But now they have a dead some left tonight, so I bought just a couple
Okay, good. I don't know a few days left maybe of swishers. So yeah, it's just
This stats is stats through stats Street walkers are earlier
No, that's not a problem. That's not a problem, sweetheart
Pot has many medicinal
Benefits from it
It's also like an ancient crop it's an ancient natural crop and it's like we also we have these
THC receptors specifically made for
receiving and transcribing THC.
Okay, we have another guest to say hi to Christine
and Miguel with a pencil.
Hello.
Leave Miguel alone.
No, I mean, I'm sorry.
I mean, I'm a ninja with a pencil.
I'm sorry.
I can't see tonight, I swear.
It's okay.
I told you you need to have your eyes checked
and a pair of glasses, maybe.
Yes
That's why I came up here. We're okay. How's it going baby? I'm good Christine trying to stay cool. It's hot
That's what I hear. I hear it's hot as it which is
Oh, yeah, but it's cold as a witch's titty than what if it's hot as a witch's what would it be?
Sorry, I was a witch's pussette pussette. Yeah, it's a put they
Putty putty putty
Putty-pud. Okay, FD. It's usually a bit stat. Street walkers die
Oh, it was D-30 diamond not for diamond get some bear maze or just stay on the internet and get off of the streets
Please I don't want to hear you on those. Well, and you know this is basic of the street walkers
And he walks by himself on the street
You know the statistics about that
Nobody's dumb. Where put on a burka until someone takes you, you know
back to a safe room, and then you can then you can reveal yourself you're
And and you don't know if it's a safe room. It could be somebody that's got a red rummer
Well, I'm right guys. It's you day. It's too dangerous. I think it's too dangerous. It's dangerous. It's very dangerous
Just you know just invest in a ring alarm. I guess don't loss and then I can't have bare mace and then
You know just forget about the cameras and stuff like that. It's just the
You know, you can like maybe train and train an animal to do the self defense of your house
I don't know like, you know like a
really cute when like one of those capuchin monkeys was trained with mace and
Whatever else that guy's channel. Yeah, we cool cookie
Rambling guys. It's just pot. It's his pot guys pot is bad for you. I
Only have one beer. I'm acting what's not bad for you, so you don't
Well, you know, I don't think it's great. I don't think it's great for you. I mean, it's good because it's like, you know
Oh, it has very good and additional
properties in it. It helps the lady. It helps insomnia. It helps inflammation. It helps depression
I mean so many things
Yes, so TGIW thank goodness
Oh, FW for weed for weed. Okay. Do you not mean gels of the batch implants keep project?
In plants she does he does not like that I have implants
Guys he thinks that going at me because my implants is a bad thing
But he doesn't realize I did that for myself. I've raised I birthed four sons
I breastbed all four of my sons. That was my treat to myself
Yeah, and that is a
gift you brought to the world caring force on wow, that's that what 36 months of
being pregnant and
It's not it's not easy. That's
Each one of them
breastfed till about 18 months to give them proper nutrients
Oh, it was a bad start in life
Yeah
Well, you know, I I
Unfortunately, I drink just formula and by the time I came around my mom had already had two sons. They're probably about 10 years older than me already and she was
She she's like with she's not with the breastfeeding did to her boobs at 20
She's not gonna she was like what I did at 30. So it's like, yeah, so she just like, you know, yeah, these great great formulas
I think I turned out completely normal guy. Yeah, so how are you sweetheart?
I'm just kidding. I'm fine. You're not okay. So guys, everyone be nice. Let's not talk about people's
relatives or their family. Let's all let's just address the people and talk about you know, if you
start talking about family, you're going to get timed out people. No stands or buts.
Yeah, that's like, let's uh lay off a la familia.
There's no reason for it. Yeah. Yeah, there is I mean there because there's our families have done things to do with
Yeah, you want to go after somebody go after them. Leave the family alone
Yeah
What's this?
CCC C senior reader. Here we go. Okay, so thinking of something to eat tonight though. I might get a
Little delivery, but I think I'm gonna get way maybe by nine three or ten. I'll be starving
It's like you have become the patriarch of Benny's or a Benny's channel. I have become the patriarch. Well, how why is that?
What do they say about me over there? I was I was there recently to say hi to Benny, but you know
I don't really go to chat anymore. You're not just
Hold on
I'm missing all the comments. Look at all the comments that I missed. Oh my god. I'm way behind. I'm so sorry guys
Godie you attacked her at times. Okay. I don't know but
Times or time keys. Why me? I'm gonna use time or time time after time
Butterfly is the bat for the babies. Wow psyche. Okay, Christine haven't thank you for saving the song
30 are you gonna meet Vader? He's an online young man
That's I think we're caught up, okay
Nobody's laughing
The actual nobody in the chat is laughing. So it's not nobody's laughing. It's nobody in chat laughing. You're attempting to
Go simping on her using you. I had a no raising demon. Don't hide your
Yeah, your sock account. Okay, so date me, please. Okay. Well, I guess I don't have any
I mean, you know sedation all I can do is like, you know
Continue lullaby and kind of like, you know, just fall asleep listening to the show. I can try to wake you up by
Surprising you with my speedo, but you know, I don't know. All I know is the element of surprise and the element of boredom
That's pretty much all I got so far
Seiki there's a whole other dance
Or voice
Yeah, yeah
Oh my god, yeah, we if you think my discord was bad way to you, you know, I have a
Make my disc if you think my the food I myself on these on YouTube is bad. I'm waiting to my discord. Oh my god. It's just
Oh my god, so many documents like if I was like if I had like, you know all the time
I could it's like a legal library. I could just be case after case. I mean, it's just like
Oh, I think I have a bunch of attorneys running my disco. I'm not sure. Okay
Yes, we're having fun guys. Yes, there's not really uh, there's not really I'm not really being stalked by librarians and nurses
Yeah, JT is here. It's a good thing. I don't see Hannah or Tiffany, I guess
Well, that means that they've blocked you and so they didn't want to see you
I'm sorry. You just you fell your
collateral damage
Alex
Are you underwater? Alex you're underwater
Okay, you want us to call the police okay, I was gonna call 911. We'll get it. We'll get you dragged out of that river
I've been forced to July, so
it's forced to July, shut the fuck up
I'll wait for a second
Shut up, shut up, shut up
it's forced to July
let me enjoy my forced to July weekend
like a real American
do you understand what fireworks represent
they represent bombs
dropping on the enemy air
it's re-represented
you know my son
I had a son born on July 3rd
and it's so funny because when he was growing up they normally you know in bigger cities do fireworks on the third
versus the fourth
And he always thought for years those fireworks because of his birthday. It's cute. It was cute when he was little
Oh, that is cute. So I have a son's birthday tomorrow and in 28 minutes
Maybe I'll go wake him up
Awesome. We'll have the birthday to christine's
Son, you know, I do know some people with birthdays around these times too that are poor to me
Wish everyone a happy birthday in chat that has one or you know in the future in the past, you know
Whatever is closer. Well, we all have a birthday future
Birthdays
Well, this will just call my show the birthday club now. I was supposed to get a birthday club
Just to call it or the unbirthday club. Oh, I'll work up the logistics. We gotta we have to also get a compound guys
We're all gonna move to this compound. We're gonna come we're gonna go in by helicopter
That's the only way that you build a game. Jay one. Is it really your birthday tomorrow, too?
Oh wait a minute somebody said was a birthday. Yeah, J1
Are you telling the story J1 is always trolling you never know when to believe when we're not
Uh, yeah, Hannah, you also happy birthday. J1 guys miss miss Lear and Hannah. No, no arguing over men, you know
women always women never look
This makes man look good when women are arguing
My other my other son one of my other son's birthday is the same birthday as
School of Athens. Oh wow
We have a we have a we have a J. Welcome to the chat J
Hello governor
Oh, oh, who's that? Oh, he left. Oh, I'm sorry. I didn't mean to offend you
I mean it was it sounded like they won, but I don't know
It's everything is J. Well, I think it's strong. I don't know
He might be having internet issues. I
don't think his
Here's back. He's back. Let's go. And you know
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't think, you know, Angela
He is a very, if it's a he, I'm
very, I'm not sure he or she, um,
very talented though. I have to
give him that. That he is very
talented. That's what I think
that's a lot. That's what a lot of
I hope he's doing something with
that talent because I'm telling
He might be he might be
Role-playing as a dog in my nether chats. I'm not just I'm just not sure. Are you are you Jay? Are you are?
Jay are you doing that?
Are you a character
Drawing a Christine
I have I have one of Christine and her dog doing is he follows you and
Well, here's Fawzi. Hold on, I got Fawzi.
Fawzi, Fawzi.
Fawzi.
Okay, here we go.
Okay, so here's Fawzi. It's not...
Guys, my art is... I'm still learning art, but there's Fawzi.
Fawzi?
Fawzi.
And then I have Christine.
I drew on this page.
Oh my gosh, okay. So here she is. There. She did glasses on her head.
She's that she's that that kind of where's my real teeth. I don't have all my teeth that Mona Lisa
Yeah, see they're there near the Mona Lisa spot. Yeah, but look there's there's a little bit of lips
The lips are going around the teeth in a perfectly symmetrical way. I do it for summer
Yeah, I will if someone needs to pose. I need her to pose like a French
you know French woman and
I'll do a little Titanic
drawing for
Spanky you got the short one make a wish. Oh
We've got the short we've got the short short chopstick or something. Oh, oh, we also have one we have rock
We have Ron Joe Lord Vader. Yo, do you know Vicky? We have Vicky and then chat. I do Vicky
She's Vicky to said draw me as boobs. And so I tried to like grant her wish
I don't know if it worked perfectly, but it's like kind of looks like boobs or maybe a couple of left over doughnuts
And yeah, there's that's that's Nikki. Okay, or Vicky Vicky. There's this is this is actually I thought it was Doug
but it's actually
It's actually dingle or dong, it's dingle again, it's dingle like avatar, and then...
I drew uh the guy that is like Luigi I drew him too but I guess it's like Luigi that would stay turned
Yeah, stay turned. Yes
I'm drawing about you know, 30 or 40 portraits already. I don't
I'm in world famous
Yeah, I'm drawing like, you know, I drew I drew DJ electric. I drew the electric, you know, there's DJ electric
She's waving at everyone say hi
um, I drew
No, Gotti. I drew Gotti in the shot. I drew Gotti. He's right there with the banana.
I drew Rogue Nomad. I drew others easy having a sip out of his pina colada. Okay.
And there's there's Harry Justin. He's he's he's a lady a lady. Bick a lady
Both he needs the odior and the shaving cream and then there's sassy scarlet if you're familiar sassy scarlet
There's time yeah, there's uh, there's a spunky there's spunky
Ghosts there's ghosts right there
and we have
Jamie's Cowboys, and we have J-Dog.
Wow, it's the whole everyone's here a doggy dog. And then we have flirty diamond and oh wait home. We have X
Existence we have a money for 20
There's LD LD with his dog Duke, okay, and I say after my chat
Where's the 40 there's big Eldo like rolling his eyes and I think there's oh
There's another picture of Godie and then
There's a diamond 30 diamond and God you're the same same person guys. It's okay. I'm revealing it there for the first time
person you can change it you can
Pick on flirty diamond and got it. Well got it flirty diamond is just gaudy and a voice changer
It's just a character. He's made up. He likes to drag on the weekends. He does like to go to the blade
But they're just gonna buy you're supposed to buy a hot dog. Maybe mug somebody. So yeah
I think they think it's one of your first ones.
You have a Lucy.
You have a laughing Christine.
Marty.
Why?
Oh, I don't want to say, uh, no.
The flirty diamond as a deck?
Uh, never mind, never mind.
Yeah.
It's safe.
How you doing, mate?
How you doing, man?
I like the curtain back there.
Nice curtain.
Oh, it's OK.
No, it's OK.
So you're interested in dating a flirty diamond, mate,
420?
Money I see there's no damn is in chat. I can hook you up. But you have to say yes right now
Why are you hiding me? I'm not you know, so I was talking myself on full-screen
You wanted people to come up we came up. What do you hide?
I was I'm very focused on the question. So yeah, sorry. Are you interested in this guy money for 20?
I think you might have some weed
You know
Baped rejuvenation that loose see oh my gosh. Sorry. Why are you saying that?
Way for a bit. They're not they're not to say those words on my show for you, please especially
It's absolutely shocking please guys. No, no
You respect the vagina
We all came to this earth through vagina all of it, you know
C-section this is actually we saw the ticket. We saw the ticket to come through the vagina
Where where'd you come out of my children came through a vagina
I came out of I came out of a I came out of a store. We're still trying to figure out who fucks the store
I'm just okay. That was a really stupid joke. Oh, I'm so sorry
I bet you did man's that's kind of gay
it wasn't my it wasn't my I think I think I'm
I was
are you threatening the channel 30
oh that's many for 20 I thought it was
many for 20 I'm sorry I thought that was you
say what the hell is wrong with you say
I'm sorry that was I thought that was you
I know you like I know you do I thought
I thought you were Jeff because
I'm a little bit confused right now
I know you like I know you like
Everyone's like everyone's nice pussy, you know as long as a little groomed and you know has a nice meow
Rondo come from lion
Your name on this it says it says
I don't know who you are. Who are you sir?
Rondo from yesterday. I come from
Lion, okay
Okay, rondo guys is rondo okay to be on the show. I'm not sure
You draw a picture of me
Right. Oh, I drew you too. Let me see if I have the picture. Very nice teeth
That let me see
I don't know if I see it. Rhonda. Oh
I drew babs, I drew beta. I don't see it. I don't know. Oh, oh, I found you. I found you. There you go
I drew Rhonda. I did. No, no, no, no, no. You guys, you can compare his photo to my
See
Yes, it looks just like look at that. This is me. That is me fitting in
Hold on yours
Yours is a picture is yours a picture of like Andy Griffith's
Covered in tar or something. What's going on?
Where's that picture? It looks like it looks like a black person
Who are you?
Why are you talking like an African? I don't believe I don't believe you're African. You sound like you're putting on some kind of
jungle voice
Hello. Yes, sir. I
Am too young. You're exposed. You're exposed. Okay, a little black Sambo. You are
anybody
Yeah, well, it's actually an Indian name. So don't don't be offended, you know, not in India
Yeah, like in India. Hey, I have poison dart just for you
What are you talking about about me?
Well, I'm sorry.
Everyone on that show needs to have an average IQ of at least 50.
You're way off, sir.
But boys like you're in the mood, huh?
I mean, it's like, I'm not going to have an hour discussion about
the brand name of
Bananas or I don't know whatever the fuck we're talking about. He's he's taking us way up topic
rondo like banana fool rondo you're not
He's still in elbows name. He's confusing me. I mean I think he's elbow and I
Send you for American dollars yesterday. Oh, I know you are. I know you are hold on
Okay
Yeah, I don't think he's the same person that he's talking about. I don't think he's I think it's a smokescreen guys
Yeah, someone was you know a couple people were timed out for probably until like 9 p.m.. To midnight tonight
So or between that time I can probably come back
JT what we have here is a perfect
shit, oh
Okay, so so I'm so I'm trying to argue with people and yeah
You guys are you JT's annoids you as a mod?
You can time them out for five minutes and let them sit there angry
Seem as do you just time out there if they're causing trouble
But fuck you fuck everyone who's trying to ruin the room this panel. Just don't hide. It's time out guy. Yeah
Yeah, it's time. It's time out. It's time out
Yes
It's very effective because if they don't like to show and then they get timed out
They'll just be like oh fuck show and then they'll leave immediately if they leave like the show
They'll stick around to find out they're untimed out in five minutes. So it's pretty good system. It works worse
Hey tricks, how are we doing guys? So it's Wednesday. What's going on tonight? Oh, it's almost Thursday
Uh, it's the life force weekend. We're gonna have you have plans. You're gonna have fireworks or anything
I was a fireworks night. It looked kind of more like dynamite, but excuse me psyche. Yes. We want to know when
Beta come on panel. Yeah, she was here tonight. She
I didn't hear
Yeah, she came up for like just a few minutes, but then she started being started acting
Oh, actually it was like last night and then she
She was just she was last night she came on the panel and then tonight
She's or the day she just came in the chat for a few minutes
but she sent me some very unusual text messages that just had me scratch in my head and
says some
Pretty unusual things like weird things to me like you know, just like I mean the birthday and then she's mad at me
I'm just anything I'm saying here. I was like being nice
I don't know guys. I don't want to offend the audience but beta
She's into very very black african man like rondo. Okay, shut up rondo. Okay. No, and she will
Be be the dated raging demon and raging
He's wider than I am region is wider than I am so be it's not true
It is not here. We really should I know I know okay. Well, yeah
At least he brought up her name. I didn't because I'm not allowed to say
Well, I hopefully hopefully we all get hired for you know
Movies and TV shows when we show we saw our great range of emotion and
Ability on these panels. I think we're all gonna be discovered by Hollywood at least
Maybe the world
Crack fingers my fingers are not crack thing. I mean guys guys. I just got this beautiful new nail kit. Look, it's really cool
It has has all these different
There is all these different tools to clean my nails
well
Actually in Africa
We mixed our cocaine with the gun gun powder
So that's not very smart. So when you go to the top of a line, it would explode and you get trapped and what happens?
No, we have sex with that.
We have sex with that.
You have sex with who?
We, when we do sex, we do cocaine with the gunpowder.
Okay, well, let's not glamorize any kind of blood stuff.
Okay.
The cocaine is a little bit 1977 a little bit expensive. It's a little bit
Well, you know
Alex could tell us how much it is
Alex how much is the how much is the eight ball Alex? I know you just
Eat so it's very cheap
Well, you know crack it crack defense on the price cocaine is cocaine's expensive, but crack is cheap, right? No
Yep, I don't I don't I had never been to Africa
Oh, I have to say is no your dealer because of the simple fact that no is mixed in a lot of shit and
No, I'm a lighting
Tell my brother that I have heard but I've heard of you know music with Marty
And then we had to send the person
You guys know someone passed away from pencil on the chat she's like somebody I'm sorry
I'm walking like the name is escaping right now. I'm gonna send very recently a fentanyl to right who was that guys
Andre agent six six six
Watch her rejection play out is in front of you all what who's rejection?
Yeah, you know, they're having a conversation in chat
I can't follow it all. I mean, they're they're writing novels in there. I can my book is writing itself
I'll just copy and paste the chat into this book and
Have them most drama you've ever seen
Spanky, how are you rumor has it?
Rusty's vagina was made
For the pictures and Arby's man. Oh my gosh guys come on guys. It's not nice. I'm sorry. I guy
I can't see the comment and
Read it before I say it
I'm sorry. It's behind a dollar sign. Hannah would, yeah, Hannah loves JT. She doesn't have a good heart.
Ron, Rando Vader wants your BBC. Well, help to ask, help to ask Barry The Turtle about that.
I don't know if anybody has a BBC over here.
No.
No, I share I have a I have a BBC but it's it's a it's a more like white and pink
That's not really not really. I don't want to hear about your BBC. I would knock you out with my deep
So, you know, sir, you have to have more than a two inch or did not get anybody out, okay?
Sir, you know you have two inches
Brando two inches. Yeah, it's more like two feet
It's more like what?
It's oh, oh my god. Oh my god. What's the nice size?
24 inches 24 inches. Okay, so that would mean it's like longer than your your arm your
Yes, I like I actually strangled Christine with my undercut. Oh my god. Oh my god
Christina Christina machete that she tops the heads off
She's in it. She just like Nicki Minaj and she can even rap better than her. Okay
Nobody can we get back? You need a bundle for 40?
Guys also around our own bundle business. Oh, so big and
Enough big and enough blood you pass out. Well, you know, unless it's my blood. I really I'm not gonna
Be too shocked about some of the time he tried to pretend
To play bongos and betas and strewn it up because the video he was going to use an addict commercial
Yeah, oh my god
Rado you gotta get the youtube premium my man. It's like that. No, no, no, no, it's
It's way too expensive to have that
No, no, no, I just I just subscribe to it and it was I think $12 a month for the first few months or six months or something
That's but I am in Africa. So
You can afford your phone bill he forgot what he was doing and we heard a different voice so
There's that now. Yeah, and I recognize you are and I know that
Um, but I'm not gonna I'm not gonna blow your cover. You know, you can just be right. You can be a rondo or rando, whatever
But everyone, you know, we want to be you want to be you want to be you know, you know
Do you want to be an antemima?
Buckwheat
Yes, is it racist
No, it's not racist because it's like, you know, it's like
It looks like
We don't believe in racism in Africa. We don't believe in it
No, I don't think I don't I mean, it's just a very dark. It's a very dark skin
But I haven't seen people from Africa with that darker skin. I really have I mean a second so they're very dark
It's not some means and there's all different guys were all a cornucopia of different colors and I mean
I'm whiter than like the you know
Yeah, we still people I got I got a lily white a white rabbit. Yeah
I'm freaking white and then I thought I was white and then fucking I see like you know
Well, they make Johnson and
Yeah, yep, oh my gosh, it was so much fun. I love when we let we all that lose in the panel and
Yeah, I took a hydrocarbonate the other night you and everybody thought I was drunk, but I was a fun drunk
That's very good. So I will be back. I'm going to strangle my own anaconda. Okay, okay
Send me a photo when it spits the poison. Okay. Bye. Absolutely. Thank you. Bye. Bye. Bye. It's later
Later skater
After a while anaconda dial. Okay. I mean racism. It says there's no reason I said there's a reason. I mean it's like
It's very controversial. Let's not talk about it. Everybody of color is a wheat and that show is corny
Everybody is the color of wheat everybody. I mean, it's like, you know
White people are kind of like more like the cream of wheat and you know, I'm just kidding. Okay. Keep Hannah modded
It's like you in return your account
your channel will keep getting
Advertisements from BG BKT. Well, it's okay
I advertise and see if every time I go to the beach take off my shirt
If people ask me and I'm mad at be that if I'm not mad at be they'll say you know
Beeski if I'm mad at be that I say it says for Burger King is good
And then I should I put them in your oh, it's Burger King anymore. Come on
Well, I mean it this is it this fits the initials of the other tattoo
I don't know about everybody else, but I am you're you're what?
I'm a fun drunk. Oh, you're a fun right? Oh, I
Various if I just start drinking too early, and then I think I'm like 12 hours later. I'm still drinking and stuff like that
I'll probably just pass out and I'm interesting. I have a good buzz going and I'm having fun on the show. Yeah
That's a long. Oh, I'm ready for bed almost I'm tired. Oh
Christine the entire well
I dropped the z
It's kind of like that's kind of it's not a very mild
No, it's an anaheist to me. Oh, okay, miss to me and
Apparently me and anaheist means don't do well together because I guess I just don't take drugs
And I took an anaheist to me to those feeling dizzy and boy
Everybody thought I was drunk. It was kind of fun
I love uh, I was like on the party. Yeah
then guys there is a difference in El Dorado and
Rado Rado here the Xander outside. Look. I was in a side
He's doing fireworks
He's gonna do borrow IRL. What can he do? Oh my god?
Oh my god
I hate those, I hate those whistlers, they strike me hard dude.
Oh shit, that was amazing horn.
Oh I love it, oh yeah, I love it, it's great.
Yeah look, keep it going, yeah.
Whoa!
This is the Alex we know
That's the best you got
Finally a higher pitch and more annoying sound than Alice's own voice. Thank you Alex perfect
If we said Danny, I used to say I'm perfect. Okay. This is me warming up baby. It's not forced to July yet
This is the epicizer on the fourth when you hear those bombs blowing. That's me
I mean the fireworks. No. No. Yeah, when you hear the high-end shit
Let's talk about BOMB. Let's know no be no BOMB. Yeah, okay, please. No
That's all calm down as we don't need to go straight to oh, you know, you know
Please please stop
Ever been good. Oh, hold on. I'll go fix this here. There we go there now. We're all we're all equals. Okay, that was there
Yeah, I get excited about my postage you like what the hell
Why nobody I mean, it's like, you know, I'm a patriot I fall for my country, man
I get excited Alex you wake up early decorate your bicycle
Decorate your bicycle with you know, you know, maybe
Here's more
Okay, okay, I mean I told you just calm the fuck down. You're not you're you're going insane again again
Why why is the blast has that's you know, but that's embarrassing playing with little kids fire works
Yeah, that's so shitty like those. Yeah, those are like you know, you can get those for like a dollar at the at the little
Little taco stand or whatever. I know the little Mexican stand, right? They're like in a little little poppers
I mean my brother when actually he would go to a port of Arata
He would get in that the first cab to get fine
He'd tell the guy driving to like an hour away to like the professional fireworks
You come back with these big bombs. It'd be like a professional fireworks show, but as it was cool
I did like Alice's attempt. It's this cool. Thank you Alice for bringing fire with such a he's not backstage. So
It's okay guys. This is gonna be crazy. I'm a block on the fourth. I'm gonna be live for a while
Block party. Are you in a block party? Are you gonna go to is everyone going to good times?
I hear good times of having a huge 4th of July bash. Is everyone going there?
Everyone's coming out. Summer shoots fireworks often for life
She does well page page two pages a lot
Top page this song called up on the roof. I know a woman named page
And she likes to sit up on the roof
Can't we always use the top of your head
What's going on? How are you doing? How are you tonight? Oh, I'm good
The real fireworks are going to happen. It's like he and Alexander go in there first live. Oh, yeah, maybe
I'll be better
I don't know how it happens, but I think the stream just gets worse and worse. What midday?
Guys and someone banned me night for a day. There's
Every time because he just so and he just comes in so negative saying oh the stream is worse than worse
I'm terrible the chat the panel so he's so negative
It's just bad keep panning for a day until he comes in where it's the old treat his brain to eventually write nice things
And then them like leave him on the panel or like leave him on the chat at least but till then
We like
Well, yeah, we like I I'm like, you know, I'm more of like a
12 noon person is it that I'm midnight person. So I look at him a little bit of suspicion
Hey platform boots. Hey, there's rusty in the chat. That rusty gets rusty. Okay
Hey of low key best loser Irish fresh and Vicky guys we have the whole whole bathtub is
is on the set tonight. We're having a bath together. Kind of a little bit erotic.
I mean, I bring the lights and the bear. No, we have lights, guys, all here.
The bear? You're about the bear? Where's the bear?
No, your dog I I'm the bear. Oh, you're the bear. Okay. Well, let's talk about let's talk about the after party later
I don't ever know our business
Yes, please teddy bear. Oh every cat your cat. I heard meow. No, that was the dog with the squeaky toy
Oh, the cat the cat is still in somewhere in the house
I don't know. I thought I thought the dog could squeeze the cat too hard.
No, and also this toy is not supposed to be out here, but whatever, you know.
Yeah, my dog toy, he can't take certain toys outside either.
Mhmm.
He has inside toys and outside toys.
Yep. Oh, yeah. Well, I have I have toys I use on the inside of me and toys are using the outside of me
So I really oh my gosh. Oh my gosh. Oh, that wasn't appropriate. I'm so sorry
Be a flag
Be here all you want to see if I don't care how many
Cox you choked down or wear puto. Oh my gosh guys now. I'm speaking
Mexican gangster like guys stop making me say these things
Come on. I can't I can't see the chat before I read it out loud because I
But I mean I think I'd like to like be able to like you know is the chat, but I mean there's just a vulgar
All right. Yeah, I want to see the chat
You guys can't even get a lighter
So I couldn't get fireworks if it's life-dependent on it money for 20 couldn't get fireworks if it's life
Dependent on it
20 couldn't get a bottle rocket
He wouldn't even know where to turn to get a fucking those snapshots that you can find in the night at a sex store
That you snap you throw on the floor
Shut up. None of you got fireworks. You don't even have to connect to get fireworks and you're not going to Pennsylvania because you don't have cars
So shut the fuck up
Shut up, dick. You can't even get fireworks
Dangerous anyway, yeah, I got ten mats of bottle rock is ten mats of everything you can't get a fucking matchbox
Here's a little
Yeah, cuz I sell them bro. I go to Pennsylvania and I rack up
I spent 10 grand and I come here and I make 50 grand
You understand our business works, bro
Yeah, I go to Pennsylvania. I have my boy that runs a show. I buy I rack up 10 grand
I come here and triple that shit. I buy them down. What do you got?
Let me see you show one of firecracker
Don't fuck up. I got shit here. Fuck. No, sorry. I can fucking I put I throw money in the pot
I don't go. I gotta deal with that shit
Well, it's better, but money in the pot than P in it like mr. Bigfoot is that so
Look up in the sky and what I blow off every force of July
and
I was one of my 20 years and
You think people like me motherfucker that
Fuck you can't even afford a fucking matchbook bro. Shut up your volume Alex. You're
Tranquilizers
I turned it all the way down. He's this is loud. I mean, I don't know what he's doing
He's talking at like an ultra decibel level. Okay. We have stay back. Let's welcome stay back. Yeah. Always a pleasure. Hello
Hello, hello, hello, hello, did the real J. How are we going to be bombed? Oh, it's real
Hey, where's summer when you need her summer is a summer's in the bushes. I think he's in a Power Ranger costume
She has a plaza right page
Page had enough of this of this shit on this page pages pages pages left
Not not not great. I'm with a smile. It's just
With a mad look on her face, and I don't like that. I wanted to be happy
Yeah, you turn I turned down. Oh, who's down there? I turned Alex down already. Oh, no Alice is not here
Who turned her down? I say page in the chat
Hi page
Okay, see page is a ball page is watching she's in the bushes of summer age
they
You're the really good at the making those those
Sculptures those that lawn sculptures J1. Why is your camera on and why are you showing a leg?
J1
J-1, I just saw your third leg and it was
Disappointed
Yeah, we have a page. I think I think the I think the evil people got bored
Okay, I think I'm gonna drop down and I think I'm gonna love you Christine. Thank you
Have a good night. You're a great friend. Love you
Love me. It's it's you know midnight. I always try to get to bed right on midnight
That's why I like it.
Don't turn it so pumpkin, though.
That's right.
Don't lose your glass to you or maybe a prince will come looking for you.
Okay, bye. I love you.
Oh, God. That's fucking funny.
Wait, I want to see you.
How have you been, psyche?
I've been pretty good.
I think Hannah, oh, hold on.
I don't want to talk about other people in the chat.
You know how sometimes guys are...
Guys are ugly hats where they have some charisma or some symmetry to their face not
Spanking Hawk
Who's breaking up? Oh, it's been a spank. I think they're talking about spanky
That's not spanky. Hold on. Here's Allison. I was in your behavior
I sell a wow you as soon as you said a psyche band midnight Christine went crazy. Why?
Okay, because it's either her
or
She's midnight or it's summer or someone close to them
This is what I do. I soon as you said bad midnight
Christian summer okay, they're making
Oh my gosh
They want to take over your channel
It's too many allegations me too. I need to think about this a little bit. Okay guys. Okay. It's like you say skibbity
I appreciate your comment. Thank you. There was like one if it's like one character. It was like no one's gonna be
You know having like a bunch of costume changes. It's gonna be one character like it'll have one another character
Maybe maybe two up there like I'm really big celebrity not usually more than that unless they kill off the whole
Okay, I don't know. It's kind of complicated, but I just
It's just that he seems like a
Ziggy with the other the ziliets from the other way around. I don't know. Is that right? Hold on. Hold on
I think I was in every loss Alexander. Oh, well
Where are you Alex?
Here bro, I'm just gonna shut up. It's anything I say. Are you going the green room?
I thought we were we're doing a line of cocaine
I heard why don't you just give me a script to read so I don't say the wrong thing and so
That's how it seems up here. I don't read your script. I get kicked
I can't speak my mind. I don't can't speak my opinions. I can't say shit
So give me a script
Okay, Alex I send the script to your agent every morning. I said it's your agent, okay, and they prove it and then you read it
Okay, I don't know shit. I don't
He's party part of the he's part of the main cast on the green on who's this?
Yeah, I'm back. Okay, okay
Yeah, okay, thank God
White Rambo yes, you're right Rambo
It's Rondo man
That's Oliver Gibroni's picture though, why are you using Oliver's picture?
Oliver Gibroni his picture
No, the other no other ones. Yeah, that's my brother. Oh, I'm actually like albino, but I'm African you're albino
Yeah, I'm I'll buy I'm an albino african america you're black albino so you're you're in other words
You're to your white person full screen full screen show the full talk like a black
I don't want to find out it's gonna. I don't want to well that's because my voice
It looks like a child and I don't
I don't I don't I don't want to put some like you know, what?
I wish my skin meshed.
Spanky, do you take your girlfriend to another cat and spend time with her?
Hey, look at her.
The shrub light is good.
Wow, I know, guys.
I feel like I'm on a studio.
Why are you shrubbing out, dude?
It's the mini shit disco ball, bro.
Look at this thing, right?
So you can see what it, like it's literally just two sides
and it just screws in your light bulb.
Tits yeah, and it was like five dollars because I got it on clearance because I'm what about the real disco ball
Did you not want to get the real one that do you need like you know like in the 70s?
I mean to be fair. I wouldn't have bought that if it wasn't so cheap
Cheap fuck so did this disco balls are like already broken though because they aren't like
You can find them on they you can find them on eBay like the real ones
I went through a phase for about a day and I thought I was gonna get one, but I didn't
It feels just like I'm walking on shattered land.
Wow, I was like really unattractive
with the light on my face like that.
Wow, my skin is not like that.
It's gonna be a big phase, I say,
until next stream and there's now a fucking disco ball
reflecting the bullshit.
God damn it.
Okay, well.
Stop giving me ideas, guys.
It's a disco ball.
Don't, don't, don't shipper us, it's just a ball.
Okay, so, hey, hey, Iron Vader,
with the spanky spunky and Hannah,
like to make love in chat rooms.
Make love, it's funky in hand, make love to who?
No one's making love in my chat.
Are you getting sex?
Guys, if you have sex, you cannot do it on the page.
You have to be in the back and backstage.
Ruthie has no gut here.
Who, I don't see them.
I don't see them either.
I don't even see my own mod.
I don't know, maybe they're talking.
Is it Casper the Ghost?
I don't see me as a mod either.
Well, no, you're not a mod.
I wasn't a mod.
Oh, you were.
Yeah, you were.
I
Everybody and you know, it's okay. It's okay. It's anything personal. It's anything personal. It's like I still love you psyche
Okay, you can probably you can probably get back someday. You just have to you know, just uh
I'm not going to California to earn it. Yeah. Yes. Yes. You have to move it
You have to share my bed for just a month. I'll give you a membership smile
My gosh guys look how scary I look with this light. I look so bad with the light. Why I can see oh my eyes are burning here
I'll put up with a wise wise random. See look it makes my eye my skin looks like all this color
But it looks good like that, right? It's all perfect
You should have the same background as I was there.
Tell your head up a little bit.
I should.
I'll tell you what I should and shouldn't do.
The sheds are for shitters, and I'm a...
Well, you're shining the light.
Just tell your head back a little bit.
I'm a doer.
Alright, alright run with me. It's it's it's the queer witch project. Oh, come on. Okay. It was good. Hey
Hey, I didn't say I say I say I say I don't know guys. I know I'm gonna put something in this chat right here
Hold on. Let me see anything. I
There's an icon just for you. I have for you. Hold on for me here. Yeah, look at look at this one right now
I'm looking tomato
Yep
But a bunch of them
Oh, I didn't hear anybody
He's an angry elf. He's an angry elf. That is that is a bad that is a band for tonight. I like to not supposed to stay
Anything anything similar to I think you tried some of my brother's um
What's it called that cocaine with the
You do the pink the pink cocaine or the
Yes
For it's got a name for it's called it's called it's called it's called bullet it's called bullet cane
It's called bullet cane, and it's called Bam Bam or something Bam Bam. Oh, yeah
Well, what the fuck man?
Yeah
Let them have it Alex can enjoy that shit
Well, I'm sure he will. Okay.
Nasty. Oh, hold on.
Uh, Alex, the guy, Angry Ninja, okay.
Vicky's here. It says, um, Rusty has me blocked. Rusty, are you blocked? Rusty can't block.
What's not blocked? Maybe Rusty just blocks you on her own.
Let's go blocked and chat, by the way.
Oh.
Unblock there.
I don't know. I don't know if I want you back to tell you.
Oh, come on. I hate it.
I know. I have to go over to the YouTube studio, go in the back.
I have to go find your name.
I'm clicking.
All right.
I'm trying to.
I don't want to go out.
It's a whole process at least a minute.
Let me apologize.
I'm sorry I tried to steal Page and make a separate stream.
Love you. No, no, no, no. Please. Please. I think that was these two. Please do. No, no, I want you to I wanted you to but
Yeah, I know I know I know I know you were just it was the same it's like you just say
Oh page page. I mean fall you to the end there now. Oh fuck sake. You know, you know, it was kind of like, you know
Throw the fuck psyche in my mouth that that was well, that's what you were thinking you were thinking that that was
No, no, no, okay. I just wanted Paige
I wanted to talk to Paige and summer and I forgot the other chick were
Ranting about the the tranny check page page has a new page has a new hotline. It's one nine hundred per page
It is good nine and a minute and then you know and then everyone everyone's happy, right?
Nobody likes Hannah or oh come on. Why did you stop it everyone likes them? Okay time does rain
Okay, guys, I can't read the comments anymore guys every comment is bad stop it
Stop it. Oh, okay. Yeah, every comments back. I can't read anything guys
This is a everyone fight for page pan. I know. Oh my gosh. We got let's get mr. Big Pipe's back here
Mr.. Big Pipe's and and Chris K. Oh my god. We can have like a wrestling. We have whole wrestling matches
Patience be like the Helen of Troy. Well, let's keep her. I'll keep her kind of a sequester time asked about an update about my bartender from
Which is really ironic because I got it tonight if that's okay
What was your update tell me tell us the update we're all we're all expense. It's super fucking terrible and depressing and they're gonna eat it up like candy
So we went out last weekend to Friday last week
And well definitely saw some you know
She showed me some things and you know it's touching me and grabbed my hand and whatever and blah blah blah and then she calls me tonight
She's like, oh, where you at?
I'm actually going to go out and grab a drink.
OK, yeah, I'll come grab a drink with you.
OK, cool.
We drink whatever the fuck, right?
And somebody, it's made in, I don't know, whatever,
mentioned earlier.
Like, oh, I'm going to this fucking 45, 50 minute away
city from where we're at.
I'm like.
Are you going back there again because you were there like two weeks ago? I'm like all right
I kind of think I know what's going on
Somebody made a joke is relieving a bar and she's like yeah
He found a girlfriend and then they looked and they're like oh you finally said yes, and then she looks at me like
Fuck and then looks at them and she's like yeah
He asked like a thousand times, so I finally said yes to him like oh shit, so he's got a boyfriend now
For some reason I'm still around because it's not like a new thing
but uh well it sounds like you've been friend zoned are you friend zoned or no but but i've seen
action so it's weird so i'm a i'm a side piece yeah for the first time in my life yeah you're
you're you're maybe you're a side you you're a side bitch but you know what
um so obviously don't do that i don't know um just uh hold on it's i think it's your
Hello, yeah, it's yours. Yeah. No, I mean yeah
Hello
No, I did it
Hello, did it all even now
Here an echo echo. Hey, yeah, but I can't do I can't do
Wasn't me
It is not this guy oh
Shit did oh he ended it really did again
i don't even know
why am i on page's channel
there we go
oh no, okay, no, we're still alive
yeah, i'm not the echoer
There's too much reading
Rondo is it just us? Let's see you're muted
Do you say am I here? Yeah, you're here. I hear you. I know where psyche what the other psyche was the echo
The knockoff psyche. I apologize. I don't want to I don't want to leave you hanging dude
I was in the gas station getting some mom some nutter butters or whatever you will call
Yeah, man
That sounds yummy. Yeah, I was getting a nutter butters
Dude, I I haven't had one of them's any of them fucking bullshit snacks in many years and
Yeah, no, no you mentioned it now. I'm thinking about it, man. Fuck not tonight. I'm not I'm drunk. I'm not gonna drive
What do you go for healthy? Yeah, you've gone health not on me. What would you do? No?
I just usually don't go for sweets, but I mean I did have an eighth of a crumble cookie today, but
you know
Sweets are in my bag. Hey, I do I eat healthy absolutely not I'm fat and I douse crab legs and butter at least you know
a couple times a month
Well, you think that's you said crab legs and butters on healthy
The crab legs themselves aren't unhealthy, but the butter disgusting amount of butter that I doubt cinnamon is that's the unhealthy part
Can't be perfect exactly. Oh, dude, I mean, I'm not you know the rest of my diet
Uh, it's not the greatest, you know, there's a lot of Taco Bell involved because, you know, I'm a lazy piece of shit a lot
I don't like cooking my own meals
You're on the road frequently, uh, I do drive around all day. I'm a landscaper
I don't eat during the day though
It's when I get home at night and I'm too lazy to cook a meal. So I just door-dash or Uber
I'm running off of I had a wingstop the last two nights
Some fucking subplaced last couple days and I don't even know what the fuck else Taco Bell a couple times
Shit, I don't even know what what other bullshit. I fucking ordered this week. Oh my god
You know, I think I'm gonna do I think yeah, I do all that stuff
Do you said do like always fast foods that you're in there or whatever? I think I'm just gonna start cooking steak
I like that's it. Just stay
Dude, I I don't know why I stopped doing my own grocery shop like I mean even though it was it was always steak
I'm getting you know
but
Like yeah, it's steak and they'd make asparagus and you know
Maybe some sort of fucking potato or rice with it
Yeah, and I got lazy and for the last minute. I've been fucking
Not cooking not even you know my shopping consisted of picking up meat bags of rice
Bags and fucking literally what I just said and
Maybe some other mixed in you know broccoli your cauliflower here and there. I don't know why I stopped. I don't know
It's like
Yeah, I need to go back to that. I was fucking bomb. I don't want to do a carnivore diet. I like pasta too much
Way too fucking much fucking ramen noodles. I can't give that shit up
but
You know
Going back to at least making it myself
Yeah, that's best to stick with those complex carbs, right?
The comp oh, yeah, yeah, then the simple wait not or yeah, is that the right way?
I know it's like the red potatoes and I said you said the white the rights
Yeah, like I don't really fuck with bread ever like, you know white bread wheat bread's terrible for you
But isn't really I thought I thought wheat bro was good. We all know grain bread's good for you whole grain and wheat bread
I'm not sure about the whole grain for specifically wheat bread though is not
Not good
whole grain I'm pretty sure is pretty much on the same level because it's like
the white bread is like a filtered out version and how American bread is it's
you know I mean most other countries don't consider what we call our bread to
be like food great food like so yeah it's just not yeah for instance subway
For the UK, I know specifically, Subway, the United States version of Subway, is not approved
by their food administration.
So it's fucked up.
Yeah, so our bread recipe.
Here is disgusted. It's just all sugar. That's the problem. And then we have sugar and ours is all processed and then
What the fuck is that, you know, dramatically modified fucking
crop
Yeah, I was under the impression that bread was like a really really ancient type of food for
Okay, we fucked it all up you say. Yeah, we you know, the United States fucked it up for profit
So, profits over health shit, right? Like, why the rest of the world makes one of us for being fat, even though they eat the same amount of shit.
Uh, I mean, well, let me rephrase that.
A lot of parts of the world consume the same amount of shit that we do, right?
You know, even eat the same calorie level of intake for shit, but Americans are always fatter.
The reason is because our processing of it is so hefty and sugar on the back end and fake shit
That's like that's the difference in there
So, you know a French person will eat an entire fucking two-foot-long baguette in the day
And that's just straight bread carbs and still be skinny as fuck you do that here. I mean, that's a good friend
You're a diabetes risk, you know
That's fucked up
That's it's all because of our bullshit. That's all because they want to make some moneys, but yeah, yeah, no
I agree it is bullshit. I
Wish you could be healthy. I mean we can be healthy. I don't understand, you know
like
Like think about it because there's everywhere you go. It's impossible not to eat this stuff. It's it's everywhere. Oh, oh, yeah
Oh, dude trying to shop right you fuck, you know, I shop at Whole Foods great
You pay triple the price for the same fucking shit quality product
It says organic on there. Uh, you know some probably are not lying
but I you know
Most companies are definitely lying
but able to get away with it because it's like oh well um this one part of pasteurization we
keep out so we can say it's organic but it's still just see what you're saying slightly less
shitty slightly yeah and it sucks too because they all say all right you know like meat shortage
driving up the prices and shit and like there's all these shortages
From like, you know the farmers pretty much that you know blame the farmers
But you look on the other side and it's like all right, well
Hey, they're adding the extra processes to actually, you know to stretch out all the product that the farmers are making unnecessarily
But also be the farmers are getting paid
Subsidies to throw good
Fucked with product away
It's like it's fucking terrible
So like the eggs the egg price skyrocketing right?
Farmers heard about that far more getting paid to dump eggs. They have dumping pits
That are disgusting
but also
They're just dumping pits because the farmers are getting paid more from the government than they would be getting paid to sell the eggs
to create a
Like false fake shortage
We produce plenty right plenty of shit to feed the country
Yeah
Everything's still super expensive and the price has got driven up
Why it's not like COVID affected the fucking chickens or the farmers
Realistically there was over fucking production, right?
So theoretically, alright overproduction somehow somehow because it's not like people change their fucking eating habits
But either way somehow now there's overproduction because of COVID so they're throwing shit away
Now we're back to normal place and there's underproduction even though we have the same amount of farmers farmland and nothing has changed in that route, right?
How does that make fucking sense?
What if Bill Gates bought all the land off the farmland is that what do you think?
He has there's a chart out there that shows all the farmland that Bill Gates owns
What's real interesting is when you look at these chemical incidences where there's chemical factories or a
train tipped like so for instance Palestine, Ohio
That's my neck of the well and not quite my neck of the woods for Ohio, but
I'm an Ohioan. I know all about Palestine, Ohio, and this train crash, right? Cool.
Whatever trained derailment
it was in a very highly populated old Amish, you know, old Amish area, so
there was a city where
normal every day, just say white people lived and surrounded by Amish farmland that was completely affected and
Well, guess what foundation swooped in and bought all that property that was affected by this chemical spill from this train crack trained around
That's not good see where it's going
There was so North Carolina's another one all the crazy flooding for the mountains of North Carolina
Yeah, the mountains of North Carolina getting flooded. Yeah, all right
Well, that's the natural copper and lithium deposits in the United States
Guess what foundation bought out all that property after the fucking hurricane. Oh shit. Yep
That's all goes. I do it's an easy fucking chart, right?
So it's like all right, you know, you look at it
What foundation?
Who's the owner of beyond meat the vegan fake meat company
What company who owns that?
I'll give you a guess. I don't think you need it
I've never liked Bill Gates. I always think he was a really really creepy individual. I never liked him
I don't like him. He's a piece of shit. He's a piece of fucking shit
He owns though the Gates Foundation in subsidiaries
Probably directly to the Gates Foundation owns the most farmland in the United States
think China is literally the second most the second leading you know say
organization for farmland ownership in the United States right which says
something and China led to a rise in pork prices years ago because they were
exporting so much fucking pork it actually had an effect on the US economy
because they own so much fucking farmland but a that's just pork be though
Gates trying to push his beyond meats bullshit on people. Well, okay, I don't want you to eat eggs
I want you fake eggs because it's cheaper to produce that crop that Monsanto's making those fake ass seeds, right?
You're genetically modified bullshit, and that's how we're making our fake meats
Soy beans all that bullshit, right?
Yeah, it's all for profits on the Gates side
It's all super unhealthy. Soy is not supposed to be a regular like a main staple in the diet, right?
You know Asian people don't eat tofu all the time, right because that's mainly a soy bean, you know, whatever the fuck, right?
They might have it daily and then there's soy sauce, but I mean that's kind of a stretch that's so far
You're not you're not drinking glasses of fucking soy sauce. Yeah, right and South Park on a man, right?
phenomenal episode of South Park and
They're all eating gluten and soy gluten and their dicks are shooting off. Oh
Fucking hilarious episode. Well, think about the skyrocketing and gluten allergies, right?
Going hand-in-hand with all these fake fucking products on the market to replace real natural products regardless of what it is
They're replacing just
over saturating it with soy and the fucking processed wheats, right?
We can eat
You know like wheat is okay to eat, but it's still supposed to be a moderation even just the regular wheat shit like bread
You know bread is unhealthy for you in general anyway. It's not a healthy item
You shouldn't eat, you know, I won't say you shouldn't eat a sandwich a day, you know
But you shouldn't have multiple sandwiches a day and you know that many pieces of bread
Toasted breakfast for your simple carb
But that's also considering it's not the American processed shit bread
So I don't know sorry
spewing
Food nonsense. No, it's everything. It's everywhere. Yeah. Yeah, and so it's all we
Other country, but this country. Yes, it's everywhere. You can't fucking
Unless you live next to the farmer or you are the farmer or you're in that small town. That's not worth, you know investing a
Whole McDonald's and Starbucks franchise into you
You get the real food
Assumptively
You're getting the shit that's straight from the dude down the street that just raised it
And fuck it's probably cheaper than the prices. We're paying for our process crap
Versus, yeah, but we just got to eat shit
The other shit part is though is like, okay
Again you as the consumer like if I were to try to go to the grocery store and find
I'm I'm trying actively, you know to find the healthy shit the unsupert, you know avoid the unprocessed shit and buy it
in an expensive store or a chief store, it's like
Damn, you're fucking impossible when you start reading these fucking labels. Well, when you think about it, what is there really?
What's what's our offer so you go to the grocery store? You want to get something actually sustainable?
What are you getting like you take away all the bullshit? What are you left with?
eggs
The fucking steak a steak good luck with the eggs that aren't pasteurized
I'm not going that deep in it. I'm just saying overall. Let's talk about like eggs a steak and a fucking what else all right?
Well, what else?
Nope, maybe no. Well, all right
Just the flip to that is though a lot of the grocery store change shit, right? What are they feeding those animals that?
Produce in let produce that right?
So but either way you're right. That's another step looking too deep, but yeah, that's that's literally about it
Working it I worked at Myers for I was only like a year about a year ago
and I was trying to
specifically find healthy shit and
The one item
One company it's called Cousins and it's a rice company. They were out of I got I don't know
30 plus different rice brands, you know rice and Rooney uncle Benz all that bullshit
30 different brands not just flavors brands
They were the one that don't used enriched didn't use enriched wheat in their product and that's the really that's the bad shit is the
enriched wheat
Oh, I see that word. Yeah, I never know what it really means, though
Enriched means they add a bunch of shit to it. Oh, yeah, right. It was like vitamins vitamins minerals
quote-unquote vitamins, but it's not it is shit the body can't process like our body can't process what they're enriching it with
So it's not just enriched with vitamins, but it's also shelf. What are those the things that make shelf longer shelf of the
Preservatives and other shit to keep it stable for longer or what not even stable for longer just keep the product
I don't know
Usable whatever the fuck money money money money money exactly. That's it one
One rice company from over 30 options and other options claim organic
Unprocessed blah blah blah and then you flip it over and it says enriched wheat on the product for their rice and it's like dude
No, you can't call yourself organic or healthy using an enriched wheat
That is one of the worst things for people to consume
Our body cannot break that shit down
But hey here we are
But it's better than going to Wendy's though, right? It's better when it's not at all not
I mean the only the only argument there is grease
That's that's the difference is grease
You want to make I mean, you know
Realistically depending size for size on what you're fucking eating. Yeah, there'll be an argument of healthy there
But if you're just saying Wendy's french fries versus I don't know
Like when my friends, I don't know some frozen french fry brand or whatever the fuck. Oh, it's the same. It's all the same and rich shit
It's equally unhealthy
It's that maybe you air fry your shit at home so you don't get all the fat from the fryer grease from Wendy's
That's that would be the only fucking difference
But the actual item you're eating is equally as unhealthy all the same stuff. Yeah
What about what about chlorinated chicken and steroid fed beef
That's where we weren't getting that deep into
Yeah, I can't get past that. I mean, that's what I got here, you know, that's where we that's where we kind of stop
But yeah, you want to talk about yes, steroid injections water injections to make fucking chicken breasts look fucking thicker and meatier and
Blah blah blah and wings, but then also what the fuck they're feeding them as far as you know, Monsanto produced
genetically modified. So, chlorinated chicken, chlorinated, in other words, washing rancid
chicken with chlorine, and then feeding all your beef, all your cattle with steroids.
Yeah, fuck.
Yep, uh dude exactly
You know
That I didn't well we were kind of avoiding that deepness a little earlier, but you said it
So go for it go for it. It's completely true and the shit that they feed the beef. That's not just the steroids again
Corn crop right corn is obscenely in health. I mean a people can't process corn
You know, that's why you shit out corn after you eat corn on a cob
But it's all genetically modified now
from, again, Monsanto, and that feed goes straight into the chicken, goes straight into the chicken feed,
pig feed, everything, we fucking... Sorry, I sort of put the ball through a few pins there,
you might have heard it, but I'm asking you the main pin, why you've heard fed corn syrup in
Why why why because it's cheap and it's an easy sweetener
And I I don't I mean, I don't understand they well they created a sugar addiction in the United States
That's why everything is so sugar sugar sugar
Here's a question. So many somebody moved from Europe coming to the United States. Do you think that they're?
Do you think that they're like their diet gets a lot worse and their mental health changes potentially? Yes
Yes, well
foreigners eating our food. I thought you were asking me. I apologize. Sorry. Sorry. I thought
you were asking me because I'm from Europe. You know what I mean? I am the vanguard.
Did you move to the United States, sir? No, but I have visited it. Did you get sick
eating some of the food while you were here? No, I was only there for a fucking couple of weeks,
so you know what I mean?
Yeah, well, I mean not the long term but our sugar usage is so dramatically. Where are you from?
I'm from Asgard. Do you know where Asgard is?
Okay
Tell Thor I said hi
No, I don't know
What what country?
Pardon me. What country?
Which country how many countries are in the United Kingdom?
There's many
All right, fair enough fair enough. Well, I mean you got you got us you're in the UK
Scotland Ireland England
Wales Wales is a country, right? Yeah
Mmm, I know there's I'm pretty sure there's at least one more I'm missing. I
Don't know
Scotland England in Wales you got it right. Oh, I was right. Okay. I thought there is one. Well, I guess the distinction with Northern Ireland, but
Either way, all right. Hey, there we go. So
Yes, so well, all right, so you're from UK
Although it's not technically a continent, which is I don't know
One of the oldest countries is what made your country
What made my country is older than you have ever breathed
I know I didn't say country I said continent and then you go into a country breakdown
Which the UK is and then you've got other countries and
you know let's see either way either way so that being said though you stop
making me dizzy and walking around in circles you almost look like you're it
almost looks like you're a turkey farm
Come on a turkey farm
Yeah, man, you keep walking around in circles. It's making me dizzy, man. If I start gobbling will that make it better?
All right, all right, so but either way though so in your travel so you didn't get sick from here
I'm just saying the sugar difference, you know from the UK and the whole
And process sugar like fucking our corn syrup
Shit didn't make you sick in this day
Look how many products that are banned from the US, but we're still important.
But anyway, corn syrup is one of them, all your e-fucking numbers in stupid numbers
and other factors of colorants, we're not allowed, because we're fucking, what? Sensible.
I agree.
It's stupid.
we're full of fucking idiots that just look for what can fit in their fucking mouth and that's
gets what gets the job done and nobody wants to ask a fucking question
don't worry i'm so i hear idea can i ask you a correct question
do you claim to be viking or what no not at all
I understand my haircut says different, but that's not why I have this haircut
Yeah, man, but anyway folks food colorings
chlorinated chicken and steroid in beef
Everything that's wrong. Why do you think the UK and European Union says no to American products?
They have a sense they have sense
They don't have
Food there is not based off of profit. It's based off of I mean
Health for the population for the most part for the most part
well
Thank you for saying that you're quite correct because it is a profit margin and it is profit
But we don't go down the road you go down
Show me see that not at all you guys outlawed like so we openly use Monsanto Monsanto is the biggest genetically modified crop company in the world and
The United States openly lets them do whatever the fuck they want to with corn soy beans, whatever gets grown in the ground
But it's damn near banned and I mean fucking when Africa the Middle East
Bans your fucking product from being there, you know, it's a problem
Well, when when a company like Monsanto makes a one-life seed and they make sure of that
That's the problem
In other words, you have to keep buying seeds
You cannot get free seed from a said product, which has always been the case within nature
If you create corn you have seed if you create any other plant you have seed
Mm-hmm, but there's no reason there's no reuse factor. I get it. You're not gonna get you know
Any more seed from their corn product versus a natural corn product again the genetic modifications involved with their product
They're modifying it
It's not just like you
Know people breed, you know, I don't know weird-ass pairs in you know, Japan and you know, but they're not
Chemic or lab genetically modified. It's just from breeding
This the point I'm trying to make is Monsanto makes the point
you can't have any other seed unless you buy it from us it will be protected from this it will
be protected from that but it's not the correct seed and you will never get any other seed
from said plant which you get from every other plant every other vegetable they produce seeds
They've secured their profits, and the United States government backs it by...
putting a lot of regulation into buying non-Monsanto seeds and extra tariff or
well I don't know if they're quite tariffs but extra at least taxes or
costs to buy from other seed companies that aren't Monsanto. Yeah but they're
making you buy genetically modified apparently it will grow here it'll buy
anything they'll do anything and you will have a product of crop but one thing
It's seed to be viable
Yeah, and therefore you got to go buy another round of seed the next harvest or well the next you know planting
And then you got to continue to buy you again. Like you said, yes, there's no reuse. You're not getting any seed back
You're not you have to continuously buy and continuously fund on Santos one you seeds
I like you as the I like you
Thank you, which I didn't even sell vanguard. It's been a pleasure. I
Understand the but I don't want to say Americans are dumb in the stereotype
But I mean we earn it
Why isn't why don't we have an outrage of the bullshit? I mean, yeah, I'm feeding into it
Of course I'm buying it, but I really don't have a fucking option because I ain't a farmer
I don't have the means to grow my own shit. Yeah, we got to eat this way
Yeah, and I mean to be fair though if you the American that hasn't thought about or doesn't care to think about it or you know
Yeah, we're just hungry. We're just hungry
Then there's one thing being poor and being hungry is you're just hungry. Why is there so many fat bastards in your country?
I fruit I fruit toast corn syrup we can have poor fat people because of Pepsi
Coke McDonald's
You can eat, you know five burgers a month and drink five fucking drinks with those burgers and still be a fat piece of shit
Not eat the entire other fucking 26 days 20. Yeah, 26 days
25 days in a month
Right, it's it's the it's the sugars pumped in to our fucking food. That's what makes us fat, right?
Corn syrup is a cunt.
It's in everything. You look at, like, going back to bread.
Why the fuck do you, why is corn syrup in fucking bread?
You know, not every bread, but a lot of bread has corn syrup in it.
Why? Corn syrup in fucking vegetable oils.
Like, what the fuck, like...
You know
Vegetable oils corn syrup is what corn corn is a carbohydrate
Why would you have it in vegetable oils?
Let me make the theoretical statement there corn is a little sweet, right?
But corn doesn't make syrup
like you squeeze corn out it's just I mean maybe maybe you squeeze so much
yeah but corns are carbohydrate most vegetables aren't it corn still does have a sugar slight a
sugar content in there because it's a carbohydrate but you'd have to squeeze so much corn liquid
and liquefy so much corn to be able to call that syrup I'm just saying it's just a fake
again just another modified fake product corn syrup well that makes it sound
better i'm sorry i'm sorry i haven't been facetious but i'm european i do not apologize
you're fine no be you we're you know
Look look if that's one thing we can appreciate here. That's well, I mean unfortunately starting to get reigned in a bit
It's freedom of speech, so be you and say what you want
Well, thank you likewise sir cheers if you're drinking if not all my school school school
Salute or well actually no, ah fuck I forgot what the Irish
My grandma would be upset
But do you know much about the technical Viking?
No, I did not
Well, I am very much a Viking scotch
The ha see there we go, but all right. I'm willing to listen you said what was the Viking tech?
What was it you said tech what Viking?
What you never heard of the techno Viking? No
Is there just gonna be a bunch of Vikings in a disco just
You see an original Viking right in Berlin in the in 90s, right?
90s, when a fucking cunt comes up to a woman and goes fuck you, you cunt, look what happens.
Look what happens.
I'm looking I I didn't leave it just goes black as well. I'm looking okay. I don't want a video
I just want to see a description. Oh, okay. I know I think it's an internet phenomenon and meme
All right, okay. No, I've never heard it
original techno Viking
original
Techno Viking original
Yeah, I see a 2000s meme is what it says, but then yeah, it says a 2000s meme from Germany. That's all that's popping up
Well go watch the meme if it's a meme. Yeah to leave you to go beyond the meme
I just it looks what the fuck am I watching I just yeah
All right. Yeah
Yeah, you're gonna watch it. You're gonna watch it. You need more of an attention span to see what's going on your room
Yeah, no, no, no, you're for oh god. I got we got it's all that corn syrup. We're adjusting. Yeah, I
Don't fuck with too much shit with corn syrup. Thankfully I drink pop
I don't I don't I gave that
I try to stay away from pop caffeine, uh, the beer I drink actually, you know, I never checked that out
But I don't believe there's any foreign syrup in course
You're you're you're both too blind to see what I told you the techno Viking if you're not willing to watch what the techno Viking stands for
Don't that's well, I don't want to watch it right now because it's gonna take me out
Yeah, can we get an explanation with a techno viking to look it up more in-depth when we're not in chat
But as soon as I switch over to something I you know, I stopped my screen and yeah, what's techno viking?
Internet
It's the maim you're you we're doing maims. I don't know it's an act. It's an act
You know what an in act means
Mmm, not in your definition now
An act means something I'm assuming different my apologies. I don't mean to offend you is because fourth of the July is coming up
Independence from what?
Ha ha ha independence from t taxes
Yeah, fuck that team
Book bitch. Well, no, I love tea. I like tea more than coffee. I don't know how I like ice tea with high fructose corn syrup
Yeah, southern sweet tea southern sweet tea, man
But but all right
Fuck it. It's all dumb. It's all conquered nations and tribes and independence that's taken back and given and other nations
I mean, I love 4th of July. Don't get me wrong. But yeah, man. You got some firework
But independence from what?
Well, it was independence from, at least for our history, the over-arching rule, or over-bearing
rule of the English government on the settlers of the American nations, an over-taxation
I don't know, over-regulation, I guess, or over-policing, I guess that's a good way to say it.
No taxation without representation.
Yeah, the fundamental argument of the Tea Party, yes.
Can you also put something towards you, which is coming up in October or November?
your thanksgiving there
when was the last time you give thanks to Native American?
bro, what the fuck are you guys talking about?
fucking Vikings
when was the last time you give thanks?
What are you going to kick me because I said
Last time we gave thanks, I mean well, I mean, yeah
Thanksgiving just became about eating a fucking turkey and not about
The Indians and the white people hanging out together. Yeah, stuff. Yeah, I mean having a quote-unquote, you know
Free slash packs that I mean absolutely got fucking obliterated
But I mean again though it like I said it goes back to the age old tale in every country every nation
A tribe conquering another tribe nation getting freedom nations freedom rescinded blah blah blah blah blah
It's it's just the same fucking telltale of concrete never mind this never mind this fucking jewish fucking zionist russian wannabe
But the vikings got to north america
long before
fucking colombo
The history books
They did
The Vikings absolutely made it to North America first. Well, I won't say first, but at least for history books
They they definitely made it before. Yeah, long before
Colombo
Which is at leave Eric's at leave Erickson
We all look at the English as being the first and it's like no Columbus was a fucking Spaniard
But here with association with the English just because of well again, you know, I thought he was an Italian
no he was Spanish
yes he was a Portuguese
what?
Portuguese, there you go, Portuguese
no, Colombo was an Italian man
no, Colombo was Portuguese
but I mean, reference to Spanish
but say, I don't know, same fucking thing
anyway, can we just finish
the Vikings, the Vikings got to North America
long before Plymouth Rock
shall we just say it
that's bullshit
you got no proof on that uh there's actually a ton of Viking proof of being uh viking uh what is that
i've got plenty of proof on that i've got plenty of proof bro winners write history so i mean
you're not wrong you're not wrong but that doesn't make history right so those vikings weren't
So, Zinpulps, Zinpulps, you're a bit of a dickhead, but anyway, how are you doing?
How are you going to be going about the 4th of July?
All I'm saying to you is, the Vikings got to America before.
All these and all I'm saying is you got no proof to stand on
Which roots do you have to stand on
Don't worry about my roots. I'm from the earth
I
Just funny that you talking about America, and you're not even from America, bro
I mean, but I know quite a lot about your country
I
Know a lot about you
To be fair, a lot of other nations know better world history than most people in the United States
Especially the American stupid bro, what a traitor
Uh, yeah, somewhat, yeah
Oh dude, I love America, I didn't say the people
I'm gonna allow to do
Am I not allowed to have a joke?
Am I not allowed to have a joke with my American brothers and sisters?
uh-huh no we don't claim you nigger no they they it's it's got to be a fence
first in an up in arms people don't have you know you make fun of the us nobody
can have a sense of humor about it
hell no that's why we're number one because we don't fuck around
in what other than our military that's right well uh and i mean
America number one, America.
Just ask I ran about it.
Ask I ran about it.
America.
Fuck yeah.
What the fuck?
I mean.
that
That's not no, no, no, sir America dog
That's really gay actually
You mill model that gay, I mean
The mr. America
Being a patriot is gay. No, it's a lot of bunch of gay dudes
Being a patriot is gay now damn. I'm sorry for you. No, but
be a Mr. America's kind of gay
It's a little gay
I'm not my country dog, sorry you don't
You don't really determine which state you heal from
I'm gonna tell you she is. She doesn't want to dox himself. I know you don't
You're not willing to tell me which state you heal from I know which
He's from the projects, bro
the
That's why I said my skin beforehand you got the you got a little bit of the twang, but
Dang
Being from the city that's called being cultured, bro. That is not being from
Melting
Serious question
Do you do a Crip Walk or a Blood Walk?
Oh, wow.
I do neither.
I was going to say I'm a Latin king.
So I was going to. Oh, never mind.
I was going to say he was cultured, but, you know, he ruined that one.
Well, yeah, I love I love I don't do the game.
Good. I'm proud of you, son.
I
Mean we all like look a bit of Snoop doggy
So so oh my god pages in here everybody shut the fuck up hi page
Oh, hello hi, what's up your night?
Welcome back. It was fine. I just worked today. We're close
Hello, Prairie Pitch.
Hello.
Hey.
Stop the fucking eating it.
Sorry.
Sorry to interrupt.
Oh, I thought you were talking to me.
I was like, I see what the fuck.
Yeah, I'm watching you eat right now and I'm telling you to stop.
I'm looking out for use.
I would have been a little bit weirded out.
No, the little asshole puppy over here.
What?
Who's an asshole?
My dog.
Trying to eat the fucking the the I don't know the the house mat
Oh, dear
Fuck that. I know I'm panel with this weirdo
Why rondo is a Tony by the way, that's Tony
I saved the gay dude in his garage, vanguard, I have no clue.
I'm so fucking gay.
Simples, I'm gonna tell you who Simples is in two seconds.
I got him following him.
Alexander McQueen NYPD. Long Island Audits have already put you in your
placement. Long Island Audits, Long Island Audits. Long Island Audits, why are you bringing
him into it? Do I? Don't smack these people on the face, bro. We all want to be Long Island Audits.
And they can't or never will be.
So that's what
Yeah, there's only one
There's only one Michael Jordan. There's only one Derek Jeter. There's only one, you know
Oh swat like there is only one law and order like there's only one person
in that
Yeah
Set the scale the ball really high no one will ever reach it
No, these people ever reached that fucking bar
Are you saying Rudy Giuliani's fucking leaking hair dye will never reach the same
No tears
Giuliani has more money than you and me you probably ever have together, you know, just say
I mean, I mean, I'm just saying I'm just saying he looked like a bitch backing off of the Trump shit. So, you know
I want to see your nipples. I said cuz not cuz I'm gay cuz I want to pinch him
You look like one of those things if I grab one of those nipples boy turn it
that's that man see that's what's funny if you're a ninja you can take out
somebody with um you have to study like the pressure points you know because
we're all different sizes and if right you know if a psyche comes up against
and I say the only thing that might save him is pressure points
tell me about
tell me about the 12 most important pressure points in the Opa Tosso
all right so the throat 100% Adams apple boom because that's where they breathe
you're acting like a lion are you every animal goes after the throat are you including head
in your torso statement are you gonna soak that in stomach because no nature
It's so smart and they're like, how do I kill this thing immediately go after the throw so number one is
Well tour the thumb and if you got the power that my passion has go for the liver
But brother you go for the throw you cannot breathe
Hello, let's not talk about secret
Chinese change the death death death
I
Whatever you guys, we can talk about we can talk about stuff. It's just that they're certain
We'd talk about
Okay, okay, whatever they would never admitted it for sure, okay
Okay, yeah, they admitted it, but it's not true. Okay
So the thing about corn syrup is, yes, you can get a syrup from corn, it's corn as sweet, it has sugar in it.
If you boil down the corn enough, it'll be hundreds of times sweeter than sugar.
So it's way, way, way, way, way cheaper to use.
So that's why we use the cheap corn syrup instead of the cane sugar, which is the, you know, fruit on the plant.
Fair enough, fair enough.
I'm just stating. Well, part of the corn syrup. Oh, thank you. Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you. Corn syrup. Corn syrup is the evil on the world.
Yeah, it is very bad. It is very bad. It burns very fast, right? Because it's like, you know,
I saw a video yesterday that says that fluoride, when you drink fluoride, it like, uh, it capsizes your glenoplank, uh, gland.
It does your fucking brain.
The pineal, the p- the p- pineal, like, calcifies the pineal.
You- you believe in that shit, son?
Your
of the
the
Somebody
Yeah, but yeah, we don't talk too much about guys you can study the pineal gland on your own there's not too much
I can tell you about it except a there's a there's actually a
There's something called if I can't even say the name of it on the on this room
There's a chemical that it
Yeah, we're we're I'm just saying people will use this this chemical it actually is like pure adrenaline, right?
There's some new drill and it actually will make put it makes people homicidal when they take it actually
I won't
Look at there's a little a it's also an a but we can't talk anymore about we can't
You'll find it it's just look up look up look up the pineal gland
Adrenal gland chemical look up look at that
How much does it cost I want some
It's very expensive, and it is not is
They
No, it's not good it may it causes baldness insanity it is it is cannibals and guys, you know, you don't
Not drink the tonight. Thank you. I love you. We're not gonna ride these rails
Don't don't don't ride the rails, man. I'm looking out for you
No last night you were wrong though the night before that you were a hondo it's not
Rondo's in here
Yeah, I'm here. Yeah, he's not talking. Yeah, he's not saying me
This NYP
Decon thinks he's Rudy Giuliani 2.0. What is it?
He's addicted
You know, I got to have one everywhere, you know, fuck
You can't even have a conversation
True
Conversation but not what fake ass was like you when I know you're all wrong though. You're Tony
I don't fuck with you a loser bro
You're paranoid dude
I don't know who you are and what you are
Rondo you're fucking Tony
The guy that took sight down
With all the 15 strikes
When you made that to me
They won't have a real conversation
Not me
Paige you can read my tarot
Why Rondo is that
Esso allied master computer
Tony whatever the fuck he is
That's him
Okay, you can make this all better. I
Can make it all better. Can I ghost? Can I go stay em see you can make it all better?
Not your time to tell the truth. So I
I'll give you a plea deal motherfucker
You want to avoid the death sentence?
You know
I
Prairie page which
Organizing my like like my shit. I write notes on the queen can't even last on the panel
Hey page. Yeah, I see a terror tarot
Hit you with some tarot. Yeah
What like your own you were psych
uh
he went to lurk again
oh i'd like to say hi to him
fuck
yeah unfortunately that was
uh over talk
hi hi
there you are what's up
yeah how are you
i'm good
i got to go golfing tonight at work instead of
working
and i got paid for it
You work at a
We talking about the Gulf that's not really go. What do you call it again?
Okay, my my my nephews do the same thing. There's like a big country golf club here
It's cause it's very expensive to join but you know, they're a
They worked. Oh, here's the Umi. Hold on a second. Hello. Hi, Umi. Hi, Umi.
Umi is a... Your, your, your, your, your, your muted, your muted.
Are you Umi? Inshallah, walk back. Asalaamu alaikum. Let me see. Hold on.
Yeah, yeah
Is that alexander's girlfriend right there
That beautiful brother to go back to golf real quick to go back to golf in the immortal words of robin williams
I
Say are you me sir? I say a little bit say a little you me. Hi you me
Hi, hi
You was amazing
Yeah
Tragic figure just like when I was really young it was more commending. I didn't understand that because I was so young
I was like more commending whatever but as I grew up. I started, you know, Robin Williams shit
And then when I saw fucking a good with haunting
What is that, what is that? What are we looking at? What is that picture home?
You know me yeah, you know me okay, that's fine. That's fine. I thought I was like some kind of
Here's a quick question the white rondo has a question a prairie page. So would you
Say that it's true when a guy says if she smokes she pokes. Is there any truth me man? I've never heard
Yelly out
I don't hear yelling
Smokes and pokes like every day
Alex, come on, dude
And remember where he was at
Alex, oh, he left
Oh, no, he's here
Alex, calm down
Calm down, let's hear this through
Bro, if you smoke, you poke
But our nose hearing seals the deal
you're definitely fucking that shit
I don't see a nose earring anywhere
Alex you didn't hear the brother
zoom in
I saw it today
I'm the guy with nose earring
that bitch wants dick 24
hey yeah
I'm sorry
stop it
alright so Paige there's no truth to that or
Hey, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
What
I'm not sure.
First
Yes, I
Would be a page page page Rob's Indian casinos and no, I don't I'm an Indian. Oh, okay. Okay. That's why you're allowed to rob them
I don't want to I like that. I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding
Oh shit. Oh, wow. Oh, did you guys have fucking heatwaves too? Were you affected with heatwaves? Oh, yep
I just yeah weird rainstores
Pitch can I be cheeky?
You healed from
We tried
My tribe is by Edmonton. I don't know. I'm from Canada. I live in Canada, so I don't know if you'll know where
It's called I know quite a lot of tribes by the way, but the prairie people the prairie people and Pages the Queen
But I'm Korean Blackfoot in French
Korean block. Oh, she's Korean. I know your Korean. That's amazing. That makes so much sense looking at you
Okay page page, okay, I'm just gonna okay
Karaoke if I was Korean and I'm not gonna
Look look I my dad claims black foot too, so I mean
Well, here you go
That's why the Vikings
contact the first nations first
like Mike everybody's you know
everybody go on ancestor you can study your
era your history you're they have more
of the American connections you might
have so if you have any
for this way it's a lot better it's a lot better than fucking Thanksgiving when
the if it's getting is wonderful artisans is wonderful the earth in
america will not survive the winter that's your sister ever
the best dinner ever
Yeah, some shit is not what people think it is. There's a long dark history to the Thanksgiving and my people
Yeah, the serious Thanksgiving is that the turkey is a hybrid of it's a different meaning nowadays that it was
Yes, did it stem off of some very dark shit just like Columbus Day?
Absolutely, which kind of goes hand in hand with Thanksgiving ironically enough, but
Same statement. That's not what it is now anymore. Oh, thanks, Jeff. Stop being a candidate. You too. But
Does anybody know what we're giving thanks for? No, absolutely not a thanksgiving. Thanks for
America and the indians. I'm not on the registry.
We're doing thanks for we're doing thanks for corn. The indians had to cook it. Thank you guys. Yeah. Monsanto corn
The indians didn't make monsanto. Monsanto is a
I don't lie
And also Monsanto has every seed for every plant.
I mean, that's subjective.
Do you find my comments subjective or value?
What's your name again?
Do you want me to mention it?
To make sure you're in the chat
and I mentioned your name.
No, thank you.
What the fuck?
Jeremy?
I don't know who's talking.
Look at him, Jeremy.
Midnight in the chat?
Midnight in the chat at least, huh?
Midnight?
Oh, whoever's being an asshole in the chat.
Well, not an asshole.
It was a very, well, technically, it
was an asshole half a dozen, though.
It's a fair amount of statements.
Like, it's that subjective, though.
Well, no, my chat definitely.
Chat, I'm a registered Métis Indian.
Yes, I am.
I have my car I can show I'm not ever gonna show you my car and stuff because you'll dog. I'm just saying I have it all
Are you asking me about firearms like if I have to fire it like
Okay, so you can hunt whenever you want.
You don't need a tag, but you do need a harvesting license.
But you do have to have it registered.
You have to have your POW.
You have to have your registered gun license
in order to have firearms in your, yes, please.
All right.
Oh, let me clarify, is there a difference in the buying process?
There's the same thing.
I mean, the reservation doesn't equal federation as in the first place.
No, it's different.
It's different, right?
Different laws, especially when there's first, like there's treaty
and then there's Metis, right?
So treaty is full of blood.
Mixed
You go I may T it sounds like a pirate
Yeah, I'm not half-breed I got more than that in me, but yeah
I say it is more black than white.
You would never know.
I don't know.
The black frankly, queenish and Native American.
I mean, I don't know.
Arapu, Kamanchi, Arapu.
What okay
I think people are getting drunk in this
Are people getting drunk right now. I'm getting drunk
It's okay
Okay, that's so you mean where you're in Indonesia you mean you know you was in Indonesia, right?
No, it's like not a harvesting license for harvesting vegetables midnight
It's like for like for hunting for harp like for hunting
No, it's for harvesting squash. Don't lie
It's thanks to the registered years of corn and uh wait wait as a native you get more I guess
tags for registration and more harvest versus uh non-native well okay so non-native non-native
people have to have a win card and they have to they have to enter for draws and there's certain
zones and different seasons certain things yes sorry but like it doesn't apply to me
Yeah
Okay, I was gonna add the caveat it depends which college in fraternity and
Maternity of the female type. I mean, what do you call it in fraternity in fucking? What's all up? Oh shit maternity
Maternity maternity the mother the father right now. I don't think if I think you think about sororities and fraternities though
That's a little bit different. Those are sisters brotherhoods. You think about the father mother
I know
He's not getting the point he was trying to say
fraternities and sororities, but I think he's trying to say maternity and paternity between fraternity and sorority. I'm not sure
I wouldn't have you back on but
So like your mother and your father, right? Yeah, you're family tree your history, right? Yeah. Yeah
Perfect. Now we're all the same. So we're on the same page as college is
What's the shit with all those school and black bones?
They all have them they all have them it's on better known ones, but yeah
And if the non-prostigious ones have one, it's probably the second.
I mean, they all have that. I mean, every, I think every college people which has a fraternity,
sorority, some kind of, some kind of, you know, uh, system like that.
There you go. I got it wrong. It's fraternity and sorority, my ass.
Yes. Exactly. Exactly. Soror means sister. Frotcher means brother, right? And that's the
fraternity brotherhood. Sorority.
Yep, you know there
Some of the motherfuckers are interesting
Yeah, so they when I was in college they were really starting to do the
What was it? I mean?
They were called a fraternity, but there was girls in there, so like it was like a secret society
It was a very interesting dynamic
It was integrated by the yeah, it's probably a sex magic kind of thing. They're probably having a lot of sex with each other
So it happens when you mix them and you mix you're supposed to really mix them because you know it's better to okay
I'm not gonna go
I
You see in fraternities and sororities have nothing to do with your financial background at all
It's all the nepotism system
Nepotism usually means by family the family hooks you up, but it's actually that you know the friends
They're family because of brotherhood, right? So it depends if you're
What is that a patern? Well, I guess it would be a paternal member for whatever sorority or
Fraternity because you're you're it's a nepotism thing. Yes, absolutely being accepted
Nepotism comes from the word Neptune right on the Dallas is that home
It does thank God and see the God of the sea
I mean, I I said it but okay. Yeah, it's it's it's an apatism type of shit because your father was the same member in this fraternity
So you get us leg up because of who your family is in this leg turn
Yeah, I mean more I mean more more like more like the fraternity the fraternity servers will consider themselves their brothers and sisters and so
They also go through the hazing and the in the initiations and so they will tend to
hook each other up later in life as they as they're able to right 100% and more so though the
nepotism of getting it it's more getting into said fraternity right yeah or so you know because
your mom dad was a new stranger and then god because i can't go a thorough point please
Hold on, Vanguard, you white assholes, what does paternity mean and getting accepted?
Everything you said, because I'm like an immigrant. I don't know what to mean by all that.
Did you just call me a white all school? No, you're talking about a
fraternity and you got in and all this shit. I just want to know what you're talking about.
What the fuck would you prefer bleached asshole?
So is your avatar a hot dog of Trump surrounded by British
Prime Minister you're funny. It would be Boris Johnson surrounded by
Yeah, yeah, I know
The uh, well, I guess that's post politically correct. It's no Boris Johnson no more, but I digress
I quite like when you digress, actually, I was here.
You digress when you digress is my favorite.
That's what you do when the USA steps up.
You digress, right?
And it hurts you that we were on the show.
You have to bow down. You're on your knees to the United States of America.
And it hurts you
the
If anybody is familiar with
Team America world police, you know, yeah, man. I love that. Can I give you I see it
Can you listen to me for at least 10 seconds?
There's a new film right on and it's prime on Netflix. I can't remember. I think it's prime and it's cold and
Heads of state, it's the new team America
Oh, dear, it's so funny.
All right, I'm making the note right now.
Heads of state, you said on Netflix?
It's on Netflix or Prime. I can't remember, but it's the new team America when you look at its context
Shall we say Idris Elba and it's also got
John Cena is the US president
Is it in as a comedy?
It's very much it's very much like I said, it is the new team America. I'm so excited
With the caveat of fishing chips
I know so do that keeps travels around the UK, right?
It's been my guilty pleasure addiction on YouTube watching and
His fish and chips fucking croutiques are my favorite fucking videos of just traveling all over
Mainly he does England, but he's done a couple in Scotland
few in
Northern Ireland, I believe
And oh
I mean, how do you fuck up any way? Anyway, go watch the movie. It's cold heads of state
And it's Idris Elba and John Cena
It's so funny and it is
Team America with the caveat with fishing chips
I will watch it. I may I actually have made a note of it. So I
Fucking watch that that sounds funniest fuck though. Idris Elba in a comedy
Or being funny
I'm excited
We just have a fucking phenomenal
He was one of my favorite bonds
But not bonds
Either way, either way. Now question, right, fish and chips, are you a staple, is that
a staple in your diet?
Um, technically, it was the cheapest food during World War II on the 50s.
Let me rephrase this. Do you personally like to eat fish and chips a lot?
Not a lot, but I'm not even Catholic. I don't choose a Friday to eat fish and chips, but I like fish and chips.
That's so good. All right, fair enough though.
No, I'm a huge seafood fan, and I'm a definitely I scrutinize all the
Our quote-unquote fish and chip shit here, so but that's it's just funny not a Catholic
Don't worry, I'm a reform Catholic I learned better. I am no longer Alexander. What are you doing?
What's that?
What is that?
I'm watching TV.
He's uh...
What the fuck is that? Inceptioning us.
He's talking to us
and watching us on the phone
and TV.
Watching him watching him
I'm sitting on my couch for watching TV
You know what hurts me?
I got a California king bed
that goes untouched a lot.
Sometimes I fall asleep on the couch,
sometimes I go to sleep on the bed,
but either way, and then I see all these homeless people,
and I'm like, fuck!
I got a bed that can fit seven people, and it goes like
You do do it.
And by the way, it's not a Cali.
Am I allowed to do it?
It's not a king.
It's a California king.
Alex, how tall are you?
Can I just finish with this?
No, because it means something.
NYPD
Homelessness NYPD
What are you shuffling
Look at page eight hasn't changed that white tank top since I said she looks
Well, I said ten days ago she look hot into my tank top. She's been wearing the same shit for three days
Wait, what a page
All right, well me and you are me and you are here vanguard and also hey
Yeah, I like you too, man. It's been fucking fun talking to you. I'm not leaving yet, but it's you know
Yeah, man, no problem. It I don't know why this could one this lovely woman off because then my baby is good
Yeah, yeah, yeah agreed and I don't know if Paige left there because usually a psyche don't background page
But, uh, yeah, it's a new day, uh, but, you know, either way, fuck it, man, yeah, I enjoy,
I enjoy cultured things, though, cultured conversations and learning about other fucking
culture.
Actually, fuck, uh, no, that'd be a doxing if I asked, uh.
I'm not gonna well, you can ask any question you want
My god, you're gay look at your gay ass
Are you
Let me phrase it this way is there a difference like I oh
Ireland is a dramatic example of northern and southern kind of aspects of Ireland
Does Scotland have a breakup like that where it's not so much northern, but I guess maybe like that
So Scotland has a divide and it's called the Catholic and the Protestants.
What happened to that girl? Why did she go?
Because she was going to change her tank top.
That she must be so smiley and dirty.
The Canadian bitch has been wearing it together.
Did you hear my question?
Like I said, naturally, Scotland has a divide just like Ireland is the Protestants and the Catholics.
Yeah, geographically, does it make it north-south or is it still, you know, it's divided?
I mean, there's a big north-south divide in England even.
Oh, shit.
nothing you know our world history is shit you know it's a we get a one we
have one you know one of our school semesters of what I don't know fucking
is that last eight months because it's not a year of school so like eight months
and year one mine was ninth grade for school that was world history so we
You know, welcome God. What do you got? Oh, you're not done. I'll be back. Oh
Go fuck yourself. God. Yeah, yeah fucking goatee shit
God forbid, God forbid there's a culture. He was asking a decent question for once. He was asking a decent question for once, unlike you go to your friends. Already, already left. But no, you know, it's God forbid some people, you know, we make it somewhat learning and cultured and not drama yelling.
Oh, shit.
But no, so hey, I will you answered my question
I was just saying about our world history and we get eight months to learn about the entire world history and
then all of the rest of your schooling is you know
99 95% you know
American history without being offensive
America did not win the war of independence. It was a draw
Uh, to be fair, and I only raised this one argumentative point is, A, we don't follow
the Queen's rule.
And that's my one point of argument. The rest is, it don't matter when lose or draw, we are both so entangled as nations, it doesn't even fucking matter who won the fucking war.
Right.
Anyway, please tell me who was the second president of America fuck yeah please.
Who the fuck was it Andrew Jackson? No, no John Adams. John. Ah, that's where John John Quincy Adams
mmm
Wait, wait, no, who'd you just say John you said John Adams?
Yes, it was. Yeah, it was John Quincy Adams. You're right
Andrew Jackson was he I don't want to see it was I don't think he was fifth
I don't remember I remember yeah, no you're right and exactly wait. There's a statement too though is
There you go ask
Look at like it. I I like I said presented myself as knowing somewhat more about fucking history and some cultured bullshit
Yeah, you knew the answer to our second president
Let alone who here me as somebody random in the chat, I'm sure knew the answer
one person
Well put this way I love America, but I don't like its direction
so our our
Youth is fucked and our government is
Beyond fucked by support no aspects of our government
at this point and
You know our youth is corrupt or well suede
And all these older generations want to oh in my day. Oh, you guys are just being pussies. No, this that and the other
That's that's what that's what the older Americans say
Are you calling me an old podge?
No, no, no, no, I said older I said older Americans older Americans say that to all you know
If you talk to a 50-plus year old American not saying that's old, but it's older than me. So I'm saying older
Right. All right, that's how I'm describing that and that's just you're a pussy and you know
We did this and we did that but at the same point, right?
Everything as far as we're concerned
Was handed on a silver platter to you guys because you could buy a house at 18 years old
What?
You couldn't buy a vehicle in cash. What you could have a real job
You're saying what?
Is that you, Vanguard?
But, yeah, no, no, fuck that. What was the house price in, I don't know, 1960s or 70s?
You're vitrifying, objectifying the point of debt.
Is that the thing you're talking about?
That's just part of the statement, right?
And that's cross-culture, that's every nation, man, everything.
And now it's not to say that we don't have a lot of shit handed to us a lot easier
I mean especially look at fucking information and learning and knowledge like fuck
If you want to spend three hours on the internet not watching fucking Roblox and just searching some history
You could enlighten yourself easily and learn some shit, right?
You can damn near do anything aside from be a doctor these days just from what you learn online
I quite like you, I like you Ijear, I think you're fantastic, I think you're a real good one.
Thank you, thank you, likewise. I'm not just a fucking retard all the time.
You know, contrary to what Paige thinks about me, I know.
Well, I don't know much.
What do you mean you don't know much? Well, you know.
The stupid Canadian
When I do come back to America, I
Visit this this McQueen. Oh god, Rondo
And I stretch him out
Rondo just because you changed to black Rondo. We still know you're the white Rondo Rondo
Are you gonna do the black eagle or the bloody?
All right, no, we got that one statement out of Rondo.
He made that whole fake YouTube account
so he could be black for a minute.
Dude, that was kind of like, I'd be scared.
That was kind of like, that was very serious.
Wow.
To who?
I don't know, but it's his spooky.
Oh man.
Dude, fuck in. Side note though, I do think the usage of my name and being on this form
My PayPal account has been tried to be hacked like I don't know 30 times in the last month
Made our experience Chinese
self-doxing but
Chinese North Koreans include in Trump values have tried to intercept my bunghole
And I've said fuck off, but Trump wants the Scottish bung.
Trump, China, and North Korea have tried.
I said fuck you.
The new axis of you.
Axis power.
Yeah, Gaudi, I can pull you a card.
I'm not allowed to talk about Israel at the moment.
You're right.
You are in a...
Yeah.
Oh, man.
No, I don't want to do that.
It's...
I don't know.
I really, truly don't have an opinion on him.
I do want to say, though, one of my friends, and she's pissing me off, we live in an area
where there is a lot of...
All right, we're here for you a lot of Jewish population around and like
Anyway, I'm not a lot we talk about Israel at the moment so
prairie prairie beach
Yeah, um
Nardia you live in canadia. Which part of canadia do you hear from?
Alberta.
I've been to Alberta.
Yeah, what do you think?
It's lovely, but do you know where Medicine Heart is?
Yeah, I have family there.
Do you have family there? Is that why you're visiting?
No, no, no. I was visiting part of the military.
interesting so cool cool old buttons right and it's in it's it's not far from
Alberta but it's medicine that's very clear yeah yeah but British Army training unit
so few small world hey but it's a very big prairie fucking very it's a big
And where do you live?
I live in Van Gogh, Er... Asgore, Earth.
Oh, okay. Cool.
Interesting how the internet brings people together from so many places.
It's so diverse, you know?
What?
What is going on?
Oh, I'm back live again. Oh, shit.
I guess, I don't...
I was about to do my...
Decompression hang
Random I
Randomly got that added back in but once you pull a card for them pull my card. I don't know
Please and thank or sorry, will you please pull a card for me? Let me I
Refazed and I was polite
I don't want to be assumptive.
What did I do?
I'm just asking what did I do to get kicked off?
I think there's a random rotation, somewhat happening.
Right, right, right.
But, I don't know, I think this is the most polite stream I've ever been on with.
Well, but I've been to Alberta, British Army Training Unit, Suffield, which is very near
metals and that, you know, but my ability oil field is a very big prairie.
That's why it's a British Army on the Canadian.
I believe American also aligned training exercise area.
you know what I mean? There's only a few trees here and there. It's called a training unit and
everything that goes on there is live live fire from tanks to guns to aircraft. It is a live fire
range. Is it like the remnants of like the oil companies and loggers being there that just like
like made that giant fucking flat land feel I'm not sure if it's down to the
oil companies but it is a very big area
well yeah oh fair enough I mean well at least land gets somewhat used not
really in a healthy way testing bombs
Can I get this reading please vanguard? Can you shut the fuck up vanguard, huh? Can you shut the fuck up for a minute?
You piece of shit
It might even allowed on the panel you motherfucker. I'm not even allowed here
Continue page. Thank you page. You're welcome. God. God. It's good to see you
Paige, are you going to do me a favour, please?
What's that?
Can you burn some sage, white sage for me?
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Thank you.
Thank you, Paige. Thank you. You're welcome. It's for everybody. I do it every day for everybody
You're welcome
By the way, Prairie Paige. Yeah, I think you're fantastic. I think
Thank you
Mmm
Don't take Michael's little fucker
Okay
Okay, Gaudi, I'm gonna do an animal oracle today. I'm gonna start with that for you
Because we haven't really done it much lately, and I like the stack a lot and we have this fish coming out right away
so
Very much
Pricy's kind of energy it reminds me of but I will read from the books for you because this is just the best book ever
Restlessness, change of focus, and lost in the current.
The fish loves to be subsumed in life's current, nothing pleases it more than movement.
Movement and more movement.
The roaming lifestyle of the fish may be exhilarating for a while, but usually leads to weariness and slippery relationships.
With all the possibilities out there in the vast waters, the fish becomes lost without clear goals and intentions.
Spend some time with the lunar forces, dear fish, as the peace and calm of the moon will soothe your soul.
When in balance, adaptable and travels well, when out of balance, distracted and changes mind often.
Okay. Let's see these. Where's my other deck? No idea.
So, Prairie, Prairie, how would you read the Vanguard?
How would I read you?
Do Vanguard before me.
Did you just refer to yourself in third person like that?
Yes, I am the third person because I am Valhalla. I am heaven. I may am the universe.
My cards are clumping up goddess, so something's blocking you obviously.
Something's standing in your way. Something has stopped your movement clearly, which is weird because I read you every day
So this is like a really really sudden thing
This is something that's happened like immediately or as of maybe the last since I haven't seen you since whenever you talked last
Which is yesterday. I think her last night
Something
Striking it's like we're the work striking so something striking like
Comes in hot and quick and then just leaves as quick as it did. It's like a sting almost which is really weird
Not that it's really bothering you, but it's definitely bothering your forward movement. Like it's definitely a roadblock right now
which we need to
Maybe address it so you can move forward from it
I'm quite intrigued quite intrigued by your pre-analysis actually
Oh, thank you. If you want to check more out, I have my own channel. I don't just
You can join live you want some time and have a reading it's
Okay, um, go to y'all so think that I
Feel like something is like it's really bothering your it's not ego or pride, but it's something's just bothering like
Something or someone is like really to stroke your ego or your or your like dignity the wrong way
And I'm not sure if it's it's not huge. It's just it's really bothersome apparently
well
Can we just put it quite simply here right now?
Humanity is being
Well, we're gonna do we're gonna do the smaller scale
Well, this is the body is reading right now. So I can we can talk bigger scale later, but this is pertaining to him right now
My apologies, I thought you were talking about me. No not yet not yet. Oh in due time good, sir
It's really funny Gaudi because these two cards have come out for you in the last couple days as well
So it's a couple repeat messages
It's going to be until there's new and more new energy
But definitely there's a change from last night to just today and like you know a few hours
So we have the aid of Gabriel and it's a great deal of activity sudden and immediate results or important communication
So I feel like that's kind of what that strike was something that came in quick and hot and it was sudden
kind of like the knight of fawns in a sense, right?
So the three of Ariel, and do what you love.
It's a time of great personal growth in your career
or artistic endeavors.
So working with others in a cooperative manner.
So I feel like,
Every day you're learning different things from all of us and we learn from you and you know the whole connection communication thing
Sometimes it's good. Sometimes it's not good, but it's nothing that can't be worked on and it's nothing that's going to change
Because you can't change other people or their choices or the outcome you just have to go with it
You can make your own choices, right?
Page of Michael so truthful perceptive analytical and blunt so
An exciting new challenge. You have what it takes to succeed, review contracts, or documents, very thoroughly.
Interesting. Okay, I want to just look at the bottom of the deck.
So we have the chariot. So forward movement. So you're just stuck for right now because this is really small and it's going to pass.
And nothing can really stand in your way when it comes to like the little shit. Even the big shit. I think you handle it quite well.
You definitely are you know truthful perceptive analytical blunt, but you know determination and self-control
And you're gonna have some career advancement to you that's coming
I think you were working really hard on a few things whether it be you know online or it'd be in your actual like career your job
And just being acknowledged or recognized for your success or your hard work that you put into things
Or just kind of who you are and the pride that you take in the jobs that you do
Anyways, that's kind of where we're at. Anything else I have to say is probably messages from yesterday
Stop playing with a queen. Yo, I went to a wrong channel. I wanted to go to true zones
Through someone is calling me up. Like guys get up here and tell me about you robbing junkies and all this bullshit
So I try to go into true zones
somehow
I'm here
of the
the
Yes, no, maybe my PD and my PD. Are you a fucking national or an immigrant yourself?
what
National or an immigrant
National
What does that mean
you born here in America?
So, it sounds like you're a bit of a bell in
Yeah, I was born in America
Yeah
Does that make me a national?
Yes
Okay, so I'm a national
What a national is, yes
Yeah, I've never been
questioned like this before in my life
I'm a national
immigrant
I mean, what's nightmare, bro? I must speak with a badge
You see those guys on the news with the with the mask on that's me
That's me motherfucker. I'm a fucking federal agent with a badge a spake a Colombian
Your NYPD
And also, is he actually a cop?
Did he mention Columbia?
Oh dear.
But he did mention Columbian.
You would have caught that.
I don't listen to what he says.
Page.
So is this your first Scottish national?
for the reading. Oh, hold on. There is, I think, you people who asked first, so. Oh,
okay. Sorry, sorry. No, that's okay. I just got to be fair, right? I gave up my spot
for him. So, Vanguard's before me. So do you. Your third down, Vanguard.
I see that's not very much a Viking name, but I like your Viking news
Thank you, Jamie wanted one and who else did sorry in the chat
But you know what
Hannah wasn't Hannah. No, it wasn't Hannah. She came in after I
Can't go up high enough. I thought it was another girls name
Sorry, I'm talking shite. My apologies page. Sorry. I'm not gonna read you Hannah. He just asked if you were the one
Honestly guys, I don't even really feel like doing this tonight. I might just go to my own channel. I don't want to
I'm just like I've had a long day
The fuck
We all know this chance full of dicks and random shit, but Paige
Usually like I can usually take it better. I'm just I'm really
And thank you for what you've done so far
Wholeheartedly appreciate
Can you do me a favor very very can you do me a favor perry page?
Can you post?
Can you post your link?
Isn't it sorry just one second look you that was you that wanted it, right? Oh
That's why I'm not
I do not know what this page does these readings
she she is not the channel owner it's for as for the link before before you oh my god
Kate I love you guys I'm going to my own town wait wait wait all right very very why she
leave don't worry why did she leave vanguard uh
i will uh oh wait i can't even post it because i'm pretty sure i'm still blocked on these these
these women in america um um idea you can have a conversation i can't i'm still blocked on chat but uh
me don't know why she do that if you search prairie winds and wildflowers page should pop up
Yeah, I would
Yeah, I don't know. I just you know
Me don't know why she did do that. Yeah. No, me neither white rondo
This is rondo. Oh
Half rondo kind of rondo
Why she do that why she do that?
So, Prairie Pige, Prairie Pige, can you post in YouTube right now so I can go to your page please?
The priority bounce is the problem.
Yeah, but this page, this page, crowd chasing, she take all the people from this channel and she go to work.
I can get you a channel. I mean, for Foxy.
Rondo. This woman chasing crowd.
This woman chasing crowd.
Rondo. Rondo.
Tell me two things Rondo. What does one and one make Rondo?
These questions are not suitable for the Rondo. It's too simple. It's it's too simple
So why this woman come here? Why this woman come here?
And she take all the people over to her channel. She's not safe. She's not even safe
Get the fuck out of my country!
Is the general butcher your friend?
Anyway, um, can you do me a favor, Ajia?
She white devil! She white devil!
I got you Vanguard, what's up?
Can you post, um, prairie?
I don't think I can post.
I don't, uh...
You've got a link. You can put it in the ditch. Come on. Oh, did did my post just happen?
Oh, yeah
Cuz I got blocked in chat, so
What was the name again prairie what prairie winds and wild flowers
Oh, Jamie's cowboy just posted it in chat. Thank you, Jamie's
Also, Jamie's. What's up? Sorry. I didn't say hi earlier
Love you
We need to have a fucking music night
Yeah, yeah, Jamie's cowboys. Yeah, do you want me to press Jamie cowboys bullshit because he's
Cowboys posted prairies
put us where I'd rather I'd rather
Vile
Deutcher from twice. I said Deutcher from over vile type
It's the right link do I have to yes well if you want to find a miss prairie
Okay, subscribe there you go. Yeah pages the truth
German lady appears.
Frau! Frau! Frau!
Did you speak German for a second?
No, that's just not good now.
You know, from an Austrian...
Well, that's the problem. It was a mixed household.
It's not enough of heritage.
Technically Austrian but Austrian-Irish.
of the household I grew up in. It was too blended. Grandpa was 100% Austrian with German
Ausch, whatever, and grandma's 100% Irish.
I was here, I was actually talking to her, sorry, my apologies, I was actually talking
to the wild German lady, and when I talk about her, I talk about Echlieberdijk, meiner
Am I am I right in my assumption of what that means that is funny
You know what I believe it is my little chief row is what?
Well, I know fro good. Oh
German lady. All right. Got it tail end of it. No big. Oh
Wait, what the fuck is that leave dead? Are you German?
Wait, no, it's I love you. Oh
Okay, I didn't know that. All right, leave and what leave it. Well, I'm an eye yeah
You fucked up to comprehend
I love
I don't know what they say about their songs, but I
Love the German
Oh, yeah
Ekliben...
Ekliben dicktois frau.
I love you, German lady.
Got it.
Oh, man.
I actually had a decent bit of fucking...
No, not Hindi, but that's all done and gone.
I got taught on YouTube for like two months and then just that's out the fucking window.
Although if you don't have anybody to practice what you learn that like it doesn't it don't
stick, you know, like you have to be able to use that use what you learn on a regular
basis or else you just forget it all like Spanish, I have four years of Spanish I did
I quite like you as a yeah, can I subscribe to you as well idea? Oh, I'm so
Again, I can't I can't post my channel because I can't comment, but I mean if you just search my name
I'm sure I'll pop up. I'm the only one
The wonder by doge
I wish I could speak in German, but actually I wanted to be partly French, but I can't
There's not that much French that I remember Jean-Mapel Luc, but Luc was my French name
so Jean-Mapel Isaiah
It's kind of like that.
Anyway, I'm having a duff laugh.
Anyway, good evening.
Alice Klaas, we get nix?
I don't know.
It was good, but yes, it's been fun.
What does it mean?
What did you just say to me?
I was just talking to German lady.
We get.
Oh, is she speaking German in chat, or is she just talking to me?
No
That's my I started hard and was stupid when I actually cared about learning the language and I gave up
It's trying to do an Arabic one of the Arabic dialects
Man, I was an idiot for trying to make that my first real language learning as an adult
That's fucking hard, man
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, what?
Nope, none of it
Mites, eye, thread, listen
What are you learning about, doggo?
the other part of Europe right so another statement to I wanted to fend the
dumb American statement I wanted to fend against that being the we don't know
other languages aside from Spanish because well that's the next closest
aside from French being in you know fucking key back
But again, all those doors
How far are you from the next closest nation that speaks another language?
Like how much how many hours do you have to travel right? So if you for Muda, Germany, how far is that that trip?
And by boat or by airplane
I don't know the longest route the longest route, right?
Believe though not going all the way up the ocean all the way to the fucking
Through the English Channel all the way up to fucking Germany and should not that far but like, you know both land maybe plane
I don't know
Mainly well you can get to mainland you can get there within you can get to mainland Europe
Whether it be Germany or Holland or France within or invasion
That's what we're gonna do. We're gonna invade within how long sorry Asian
Within an hour and a half. Oh, yeah, so there's a statement right and that's bringing you to other nations with other languages
than your native language right which makes it very much easier to learn because that's
very much in your proximity for me to get to uh french canada can i just me i just remind you
do you do you know what suction is yeah do you know what anglo suction is yes do you know what
I have I think I I think I do but yeah yeah no yeah I do I do yeah you're gonna
talk it and it's all gonna boil down to different well probably dialects but
Well, Anglo-Saxon, although considered white male, but for white people's in some descriptions
But either way I digress. No, that's not that I know what though
Can I can I just interrupt plastic African with these curved horn? Oh, dear
Where's the curved horn? I didn't see it. Oh, I like your beard brother
Nice beard
Somebody else
Cheers cheers brother
I'm a nice beard brother. Nice beard.
Skon, skon, skon.
Mine's a little bigger, but ears looks cleaner.
Skon.
Bluistic ear for the corner.
What the fuck?
I'm gonna flinch off your corner.
For an American, I think it's somebody, another nation
speaking another language.
It is quite quite the journey of I think Quebec is probably about 14 or 15 hours away
And that's for French mainly if I want to go to us predominantly Spanish speaking place
I
Think yeah Cuba would probably be the closest and that's
18 19 20 hours
You know, like we're talking, you know, whole-on day travel, two-day travel to get to places, you know
Long-ass trip to get to somewhere where a dominant language is different than
Technically, you can go to London
to Paris
Well, that just states the same flight
but London's main
if we go to London, exclude Paris
but at least London is the example
the predominant language
is English, same shit
but France being different
and that's just all plane ride
I'm thinking more so landmass
Yeah, but you don't have
a channel tunnel, do you?
Do you know what a channel tunnel is?
Yeah
No, we don't we don't have that. Well, no, of course not
Of course, we don't have that
We don't need it nowhere
Wait, are we talking?
You mean the English Channel Tunnel, right?
Yes, definitely. Okay. All right, just want to make sure
He's talking about the Vietnamese English Channel
Around the world bro, it's you get on that fucking train and bang you
Here's a house
you know whatever in the english countryside your house covered in ivy
hey you know nice narrow road yeah yeah how many servants you want
oh man hey technically if you buy i could i could be a lord i can buy scottish property online
become a scottish lord
what
That's a thing. Well, at least it's a
Hold on may I just remind you anything you buy online is fake
For fucking stop that is not true. Okay
She did not have a dick when she got here, but she did not like me
She was a real woman, I swear.
Ah, alright, sorry, bad joke, but...
Oh no, what are you talking about, Ben?
I tried to get a woman from Mars and it wasn't a good thing.
Yeah, especially when I'm watered from Amazon and
Get the fuck right out in my country. You're from Pretoria, but live in London
Side note though, I do wish Germany was an easier closer ride because I want to go to Germany
easier closer faster travel I'd rather Germany be above us than Canada but you
know personal opinions do you know the fastest train in the world is still the
bullet Japanese
Oh, I know
201 I don't know if it's got up since then, but it was 201 for a long time
Well, apparently China's beat it, but it's not the shinkansen
Problem with China's is right like the rest of the problem of China right nobody uses it because nobody trusts it because it's Chinese
Everybody thinks it's gonna derail
What China makes some good shit mate China have you seen B. Why do you have you see in DJI drones
DJI are the best in the world
Come to their infrastructure and it comes to a technology thing they're creating China does make good shit
But if they're building anything
It is the equivalent of a cardboard house.
The bigger problem is the scale as anything is, right?
With China at scale.
So where it sits, as well as what they say they have.
So I understand.
What's your name bro?
Isaiah.
So Isaiah, I can understand that completely. It is a paper dragon.
Definitely, yeah, there is faults there.
Oh, that's what they called them, the paper dragon.
right yeah yeah yeah completely yeah because it's all a fallacy it's the
fucking paper mache oh he's keeping off the side of a
fucking multi-story house it says says the south african says the south
african of a white value of a little most
That's the bias I hear.
Are you South African?
I don't know, I'm English.
Oh, OK, all right.
No, he's South Africa.
He lives in England.
He lives in England, but he comes from not.
He comes from a, what?
Robert McGarbey's previous country.
I don't know.
Were you born in South Africa?
Robert McGarbey.
OK, all right, all right.
You know, I have many questions about South Africa.
and especially the quote-unquote apartheid against white people in South Africa, but...
Yeah man, yeah man.
Yeah man, can I bring an absolute fact to you about South Africa?
Yep.
Okay, good, that's very good.
Um, Winston Churchill, yeah.
Yeah.
was that it was that the fact right yeah I'm thinking like what Winston Churchill
a fact oh what's up spunky how are you doing honey good how are you good
We were just about to get a lesson on Winston Churchill and he dropped off.
Yeah, no.
I wanted to know where that was going.
Yeah, interesting.
It's kind of a very enlightening conversation tonight for the most part.
It's been good.
With Alfred Hitchcock?
Yeah, that's funny.
But yeah.
We've watched many topics and many nations and it's been a good night.
Drama free for the most part.
For the most part.
Uh, it's good. How's your night going? Good. I see you're having a party. Oh, yeah, always
I'm too lazy to put the other light bulb back in so
Bang it out there. There was a complaint about lighting and all you could see was darkness
So well, this is the only light on this side of the ground. So it's what I'm stuck with but
You know, I'm making the best of it, right look like the party and yeah, exactly, right?
What's wrong with disco? I mean, I'm so stunned because you got electricity shit
Whoa, I mean he is probably in the middle of BFE Ohio, right?
No, no, dude. I fucking wish I was it'd be so much better
Yeah, I'm a Cleveland area native and I fuck it. I hate city life. I fucking hate it
You live in the city now, uh, it's I'm in a suburb. Yeah
How close is your closest neighbor like right there or uh, yeah 20 foot probably third well
No, it's more than that, but you know like
No more than no more than like 50 feet. I'd say it to the next house
I don't have a house on my one side the one side's all trees and like a brushy area
Yeah, you know to property fit probably like an acre or two. Yeah, my my dream is like, you know
having like a rolling driveway and like nobody really around and
The same way fucking how it started, right?
Um, and when I grew up, my grandpa was the first house the he built the road extension in 1950s
And he built the house himself that you know, I'm in now family house, uh
in 1957
And then he sold the land next door a few you know, I don't like
Five years later to the same family who lives there now
Their their parents built the house that they're in right and my grandpa sold them the land and then the next neighbor
But there was 30 acres in this area, right?
and then by the time I'm in high school they sold off like
15 of them, but we still had a substantial property like 20 minutes outside of downtown Cleveland like fucking huge
And it's in a very rich neighborhood now because well, you know, we're the White Trash family
But we got blessed with old land and then my family
So now we have an acre and a half and they got robbed but now we have an acre or
Yeah, an acre and a half maybe two acres of land here, which is still like
Substantially valued property here. Yeah, I'll never sell it. I I this is my inheritance. I'm like, I I'll never sell this fucking place
I love this place
So it's not a mental
Because I pretty much grew up here, so that's good. Yeah, but other way so yeah, I didn't grow up in total city life
But it eventually the city fucking surrounded me. It's moved in on ya
Yeah, this all rich assholes and half million dollar houses on what used to be our land
Where were you at the night that you were like camping and how far away was that from where you live?
That was about 40 minutes from here and that was my cousin's property. He's got that was I
Think he's got 10 or 15 acres out at that property
Um, he's building a house there.
Um, well, he hasn't really started it because he doesn't really care.
I like to say, that was my first time out there.
It's like a double wide shed that he lives in.
Like it is a shed.
And it's like, you showed me and it didn't look like much.
Yeah, it's a, it's a, it's a massive shed.
And does he have AC?
Kind of like a window. I don't know because I was only in there for a second and
I mean I was already pretty drunk at that point. It's not remember if it was cooler in there, but I
Mean the way you were so drunk. They would lay in the house
No, no
Well, maybe not later at night, but I I mean honestly there's not really walls in there
So I wouldn't really want to be in there late at night. Oh God knows what him and his girl are doing, but
No, like knowing him though in his like he's very live off the land
They might he might not have AC I mean I would not be surprised at all
Fuck, bro. I mean, I can't live like that. I need AC. It's gotta happen.
Actually after the stream my phone died, like, I don't know, fucking 10 o'clock in the morning.
I was like fuck this, all right, I'm gonna go to sleep for like four hours and then drive home and
just turn my truck on and just slept in the fucking air conditioning.
Yeah, that's way better and no creepy things in the forest coming at you.
It's already light at that point, you know, but but true, true.
You know what?
It wasn't as creepy as I thought.
They were giving me shit though.
Dude, I was freaked out and I wasn't even there.
Well, he would I thought it was a joke at first because him and his friends were on about some bear sighting in the area
And I mean, it's probably black bear, but also I mean, it's a fucking bear, right, you know, right?
Like that's not very common over here
But I thought they were just on about you know trying to spook me and like you know
Scared me a bit, and they're like, oh, he's like no no no
He's like legit like you know just start yelling if you hear some crazy shit or whatever
He's like there was legit a bear sighting like you motherfucker
So make their burgers, right?
I I don't think I
Bear is what I mean, you know when life gives you lemons you make lemonade
I'll make a bear skin fucking, I don't know
You can't kill the animal without eating it, huh?
I won't eat it, I believe
There's two fucking risky man, all the parasites
Yeah, of course I can, you're not hunting them, I mean, generally
Maybe you were, we trapped a bear, I'm trying to fucking deer
Uh, yeah, well, especially if it's about eating I'm gonna hunt a bear cuz I'm gonna eat the fucking bear
Yeah, you guys know what you're doing. I'd rather eat puffer fish and take that risk before
It's a parasites man, there's so many worms and if the bear is not fucking cooked like
Yeah, absolutely. Yeah, I mean, yeah, everything's like that really life
Well, no, like you said we have all our pasteurized meats and shit we talked about so the parasite risk ain't that high
But but I mean even the shit hunted like deer
You're not gonna parasite from a deer wolf meat might make you go crazy a little bit too much wolf meat
But I mean stacked up bears one of the meats. I won't eat
Well in Africa, they you know, we don't eat a lion the Zimbabweans eat lion. It's weird
Monkey you guys don't really fuck with monkey
Primates you don't eat I don't think no no cuz the tribes that do are all bats
Yep, there's there's a lot of things I'll eat, but you know bear and mushrooms are
No
Unless they're half fun mushrooms
Shrooms are gross. It's just like dirt man. It's just like eating. Yeah, I agree. They're nasty
And then like the texture when they get all slimy like yeah, yeah
No, I don't like tomatoes either. I
Well, I'm just whatever about tomatoes actually little the cherry tomatoes aroma tomatoes. Okay. Those are cool
I mean, I'm not gonna just sit there and fucking pop a bunch in my mouth
But you know, I don't like I'm under raw, but like I'll get them cooked, you know
All the dried tomatoes, that's totally fine. It's the consistency or the texture of like raw tomatoes just grosses me out
I actually like the slimy raw better than
Right the good for you as well notice the salt in a little pepper. Oh my god, they're brilliant
Try them, you know everything about tomatoes
All right, that's a good fucking bite some bruschetta
Hey, Sponky, hey Sponky, how the fuck are you man now? Alex is back. I'm fucking great man
How the fuck are you? I'm fucking fabulous life is great
Alex you saw more fun. I won't expect anything less from you spunking later
Spunker I don't want the spunky still left
What's on your mind Alex, I always love your thoughts
Plastic African I say I'm you Lee in the garage. I don't know who scares me more
But
No, no, it's funky I told you no skirt out on the town with a G string. What the hell is that?
No, hold on you guys are the swingers, right?
Yeah, you are that's all I got from you guys you guys are swingers and you want me
but you find me and I'll fuck the share of both you and I really but he can watch
I'll fuck you spunky and Jig whatever it's Justin can watch
you find me and I'm a woman board
somebody clip and I'll fuck the shit out of spunky while retarded whatever he is watching
because that's all they want
oh my god no Justin's not a guy
yeah I checked the case man
We were like the best dress there is my friend's 40th birthday party, and it was like mom's gone wild
But not in a good way. It was like it was not
I thought you were black remember that
Yeah, you did think I was a black woman
I feel like I'm gonna start fucking with you now that I know you as long as you know, I'm just playing
Yeah, spunky rephrase it. You were at a mom's gone wild party and it was yeah fucking it was fucking crazy
No, it wasn't fucking crazy. It was terrible and we ended up leaving and
Going to the bars and then we looked like maniacs like dressed like that
Let me have a fantasy of mom's gone wild
that's what I'm saying, like, how wild can a mom get, it's like not that crazy, no, well I don't want to hear mom in anything going wild
I'll hear spunky going wild or melds going wild or YouTube bitches or anything else besides mom going wild
are we going to have a while to be fun is it a good mom gone wild
or is it just like no bro no it was like
all right i wanted to play beer pong and like that was the most amusing thing
and it was a great mom should i even be in this conversation gone wild that's what i'm saying
It was bad
That's the problem they were great
Upstanding citizen mothers that were getting wild so when they get wild it's like oh my god
We rinse it in Airbnb and got some white claws, you know
By the boats or chubby and cute
Oh, you guys had both chubby and cute. Yeah
That's your boyfriend both and home mom
Justin's my boyfriend. Yeah, that's who the psych is your boyfriend. He doesn't care about you
By the way, no, he does not. Yeah, exactly if he loved you, he doesn't love you
I'm not saying he doesn't care about you, but he doesn't love you
When you love a girl you would never allow her to do what you do
There's something called respect and love.
That's why Iran has a right.
They cover the woman for my tattoo in a fucking sheet
and just two eyeballs hang out.
So I get why they want to bomb us, bomb us into the stone age
because we're just monsters.
Like spunky, but yo that motherfucker does not love you and he'll share you with the world's spunky
You deserve better than that
You could serve a man that loves you just want you all for himself
To build a family not to parade you around like a fucking freak
Like look at her. He doesn't care about you bitch. And then you lose it. I can see through your eyes
So unhappy you all
So get rid of that motherfucker and find the man that actually loves you
And the story I'm out. I don't care what it is, but do you have a job or work? I do. Yeah
Okay, well, I mean I was gonna argue to Alex's point where his fucking old typical sense home stay at home woman
Yeah, everything versus you're a new age lady. So I don't even live together. You know what I mean
Oh
Yeah
How long have you guys been dating?
A year and a half.
Oh, yeah, no, fuck that. Good job.
Yeah.
Look, it's advice to both of you.
Stay
separate for as long as possible.
And then when you move in, right?
Don't get engaged in the first year
or the second year.
Wait a few years, because then you know
you could actually
Fucking deal with that person. Yeah, absolutely. Um, I've been married a lot of a lot of times and like I've learned my lesson
I've been married a lot of times. I have been married a lot of times. What the fuck wait. Yeah, how many?
Yes, how it's a lot. What's a lot of times? I'm 40
All right, that's a relative statement, but I would say
My a lot for that would probably be oh god actually like three or four yeah three
three's the answer holy shit I know and like when I was splitting up from the
last one is when I met Justin so like I'm not in a rush for anything why after
let alone number two just put it at number two why again I don't know I
don't like I just look back and I'm like what the fuck was I doing you know
I was I was with this my ex for 13 fucking years. We got engaged never got married 13 fucking years, right I
Still didn't want to pop the fucking question
And then I did and then we were engaged for four years without five years without the wedding. Thanks cove and part of it
And then I became the problem that was the problem
But I digress
the fuck. I still didn't want to do it. And we had been living together. She pretty much
moved into my mom's house. And we lived together for after the first like six months. It was
awful. I mean, I don't want to say awful, but we were together that fucking much. And
we got a house and blah, blah, blah, blah, whatever. And well, I mean, obviously I'm
here now without her.
Yeah, I don't know if I'm complaining too too much, but no, no, it's okay same point though
I still wouldn't want to be married to her it right now. Would I be together with her? Absolutely married
That's a big fucking commitment it ruins everything in my experience. Yeah, yeah, that was a downfall was me giving her a ring and
That was the start of the downfall
The beginning of the end yep
Yep. So, I don't know, you know, I always wanted to live life like Dambel's Aryan, you know,
party around the world, the uber wealthy playboy. Well, I might be none of those things, but
I have the opportunity.
The freedom.
Oh God, I didn't want to do that anymore. That sounds like too much work. I just want
That's my dream too. How many dogs do you have?
Just my one. I wanted to, I was trying to get, so.
Sorry.
Our dog was Kimber. I raised Kimber. I mean, we got her together, but I mean, I got Kimber.
And she's 9 now, I think. 8 or 9?
Well, I mean I wanted to take her but she wouldn't let me and then I tried to fight and take her and then you know
Yeah, legally I can win it, but I wasn't gonna go that far because I still have a fuckload of shit there and yeah
Yeah, I gotta but I ended up
January for February I got his name's Remington. Oh
That's a cute name
Eight months old. Yeah, eight months old. He was born in September. So yeah, I think he's eight months old or nine months old
Yeah, so just Remington
Remington have a middle name because he needs one with that regal first name. No, no, he does not
Oh, God, you got to give him a full government name. So when you yell at him, he knows it's serious
Oh, no, he knows it's serious because I it's it's ready
Or or mington
or Minji Minji
But if I say Remington he he he knows he already just looked at me like what what
That's cute. Yeah, no, I like obviously there's a trend of firearms with my dogs, but
Mine mine have city names. What do you how many do you have four?
What are they?
What's the Pomeranian's name?
Malibu Anastasia.
But she goes by Boo-Boo.
And then I have Spencer Aloysius.
He's a Malty-Poo.
He was a what?
A Maltese and a Boo-Boo.
Yeah
Say what right? Yeah, I was just asking if it was big because poodle but no no it's like a mini poodle mixed with him
He's only like ten pounds
Jesus I can't do a small dog. I'll step on it now. I feel and
I'll have Charleston Bartholomew. He is a mini Aussie, but he's very overweight
What and
He's like 30 pounds, but he probably should be 20. Okay, and
Then the next in then I have the one that everybody's seen on panel. That's Miley Esmeralda
I don't think I saw that one. Oh, she's really cute. She's a mini golden doodle. Jesus Christ. Yeah, she's really cute. Give her a mouse
Come on honey. We're gonna go say hi. Mini golden
You have a you have a flock of small dogs. I do I have a flock you got a flock of ankle biters
She's the biggest even though she's a mini here. I'll show you. Oh my god. Yeah, I can't do
She's not that small, but I mean, you know, she's bigger. Here's here's
Remington
Not being such an asshole right now, but
As much as he doesn't look like it. He's every bit of 70 pounds. Oh, he's it. Yeah, he's like lean looking
You know, he's long lean as fuck. I mean like he is his heads up to my waist when I kind of close
You stand up. All right, there we go. He's not real tall. He's super fucking lean like and 70 fucking pounds like you would not
Yeah, he looks like he should be in 50 40 50 pounds like nope. Nope, and he's still skinny as fuck
And I mean we I feed the fuck out of him
I know it's funny because he lost it in the last two weeks
My little ones are all skinny, but then like that one Aussie is so chubby. It's like I don't understand
I feed them all the same, you know
You're gonna do some laps
Yeah, like I see
Well, his diet keeps changing we keep so it's a pain in the dick, but we switch to
you get the whole
Instant bag of you know instant bag of rice every meal and now it's three times a day instead of two
A big can of like canned chicken and
Two to like two two and a half scoops of like cable
Still not putting on weight
Yeah
Still just skinny and lanky as fuck. He was yeah, he's probably really active
Someone he does chase the cat around the house a lot. Yeah, I mean
Yeah, I don't know not really if I'm laying down and he's laying down for the most part
like
He does run around but like I it's not you know, I don't know. Oh my god
Not that much. All right, quit quit bite me a little fucker. Go take your bone. Go get it
Fucker. He's white. Yeah, he's jumping on me and biting me, you know
fucking he's a
La black lab and German shepherd
That's a good match
I wish it was more shepherd because you know labs are pretty fucking retarded you know
golden retrievers too because Miley is like the dumbest sweetest thing I've ever met in my life
same thing because labs and retrievers are the same fucking thing you know but yeah yeah yeah
yeah they're they're they're retarded and he's got his
He's more retard. He's got more retard moments than Shepard. He learns, but then it's like
he forgets what he learned five minutes ago, and then I'm yelling at him again.
He's like, oh, okay. I'm good. And then, you know, five minutes later.
Then you walk home. You'll come in the door and it'll be perfect and he doesn't jump on you
He just comes and greets you and happy as shit
And then you sit down and then you just stand up and then he's jumping on you greeting you again
Like you fucking idiot
Yeah, my dog like she is happy all the time. I've never seen her sad. I've never seen her mad. Yep
That's it dude. It's so nice though. He's the same fucking way like even getting yelled at his tail is wagging, you know
She's like what are you saying mom? Yeah, I'm like you just chewed up my couch and she's like yeah, don't you like it you too?
Yeah, yeah, he ripped up the we just got a brand new couch and one of the cushions is fucking completely destroyed and
one of the arms has a
decent sized chunk
Yeah, I had to buy a new couch because of her.
Oh, sorry, Remy. I didn't mean to kick you in the nose.
I was just kicking your toy away.
Sorry, bud.
Yeah, that's kind of, uh, we're not quite there.
I think it's a dog abuser couch.
Yeah, you know.
You want it? You want you want your watermelon?
Oh, God.
But no, I love him.
I ain't got.
Oh.
Not having a dog for I think it was like three months at this house without a dog
I'm like losing my fucking mind because I had the last dog on and off like it was like child visitation
You know this weekend I get her and then she goes back home and then you know next
The other next week, you know like that type shit. I'm like this is awful. I can't sleep everything sucks
Alfred is back
Alfred
What happened to you? We need to hear about Winston Churchill
Jake, show me a coke
Isaiah, do you like my dog?
Oh wait, hold on
It's a I assume it's a pit bull, but not a English bulldog
It's a stuffage of bull terrier a stuffage of bull terrier is not a pit bull
US that's what we consider a yeah, that's our pit bulls. Yeah
sorry literally it's still beautiful though it's just different in the u.s. there might be minor
differences but yeah i i almost got i almost got a pity but i mean there's that it i don't know
why the stigma still fucking exists how many examples do you need of a pitbull fucking kissing
your child and the fucking i don't know any other dog breed being a fucking asshole like Jesus christ
So nice
My Pomeranian would eat your face off, honestly
Wait, I've never encountered anything to piss off
I've encountered fucking aggressive chaffers
What about this one?
What is that? I can't even see that
It looks like a gopher on crack. What is that? Oh, it's upside down. I see it. Yeah. Yeah
Hold on hold on hold on give me a second. Give me a sec. What is it? It's a mixed breed. Yeah
No, it's a stuff at your bull terrier now the American people
Did you wait that's the North American Pitbull
No, oh, that's the Stafford shire. Okay, I was gonna say I'm like I've never seen a pit. Well, it looks like that
The first picture you had up your dog that looks like a pit bull
Second one. Well again, that's a stuff at your bull terrier, not a pit bull. Yours. Yours has a different color
I got it. I got it
But without the second photo you showed a different coat
Got it didn't know there was that I mean, it's all a bully breed doesn't really fuck it
Doesn't matter too much is your dog nice and friendly
She is fantastic
Perfect, so pitbull Staffordshire don't they're just nice friendly bully breeds
to the wrong. Well, don't forget in the assessment. Staffordshire. Old English bull terriers come
from. Never mind your fucking interbreeding, your fucking fucked up American country.
All the bully breeds are being fucking from from your well, from the UK.
But either way spunky. Oh you have I talked to you before you have not honey. It's very nice to meet you
Vanguard's a champ. He's an a1 human being
He's uh, he's good to talk to spunky well lovely chatting with you
Hell yeah. Spunkyware. What is your coastal region? I won't sit here and ask a state or, you know, specifics.
I'm not allowed to say.
Oh, wait, you're right. I now remember because Jay does not want you to say shit correct
He thinks that everybody's gonna like stock me down and dox me now. I remember from that night
Yes
Fucking funny
Docs for the group of America fuck yeah
The coastal is pretty rough like East Coast West Coast Central like
you know to stay okay a little easier it's easy I'm pretty prominent on the
internet who I really am so it's hard to say anything I mean my name is easy I'm
one of one in the world so I'm very very yeah there's a few of me but there's
My apologies, with a name like Sponky, one of one in a profession.
Sponky.
Yeah, that's not my real name.
It's not?
What?
No, no, no.
My name's Stephanie.
Oh.
Stephanie what?
I'm just kidding.
Yeah.
Stephanie, fuck your mom.
Ooh.
That is an awesome unique name.
It is, isn't it? I'm one of one.
Great.
Dude, oh my god.
Imagine, just imagine that introduction at a party.
Yeah, imagine.
There's some sort of formal event.
Hi, my name's Stefan. What's your name?
What's your last name?
I'm just being crude no, you know, it's that'd be funny. Yeah, that's quite like cruise
If we can't laugh at it if you can't make a joke about it then you know
I say I was on another panel and Justin kind of like docks me a little and I told them what I'd do for a living and stuff and
Because I was like being my true self
They were like there's no way you do that for a living with a mouth like that and I was like
But gonna be specific because I think we your medical right yeah, so the guy was like
He was telling a joke and he was like what's black?
and long and full of semen and I was like oh I know this joke I know this joke
your mom oh god
and he like died I was like your mom's black and long and full of semen and then he like
he did not like that because they ruined his joke well
I would see, I would see a submarine over Los Angeles plus, never mind Ohio, right the fu-
Hey, don't talk about Ohio like that. All right, we're skibbity
You just said what's long and black and loads of semen I said it on Ohio class of marine
Exactly. Well, I said so that was the joke. It was submarine because he wasn't yeah
Foreman and it was it was funny. It was great
But when I jumped in with your mom and ruined his joke, it was it was I don't know it's kind of epic
What a faker though. He was he was fucking branched out of the fucking marines. I bet he was there
No, he's really an 80 man. I really like him baby Corman. He never
Usually they strap Corbin's on marine break marine units because the Marines are fucking retarded and always need a medic
My buddy my well, my buddy's navy Corbin. He's
He's like they fell down
I'm from the 90s in one day
I'm from the 70s in the 90s, but when I served
It was the Los Angeles class with submarines, did you ever watch the film called
Something of October what red October with oh god the gray guy George. No, not George Clooney
God, what is this fuck Sean Connery Sean Connery? Yes, yeah, man, red October was a great
So yeah, well, thank you for your service and in the armed forces. I
Tried marines would not accept me. Oh
Marines would not accept me. So mine was Marines or nothing. Yeah, nobody was there
Why would the Marines know except in 2008? I don't know when they changed their standards
But when I tried to join in 2008 freshly graduating high school
I have tattoos up the back of my neck and one of my
Tattoos was just slightly above the collar. I know they've loosened restrictions now, but I'm too old for that shit. Let's be real
Yeah, so I couldn't I couldn't join because of the tattoo like
again tattoo less than a quarter of an inch above have you seen marines these days they're more
got tattoos and vikings and they'll they'll accept a lot there's still a standard of tattoos
going in right that like there's still a certain level you have to meet when you join but once
Then it's pretty much no holds bars for the most part and you can do whatever the fuck you want to but once you're joining
There is still some regulation about it. It's a lot looser though
Obviously then when I tried to join but I mean let's be real. I would have but I was a complete fucking
I didn't wake up at all at that point. My brain was running on fucking complete autopilot
And I would have just been a grunt that fucking ended up probably getting blown up or doing some stupid shit
Yeah, blowing myself up. So, uh, you know
I'm alive today because I didn't get into the service, but I mean, I don't know if I did survive
I'd probably
Mm-hmm
But but here's the thing right if you had a half a brain
All right, well especially so you know to tell you're not willing to let me tell my story. Oh, you know
You're right. I'm sorry. I assumed. Oh
Wait, wait real quick before that story happens
Spunky had a question or something to say to me
before
Oh god, I don't remember. Yeah, it was about there was there was the doxing talk and then and then we diverted. I
Don't remember I apologize. It's okay. All right, so we can go past that. I mean, I don't remember so you're fine
I just remember you were saying something to me, but all right vanguard. I
Want to hear your military your military experience and yes
Real quick. Do you know much about how old cavalry?
No, but wait, wait, what service were you like?
But I mean more so like alright, so like the nation service like you know, there's the the royal guard royal whatever for you
You know what?
Yeah, you've got you've got sort of that correct, but I was in the British army. Yes. Ah, okay. All right
But I was part of the household division
Part of the household division. I was the Royal Horse Guards as in the household cavalry
I was close. All right. What what what did you what did you do as the household?
What did well from driving main battle tanks, right?
Oh
Reconnaissance vehicle truck tanks in form of West Germany
We did this
Sorry hard part zoom it in because I'm
Right there you go. So you know how to you know how to write a
That is what the household Calvary does for
Public view and also ceremony view
So you learn how to ride a horse and also operate a
tank
Yes
That's that's that's a fucking wild
Can you ride a horse?
No, no, no, I'm not making fun of it. I am saying that is such a wild
like a
Wild
You're creating a profession right profession difference in polar opposite ends, right?
but you're you've got your show end of being a Mountie and then
that's what people see but again you operate battle tanks like you operate
tanks that's yes that is a wild a wide a vast amount of knowledge and skill
being learned and that's what I mean I am absolutely appreciating you for that
or acknowledging you that that's fucking crazy
I mean, you ask one of the fucking, you ask a fucking Marine in a tank to ride a horse.
There's no fucking shot, bro.
Like, you ask them to tie their shoes.
It's good luck.
I mean, they know how to operate the tank.
Tie a, you know, tie a knot.
Good luck.
Right?
Like, that's what I'm getting at.
So you know shit.
That's it.
I, you know.
That's fucking crazy either way though. Uh
Do you mind I don't know if you consider it a dox or not
But like you know when you know the time frame you serve like the you know
Era when I consider it a dox put this way I serve the queen not the king
That's vague and rough
Well, I want to say it realistically this way though, I I don't honestly know how long
The rest or soul queen
Do you wanna put a window in it? Do you want to put a window on it? Let's talk about Gulf War one
Gulf War one
Okay
Actually you remember
Yeah, do you remember go for one? Can you remember when America invaded Iraq the first time?
Did I remember? No, because I was a small child, but I remember I know learning about it, right?
But I was like three years old when that happened, or four years old, I think.
George Bush senior, not George Bush Junior.
Oh, I know.
Cuz George Bush jr. Was just continuing the fucking legacy with the invasion of Iraq for nuclear weapons
All right, sorry either way, I didn't mean to detract but all right. No, that's cool. That's for the time
You know, I didn't want to
Yeah
Whatever you were comfortable with saying there though
Did you get
Maybe not in a judgment sense were you deployed at all in that time frame?
not necessarily just there but you know anywhere else was I deployed I don't
know actually I don't know what the differences in that statement but deployed
in the sense of you know other Nate service in other nations whether it be
Not necessarily, you know, offensive, defensive, or military, you know, even training, you know.
Yes, no, maybe.
I was saying deployed, deployed in the sense of any military, really activity, so not necessarily
offensive, defensive, active combat, training sense.
Did I serve in active duty?
No, I'm not saying necessarily active.
I'm kind of more so asking, kind of more so what you got to see, like, did you get to
I mean if you want to say I've traveled big time mate. I've traveled all over the planet big time
What was your favorite? I guess you know what fucking military excluded. That's not part of it
Where's your what's your favorite place you've traveled to in general, you know
The favorite place I've ever been
Germany
Ah, see?
Well, I've never gone there, but like I said, I wish we had Canada or Germany above us instead of Canada
Either way, uh-huh. What? Well, which what made Germany your favorite plate or you know the favorite travel?
Nice beer
Fair enough fair enough that is a renowned drinking drinking place
Anything else other than the booze nice women
Fair enough ooh
All right. All right now when you say it like that comparison
You know booze and women your next favorite destination
What do you mean by like, um, things you don't do military-wise?
Well, I didn't say, yeah, I don't mean it doesn't have to be, just in general,
your favorite in general from all of your life experience.
You know, so you said Germany and booze and women, what's your next booze and women destination?
Oh, yeah.
I know, I'm asking the tough questions.
I've got to see Britain.
Oh, alright, I didn't see that one, but, well, you know, I guess with some of the other
And I want to ask you what made up the difference between the Germany and Britain experience as far as both go
What?
Yeah, yeah, why did you like Germany better than Britain?
Germany's cleaner
You know, I would definitely assume that offer it
All right fair enough anything else on that one
aside from cleanliness well you didn't ask me about military and the best place
to operate things like that so oh yeah if you want to do the military what was
yeah your favorite okay military speaking what was your favorite place to
operate or you know training active duty whatever you were participating in at
All right
All right, okay, so on the operational standpoint why Germany aside from booze and women
Well, um you get to face off with a lot of Russians all the time
All right
now
Well, I assume it wasn't you know completely hostile at that point like
Are they just like an aggressive group of people like just you know their nature in general that you were I guess encountering
stating the face-off like that
Face-off like it wasn't active combat face-off you're saying right let me clarify
Anyway, let's just put it this way, when it came to Donald, sorry, did I say Donald?
I meant George Bush Sr.
What a coincidence.
Can I just mention the fact that, let's go back to Kuwait.